<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<httpclient:response xmlns:httpclient="http://exist-db.org/xquery/httpclient" statusCode="200">
    <httpclient:headers>
        <httpclient:header name="x-amz-id-2" value="tW2ePrRp7c3f699SxKQ04gg1iZeU1fe8rE9wDGpXRa7WkBnipaLBNINppieVBUVM"/>
        <httpclient:header name="x-amz-request-id" value="3CD8B7336553017F"/>
        <httpclient:header name="Date" value="Wed, 20 Aug 2014 09:47:29 GMT"/>
        <httpclient:header name="Last-Modified" value="Fri, 25 Apr 2014 22:41:58 GMT"/>
        <httpclient:header name="ETag" value="&#34;a568d13e8a966323c8abd6003a4bd739&#34;"/>
        <httpclient:header name="Accept-Ranges" value="bytes"/>
        <httpclient:header name="Content-Type" value="application/xml"/>
        <httpclient:header name="Content-Length" value="54189"/>
        <httpclient:header name="Server" value="AmazonS3"/>
    </httpclient:headers>
    <httpclient:body mimetype="application/xml" type="xml">
        <rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" version="2.0">
            <channel>
                <title>The Arabist Podcast</title>
                <link>http://arabist.net/</link>
                <description>Podcasts from Arabist.net, the website on Arab politics and culture.</description>
                <generator>Feeder 2.5.1(1836); Mac OS X Version 10.9.2 (Build 13C64) http://reinventedsoftware.com/feeder/</generator>
                <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
                <language>en</language>
                <copyright>Arabist.net 2009-2011</copyright>
                <pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2014 00:36:22 +0200</pubDate>
                <lastBuildDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2014 00:36:22 +0200</lastBuildDate>
                <category domain="http://arabist.net">News &amp; Politics</category>
                <image>
                    <url>http://web.me.com/issandr/podcasts/arabistico300podcast.jpg</url>
                    <title>Arabist.net Podcast</title>
                    <link>http://arabist.net/</link>
                    <width>300</width>
                    <height>300</height>
                </image>
                <atom:link href="http://arabist.s3.amazonaws.com/feeds/arabistpodcast.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
                <itunes:author>Arabist.net</itunes:author>
                <itunes:summary>Podcasts from Arabist.net, the website on Arab politics and culture.</itunes:summary>
                <itunes:keywords>arab, arabist, egypt, lebanon, palestine, syria, iraq, mideast, iran</itunes:keywords>
                <itunes:image href="http://arabist.s3.amazonaws.com/arabistico300podcast.jpg"/>
                <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                <itunes:owner>
                    <itunes:name>Issandr El Amrani</itunes:name>
                    <itunes:email>podcast@arabist.net</itunes:email>
                </itunes:owner>
                <itunes:block>no</itunes:block>
                <itunes:category text="News &amp; Politics"/>
                <item>
                    <title>The Arabist Podcast #46: "His program is the crisis"</title>
                    <description>Issandr El Amrani and Steve Negus are back with Ursula Lindsey to geek out on Egyptian politics. Does the presidential election matter? Are Sisi and Sabahi just two variants of Nasserism? Does anyone know what's going on anymore? These and other questions are considered, and Steve tell us about his trips to deep Upper Egypt, where sectarianism is never very far below the surface, echoes of the 1980s and 1990s are pondered and the shockwave of the counter-revolution crashes on some much deeper problems.</description>
                    <pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2014 00:17:14 +0200</pubDate>
                    <enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4a/arabist.s3.amazonaws.com/podcasts/arabistpodcast46.m4a" length="27604095" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">571167B3-D759-41FC-BB9C-1E94899269B5</guid>
                    <itunes:author>Issandr El Amrani, Ursula Lindsey, Steve Negus</itunes:author>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:duration>56:37</itunes:duration>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>The Arabist Podcast #45: Underdogs</title>
                    <description>Arabist podcast hosts Ursula Lindsey and Ashraf Khalil talk to Khaled Dawoud, a prominent Egyptian reporter and activist who campaigned to remove the Muslim Brotherhood from power but later resigned as spokesman for a secular political coalition in protest over the killing of Islamist demonstrators. Dawoud has been attacked from all sides of the political spectrum, as he continues to argue for a poliitically negotiated solution rather than the ongoing cycle of violence and repression. He looks back on his last three years of activism; the role of the revolutionary, secular movement; and whether, in ousting the Brotherhood, it became the pawn of the former regime and the military.</description>
                    <pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2014 16:53:19 +0200</pubDate>
                    <enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4a/arabist.s3.amazonaws.com/podcasts/arabistpodcast45.m4a" length="33509659" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">09CEB9E9-3116-4315-A398-8828AD54C4D6</guid>
                    <itunes:author>Ursula Lindsey, Ashraf Khalil, Khaled Dawoud</itunes:author>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:duration>1:08:04</itunes:duration>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>The Arabist Podcast #44: Just how bad is it exactly?</title>
                    <description>On this podcast, journalists Ursula Lindsey and Ashraf Khalil speak to Human Rights Watch's Sarah Lee Whitson about the greatest threats to human rights across the region, and about how to defend human rights in the midst of Egypt's "war on terrorism" and its crackdown on the Muslim Brotherhood.</description>
                    <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2013 11:51:34 +0200</pubDate>
                    <enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4a/arabist.s3.amazonaws.com/podcasts/arabist-podcast-44.m4a" length="20434546" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">2877CA8E-85D3-4CD6-AD65-1902A013CEC6</guid>
                    <itunes:author>Ursula Lindsey, Ashraf Khalil, Sarah Leah Whitson</itunes:author>
                    <itunes:summary>On this podcast, journalists Ursula Lindsey and Ashraf Khalil speak to Human Rights Watch's Sarah Lee Whitson about the greatest threats to human rights across the region, and about how to defend human rights in the midst of Egypt's "war on terrorism" and its crackdown on the Muslim Brotherhood.  </itunes:summary>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:duration>42:44</itunes:duration>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>The Arabist Podcast #43: Minority Report</title>
                    <description>The Arabist podcast is back after a long summer break, hosted by regulars Ursula Lindsey and Ashraf Khalil and featuring Lina Attalah, editor of Mada Masr. We discuss terrorism and military operations in the Sinai peninsula; the Egyptian media's cheering of the army; and the shortcomings of Egypt's new constitution.</description>
                    <pubDate>Sat, 12 Oct 2013 18:48:37 +0200</pubDate>
                    <enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4a/arabist.s3.amazonaws.com/podcasts/arabistpodcast43.m4a" length="32545877" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">33D04232-6372-4F1B-A5EF-593C3B77CD61</guid>
                    <itunes:author>Ursula Lindsey, Ashraf Khalil, Lina Attalah</itunes:author>
                    <itunes:image href="http://arabist.s3.amazonaws.com/arabistico300podcast.jpg"/>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:duration>1:05:50</itunes:duration>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>The Arabist Podcast #41: The Terrible Twos</title>
                    <description>More chaos and mayhem in Egypt over the weekend on the second anniversary of the January, 25 2011 uprising. Is Egypt becoming ungovernorable? What do the protestors want, can the opposition come up with a credible position, is the Muslim Brotherhood even interested in negotiating? Has the polarization created in late 2012 over the new constitution and Morsi's decree created an irreversible dynamic towards more repression, chaos, and instability? So many questions, so few clear answers — but we give it our best shot.</description>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jan 2013 12:25:53 +0200</pubDate>
                    <enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4a/arabist.s3.amazonaws.com/podcasts/arabistpodcast41.m4a" length="23191120" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">84E73CD4-A445-4E54-9259-24FE52D671CB</guid>
                    <itunes:author>Issandr El Amrani, Ashraf Khalil, Ursula Lindsey</itunes:author>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:duration>47:04</itunes:duration>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>The Arabist Podcast #40: Referendumb</title>
                    <description>The first round of Egypt's referendum on the draft constitution rushed through by Islamist forces has taken place, resulting in a narrow win for Islamists in early results. Our guest Hossam Bahgat, Director of the Egyptian Initiative for Personal Rights, helps us decode the trends, processes, and politics of the current crisis and how it might unfold.</description>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 17 Dec 2012 19:25:44 +0200</pubDate>
                    <enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4a/arabist.s3.amazonaws.com/podcasts/arabistpodcast40.m4a" length="37192367" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">CEDCB1F3-B7A0-4611-8783-03A124D895C7</guid>
                    <itunes:author>Issandr El Amrani, Ashraf Khalil, Ursula Lindsey, Hossam Bahgat</itunes:author>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:duration>1:15:34</itunes:duration>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>The Arabist Podcast #39: Capture the castle</title>
                    <description>On this week’s podcast, Issandr and Ursula are joined by Human Rights Watch’s Heba Morayef and The Economist’s Max Rodenbeck to try to ascertain which of the developments of the last week we find the most disturbing: Morsi’s extraordinary new powers? The Muslim Brotherhood’s aping of Mubarak-era tactics? A rushed constitution with major contradictions, ambiguities and curbs on freedoms? The stark political polarization? Take your pick.</description>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2012 19:03:20 +0200</pubDate>
                    <enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4a/arabist.s3.amazonaws.com/podcasts/arabistpodcast39.m4a" length="24134267" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">6D527665-A5CB-4210-9468-BC0FBC6BAD94</guid>
                    <itunes:author>Issandr El Amrani, Ursula Lindsey, Max Rodenbeck, Heba Morayef</itunes:author>
                    <itunes:image href="http://arabist.s3.amazonaws.com/arabistico300podcast.jpg"/>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:duration>49:37</itunes:duration>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>The Arabist Podcast #38 (Part 2/2): This is Cairo</title>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Here is Part 2 of this week’s podcast. This was an experiment: Christopher Lydon of Radio Open Source is in town and we invited him to join us and gathered some of our accomplished friends to discuss a topic that is close to all of our hearts: the city of Cairo and the shape it’s in today. Our conversation with architect and urban planner Omar El Nagati, blogger Mohamed El Shahed and writer/curator Sara Rifki was as rich, dense and meandering as the city itself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We discussed the meaning and potential of Cairo’s reigning informality; how to find a balance between local initiative and state planning and regulation; whether the Muslim Brotherhood has a different urban development vision than the Mubarak regime; and the many exciting ways that Egyptians are laying claim to public space today.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2012 11:25:53 +0200</pubDate>
                    <enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4a/arabist.s3.amazonaws.com/podcasts/arabistpodcast38-part2.m4a" length="36549506" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">3D9BF6FF-CC70-403B-B876-21A88D8FB818</guid>
                    <itunes:author>Issandr El Amrani, Ashraf Khalil, Ursula Lindsey, Chris Lydon</itunes:author>
                    <itunes:image href="http://arabist.s3.amazonaws.com/arabistico300podcast.jpg"/>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:duration>1:13:03</itunes:duration>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>The Arabist Podcast #38 (Part 1/2): History on repeat</title>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;A friend here in Cairo recently told me she felt history was repeating itself all around her: a new Egyptian train tragedy; bodies of Palestinian children being dug out of the rubble of Gaza as Israel carries out yet another bombardment; protesters and police facing off again, on year later, in Mohamed Mahmoud Street.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On Thursday evening President Mohamed Morsi issued a decree that involved some repetitions of its own: he sacked the corrupt public prosecutor (again, after a first failed attempt); he ordered the re-trial of policemen and former regime figures. Most strikingly, he gave himself and the Islamist-dominated constituent assembly immunity from all judicial challenges. “Don’t worry” Morsi repeated half a dozen times during a speech on Friday — the sweeping new powers he has given himself (which include the power to take any necessary action to defend the revolution and national security) are only temporary, and will not be misused, he said. But the thousands of protesters who had already come out and those who had attacked several offices of the Brotherhood’s Freedom and Justice Party were indeed worried, and fuming, at their sense that history is repeating itself: Morsi is an elected president, but he has given himself more powers than even Mubarak had.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the first installment of a two-part podcast (we had planned one on a different topic before the crisis), Issandr and Ashraf discuss the weekend’s events. The second part will be up soon.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 25 Nov 2012 13:35:23 +0200</pubDate>
                    <enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4a/arabist.s3.amazonaws.com/podcasts/arabistpodcast38.m4a" length="13692054" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">F3DED304-1AF8-4792-B536-D4166273AC22</guid>
                    <itunes:author>Issandr El Amrani, Ashraf Khalil, Ursula Lindsey</itunes:author>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:duration>27:44</itunes:duration>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>The Arabist Podcast #37: A Constitutional Smörgåsbord</title>
                    <description>The long promised podcast on everything you wanted to know about the new Arab constitutions but were afraid to ask is here. We sit with guest Zaid al-Ali, a member of the team that advised on the Iraqi constitution in 2005 and now advisor to IDEA on constitution-writing, who has been monitoring the constitution-drafting processes in Egypt, Tunisia and Libya. We start with Libya, where things are just getting started and the big questions are about federalism and sharing the revenues from the oil sector. Then we look at Tunisia, where the process is humming along despite some hiccups and the new constitution should be adopted by the middle of next year. And finally we take a wide-ranging look at the contents of Egypt's constittution-writing process, just as the controversy pitting Islamists vs. secularists is heating up. What are the real problems with the drafts published so far? Al-Ali's first take is that, perhaps most importantly, that is no revolutionary constitution: it's mostly an adaptation of the previous one, and the divides often exaggerated by a badly managed process. Grab a beverage and get ready to make use of your pause and rewind buttons: this is a dense one.</description>
                    <pubDate>Sat, 10 Nov 2012 22:20:27 +0200</pubDate>
                    <enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4a/arabist.s3.amazonaws.com/podcasts/arabistpodcast37.m4a" length="35973524" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">A6DD312C-4BB8-4CA7-B2FA-53CDB99BE12C</guid>
                    <itunes:author>Issandr El Amrani, Ashraf Khalil, Ursula Lindsey, Zaid al-Ali</itunes:author>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:duration>1:13:15</itunes:duration>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>The Arabist Podcast #36: Mean Streets</title>
                    <description>The gang talk about Ashraf's heroism battling off feral Tahrir hordes, secular discontent and the politics of Egypt's constitution. We top it all off with talk about the US presidential debates and the surprising lack of vision for the US in the Middle East.</description>
                    <pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2012 14:23:52 +0200</pubDate>
                    <enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/arabist.s3.amazonaws.com/podcasts/podcast36.mp3" length="27060813" type="audio/mpeg"/>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">4C08D2E2-9D70-4800-9F19-57AA9E380E87</guid>
                    <itunes:author>Issandr El Amrani, Ashraf Khalil, Ursula Lindsey</itunes:author>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:duration>56:22</itunes:duration>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>The Arabist Podcast #35: The embassy riots and their aftermath </title>
                    <description>We're back in Cairo and devote most of this episode to the US embassy riots: how they started, what they represent, the culture wars they involve, the MB-Salafi battle for who is the biggest defender of Islam, and much more. Also, we ask, what was Morsi thinking, and how might he make it up in his first visit to the US as president of Egypt.</description>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 24 Sep 2012 12:43:25 +0200</pubDate>
                    <enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4a/arabist.s3.amazonaws.com/podcasts/arabistpodcast35.m4a" length="23845330" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">F9BAB6BC-4A81-44A3-93EF-19B80A1F9E5A</guid>
                    <itunes:author>Issandr El Amrani, Ashraf Khalil, Ursula Lindsey</itunes:author>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:duration>48:32</itunes:duration>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>The Arabist Podcast #34: Morsi's Night of Power</title>
                    <description>We interrupt our break from the podcast to discuss the latest in Egyptian politics: Morsi asserting his presidential powers, the changes in the Egyptian military, where Egypt's foreign policy might go from here, early worries about press freedom in Morsi's Egypt, and how the opposition can ounter-balance to the Muslim Brothers' strength - if it is even capable of that.</description>
                    <pubDate>Thu, 23 Aug 2012 16:27:31 +0200</pubDate>
                    <enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4a/arabist.s3.amazonaws.com/podcasts/arabistpodcast34.m4a" length="32250202" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">FE64910A-C7F7-46EF-B2A2-145215447303</guid>
                    <itunes:author>Issandr El Amrani, Ashraf Khalil</itunes:author>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:duration>1:05:28</itunes:duration>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>The Arabist Podcast #33: Egypt's Quantum Politics, or Schrodinger's Transition</title>
                    <description>It's never a dull day in Egypt. Your exhausted podcasters explain the week that turned Egypt's flailing transition into a full-blown military coup, breaking down the steps: the Supreme Constitutional Court verdicts, SCAF's new constitutional declaration, the dual claims for the presidency, Mubarak's night of the living dead, and more.  It's as if Egypt's politics have entered a quantum state, where every possibility is true and false at the same time. Fasten  your seatbelts, turbulence ahead.</description>
                    <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jun 2012 18:05:52 +0200</pubDate>
                    <enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4a/arabist.s3.amazonaws.com/podcasts/arabistpodcast33.m4a" length="33875183" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">DCA7C703-9656-419E-AA7D-A3B8598D579B</guid>
                    <itunes:author>Issandr El Amrani, Ashraf Khalil, Ursula Lindsey</itunes:author>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:duration>1:08:58</itunes:duration>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>The Arabist Podcast #32: Really?!?</title>
                    <description>The usual three are joined by Ustaz Doktor Josh Stacher to discuss the upcoming second round of Egypt’s presidential election, judicial shenanigans and SCAF’s plotting, what kinds of powers the next president will and won’t have, US-Egypt relations, Salafi sex scandals and of course the infamous public service announcement warning against foreign spies that has been airing on Egyptian TV.</description>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jun 2012 20:17:52 +0200</pubDate>
                    <enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4a/arabist.s3.amazonaws.com/podcasts/arabistpodcast32.m4a" length="28150351" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">8D508882-5CC4-4461-AEE5-DFB6644CACF2</guid>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:duration>57:18</itunes:duration>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>The Arabist Podcast #31: A7atein</title>
                    <description>We talk about the results of the first round of presidential elections, the dilemma facing the one-half of voters who did not vote for the candidates that made it to the second round. In a break from Egypt,  we discuss the terrible massacre at Houla, Syria and its consequences. And we examine today's verdict from the Mubarak trial, what it means and how angry people are about it — and how it might influence the electoral calculus of the next two weeks.</description>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jun 2012 12:08:42 +0200</pubDate>
                    <enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4a/arabist.s3.amazonaws.com/podcasts/arabistpodcast31.m4a" length="29536115" type="audio/mp4"/>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">C58AC44D-E43D-4F7E-AD32-75184E71C901</guid>
                    <itunes:author>Issandr El Amrani, Ashraf Khalil, Ursula Lindsey</itunes:author>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:duration>1:00:08</itunes:duration>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>The Arabist Podcast #30: Indecision time</title>
                    <description>The first round of Egypt's presidential elections are upon us. We've talked about why the context for them is flawed, now we talk about the pure politics: who's ahead, who's trailing, what we think will happen, and what the country can handle — and give an anti-endorsement.</description>
                    <pubDate>Wed, 23 May 2012 12:05:47 +0200</pubDate>
                    <enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4a/arabist.s3.amazonaws.com/podcasts/arabistpodcast30.m4a" length="31674877" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">B362C9AD-756A-48DD-BA30-3833ACAAFB69</guid>
                    <itunes:author>Issandr El Amrani, Ashraf Khalil, Ursula Lindsey, Charles Levinson, Rolla Scolari</itunes:author>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:duration>1:04:29</itunes:duration>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>The Arabist Podcast #29: Presidency or bust!</title>
                    <description>There's 15 days left to the Egyptian presidential elections. We examine the insurgent campaign of Islamist Abdel Moneim Aboul Fotouh, ask whether the Muslim Brothers are dangerously off-balance as they try to catch up, look at Amr Moussa's claim that he's the only candidate ready to be president on day one, and wonder whether the Abbaseya clashes and other factors contributing to Egypt's political instability could derail the elections or might simply continue even if there's a president.</description>
                    <pubDate>Tue, 08 May 2012 20:56:25 +0200</pubDate>
                    <enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4a/arabist.s3.amazonaws.com/podcasts/arabistpodcast29.m4a" length="30626027" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">A232BD46-06E9-45B6-9DB5-04D71A79CCE7</guid>
                    <itunes:author>Issandr El Amrani, Ashraf Khalil, Ursula Lindsey</itunes:author>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:duration>1:02:12</itunes:duration>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>The Arabist Podcast #28: And then there were 13</title>
                    <description>ssandr El Amrani, Ashraf Khalil and Ursula Lindsey are back after skipping out on the most confusing month in the history of Egyptian politics. We catch up on the state of whatever is left of a transition,  presidential politics and elimination of candidates, and examine the chances of some of the ones that made the cut.</description>
                    <pubDate>Fri, 20 Apr 2012 19:50:38 +0200</pubDate>
                    <enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4a/arabist.s3.amazonaws.com/podcasts/arabistpodcast28.m4a" length="26643334" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">F361E7F5-8DC7-4BC1-87D6-F8D76F1E1B6A</guid>
                    <itunes:author>Issandr El Amrani, Ashraf Khalil, Ursula Lindsey</itunes:author>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:duration>54:14</itunes:duration>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>The Arabist Podcast #27: Back in business</title>
                    <description>The original team is back together to discuss the aftermath of the US-Egypt NGO crisis, dissent in the UAE, and Egypt's presidential elections.</description>
                    <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2012 15:52:36 +0200</pubDate>
                    <enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4a/arabist.s3.amazonaws.com/podcasts/arabistpodcast27.m4a" length="27942680" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">061A29F0-9905-437C-9358-13D7FA13D4F6</guid>
                    <itunes:author>Issandr El Amrani, Ursula Lindsey, Ashraf Khalil</itunes:author>
                    <itunes:summary>The original team is back together to discuss the aftermath of the US-Egypt NGO crisis, dissent in the UAE, and Egypt's presidential elections.</itunes:summary>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:duration>56:44</itunes:duration>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>The Arabist Podcast #26: The Aalam Wassef Episode</title>
                    <description>Our special guest in this episode, Aalam Wassef, was an underground guerrilla video artist and activist who went by the pseudonym Ahmed Sherif. He continues to make videos and launch activist projects under his real name, except now the target is SCAF rather than Mubarak. We discuss his work, the call for a general strike to boot SCAF out, Egypt's military-industrial complex and the NGO crisis between Cairo and Washington.</description>
                    <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2012 17:20:46 +0200</pubDate>
                    <enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4a/arabist.s3.amazonaws.com/podcasts/arabistpodcast26.m4a" length="28646752" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">07E1478C-6859-44A9-9A00-29072CD86B52</guid>
                    <itunes:author>Issandr El Amrani, Ursula Lindsey, Aalam Wassef</itunes:author>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:duration>58:19</itunes:duration>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>The Arabist Podcast #25: A divisive anniversary</title>
                    <description>In this episode, we discuss Mohamed ElBaradei's decision not to run for president Egypt, the preparations for Egypt's new parliament and for the anniversary of the January 25 uprising. All through the lens of Ashraf Khalil's new book, Liberation Square.</description>
                    <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2012 10:16:15 +0200</pubDate>
                    <enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4a/arabist.s3.amazonaws.com/podcasts/arabistpodcast25.m4a" length="27411634" type="audio/mp4"/>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">7C8BA387-D491-4FA4-894C-F39CC587663C</guid>
                    <itunes:author>Issandr El Amrani, Ursula Lindsey, Ashraf Khalil</itunes:author>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:duration>55:48</itunes:duration>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>The Arabist Podcast #24: It's a new year</title>
                    <description>For the first episode of 2012, we reflect of what's to come, discuss the Arab League mission in Syria, Egypt's elections and the rest of the transition timeline, take a first look at the presidential candidates,  and wonder about what will take place on January 25, the anniversary of the Egyptian uprising.</description>
                    <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2012 18:01:02 +0200</pubDate>
                    <enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4a/arabist.s3.amazonaws.com/podcasts/arabistpodcast24.m4a" length="25888764" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">B7731E5A-56C6-4FB5-B361-67FB9983550D</guid>
                    <itunes:author>Issandr El Amrani, Ursula Lindsey, Ashraf Khalil</itunes:author>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:duration>52:42</itunes:duration>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>The Arabist Podcast #23: The Sandmonkey Episode</title>
                    <description>In this week's episode, Ursula and I talk to the legendary Egyptian blogger Sandmonkey, a major figure of the online coverage of the uprising. Also known as Mahmoud Salem, Sandmonkey was an unlucky candidate in the first round of Egypt's parliamentary elections, standing in a Cairo district. He tells us about his experience, and how he sees the most recent clashes between protestors and the army in Tahrir.</description>
                    <pubDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2011 11:03:56 +0200</pubDate>
                    <enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4a/arabist.s3.amazonaws.com/podcasts/arabistpodcast23.m4a" length="27233243" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">E4698A65-77C1-4096-AC4F-6F5D02BB5D4D</guid>
                    <itunes:author>Issandr El Amrani, Ursula Lindsey, Mahmoud Salem</itunes:author>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:duration>55:14</itunes:duration>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>The Arabist Podcast #21: Electoral Dilemmas</title>
                    <description>We take a semi-break from the Egyptian elections to look at the bigger picture: the wave of elections bringing Islamists to office parties across the region, what Morocco's pretty tame Islamists might  do, the electoral dilemmas of non-Islamists, and more. And we re-examine the issues of Saudi women getting behind the wheels, and the backlash against that from the powerful moron lobby among the Wahhabis.</description>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2011 22:16:45 +0200</pubDate>
                    <enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4a/arabist.s3.amazonaws.com/podcasts/arabistpodcast21.m4a" length="26351400" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">5226C4D9-D3F6-493E-9F52-5B322A839172</guid>
                    <itunes:author>Issandr El Amrani, Ursula Lindsey, Ashraf Khalil</itunes:author>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:duration>53:38</itunes:duration>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>The Arabist Podcast #20: Islamic Republic of Egypt?</title>
                    <description>In this edition of the Arabist Podcast, we introduce a brand new segment, Regional Cliffnotes, and then delve into the initial results from the first round of Egypt's parliamentary elections. It's a triumph for the Islamists, with the Muslim Brotherhood getting a comfortable plurality, but the real surprise is that Salafists are the country's second political force. And that's something that worries us. Don't forget to get back to us with comments at podcast@arabist.net!</description>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 04 Dec 2011 16:02:58 +0200</pubDate>
                    <enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4a/arabist.s3.amazonaws.com/podcasts/arabistpodcast20.m4a" length="18858534" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">24D974FE-ACFE-4594-9283-ECEB6D9C7698</guid>
                    <itunes:author>Issandr El Amrani, Ursula Lindsey, Ashraf Khalil</itunes:author>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:duration>38:12</itunes:duration>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>The Arabist Podcast #19: Elections!</title>
                    <description>So the elections in Egypt are upon us, and they didn't turn out to be a catastrophe. In fact, the turnout is looking good. But should we all be celebrating? Ursula Lindsey and I argue that while Egyptians have shown they're ready for democracy, the process still leaves much to be desired. And in any case, what happens next?</description>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2011 20:35:50 +0200</pubDate>
                    <enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4a/arabist.s3.amazonaws.com/podcasts/arabistpodcast19.m4a" length="17129361" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">A8AB1396-7837-4176-A6A1-C19475830658</guid>
                    <itunes:author>Issandr El Amrani, Ursula Lindsey</itunes:author>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:duration>34:51</itunes:duration>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>The Arabist Podcast #18: Back to Tahrir</title>
                    <description>After the last two days' exceptional events in Tahrir Square, Egypt seems to teeter on the brink of another revolution or political chaos. We discuss the recent violence and the scenarios the country faces.</description>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2011 22:41:19 +0200</pubDate>
                    <enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4a/arabist.s3.amazonaws.com/podcasts/arabistpodcast18.m4a" length="19594976" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">129880A7-E248-4B68-8D10-483597922986</guid>
                    <itunes:author>Issandr El Amrani, Ursula Lindsey, Ashraf Khalil</itunes:author>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:duration>39:42</itunes:duration>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>The Arabist Podcast #17: Doom and Gloom</title>
                    <description>In this edition of the Arabist Podcast, we look at the Arab League's decision to suspend Syria's membership and the mess of Egypt's elections.</description>
                    <pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2011 16:25:35 +0200</pubDate>
                    <enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4a/arabist.s3.amazonaws.com/podcasts/arabistpodcast17.m4a" length="32271618" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">F38643C8-A202-4E61-977D-1FB7D0E0595F</guid>
                    <itunes:author>Issandr El Amrani, Ursula Lindsey, Ashraf Khalil</itunes:author>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:duration>1:05:30</itunes:duration>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>The Arabist Podcast #16: %^&amp;* the French!</title>
                    <description>After a two-week hiatus, we return to talk about Tunisia's elections, Nahda's success and the work ahead in that country's transition, why Egypt is not as lucky, and how much we hate the French.</description>
                    <pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2011 17:56:53 +0200</pubDate>
                    <enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4a/arabist.s3.amazonaws.com/podcasts/podcast16.m4a" length="38284381" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">AA2F3F43-A187-4B62-B7E1-100A4F66D459</guid>
                    <itunes:author>Issandr El Amrani, Ursula Lindsey, Ashraf Khalil</itunes:author>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:duration>1:17:41</itunes:duration>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>The Arabist Interview: Youssef Sidhoum on Maspero</title>
                    <description>An interview with Youssef Sidhoum, a prominent Egyptian intellectual and editor of the Coptic Weekly al-Watani, on the events of October 9, 2011 at Maspero.</description>
                    <pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2011 16:28:35 +0200</pubDate>
                    <enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4a/arabist.s3.amazonaws.com/podcasts/arabistinterview1.m4a" length="7684586" type="audio/mp4"/>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">BA3CD362-302F-45D9-BF6F-4B00D9308190</guid>
                    <itunes:author>Issandr El Amrani</itunes:author>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:duration>15:33</itunes:duration>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>The Arabist Podcast #15: After Maspero</title>
                    <description>In this week’s podcast, we turn to the tragic events on October 9 in Downtown Cairo, when at least 25 people (mostly Coptic protestors) were killed at the Maspero state TV building. Ashraf, Ursula and I host New York Review of Books contributor Yasmine El Rashidi, an eyewitness to the massacre, and talk about what happened and its consequences.</description>
                    <pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2011 15:05:28 +0200</pubDate>
                    <enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4a/arabist.s3.amazonaws.com/podcasts/arabistpodcast15.m4a" length="28284533" type="audio/mp4"/>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">3BDD74ED-BC43-4795-9021-BD9C8CAFEAEC</guid>
                    <itunes:author>Issandr El Amrani, Ursula Lindsey, Ashraf Khalil, Yasmine El Rashidi</itunes:author>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:duration>57:26</itunes:duration>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>The Arabist Podcast #14: The Ones That Didn't Make It (Yet)</title>
                    <description>This week we discuss those Arab revolutions that are still in progress or are being stopped dead in their tracks: Yemen, Bahrain and Syria.</description>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2011 12:40:19 +0200</pubDate>
                    <enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4a/arabist.s3.amazonaws.com/podcasts/arabistpodcast14.m4a" length="23800844" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">42B389C6-E464-48E9-86E8-CBA0064F99AE</guid>
                    <itunes:author>Issandr El Amrani, Ursula Lindsey, Ashraf Khalil</itunes:author>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:duration>48:18</itunes:duration>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>The Arabist Podcast #13: Post-Qadhafi, pre-Tantawi?</title>
                    <description>This week, Ursula and Ashraf host guests from Libya Ahmed Shukr and Anjali Kamat. They talk de-Qadhafization, the state of the (counter) revolution in Egypt, and of Muhammad Tantawi's suit.</description>
                    <pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2011 11:42:40 +0200</pubDate>
                    <enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4a/arabist.s3.amazonaws.com/podcasts/arabistpodcast13.m4a" length="23318808" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">6989D61F-54BD-477E-AA9E-87234F5A4A0B</guid>
                    <itunes:author>Issandr El Amrani, Ursula Lindsey, Ashraf Khalil, Ahmed Shukr, Anjali Kamat</itunes:author>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:duration>47:23</itunes:duration>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>The Arabist #12: We regret to inform you that revolution is cancelled</title>
                    <description>This week, Ashraf Khalil is back and we talk about the worrying turn Egypt's transition has taken, between the reinstatement of the Emergency Law, restrictions on media, threats against strikers and more. We also discuss Turkish PM Recep Erdogan's visit to Cairo, his reception by the army and Islamists, and which Turkish model is applicable in Egypt — if any.</description>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 18 Sep 2011 10:37:41 +0200</pubDate>
                    <enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4a/arabist.s3.amazonaws.com/podcasts/podcast12.m4a" length="27149390" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">FCDB2ABB-2423-4043-8BB9-0980BA0C1D30</guid>
                    <itunes:author>Issandr El Amrani, Ursula Lindsey, Ashraf Khalil</itunes:author>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:duration>55:03</itunes:duration>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>The Arabist Podcast #11: The embassy and the trial</title>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;In this week's podcast, AFP reporter Samer Al Atrush and journalist Steve Negus join Ursula Lindsey. We discuss the clashes of Friday 9 September, in which protester defaced the Ministry of Interior, broke into the Israeli embassy and fought the police, and ask: why did the army and police seem to stand back? And has the protest movement let itself in for a crackdown?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We also discuss Mubarak's trial (for ordering police to shoot at demonstrators, and for corruption) which so far has offered little in the way of a smoking gun and has been marred by chaos. Samer gives eye-witness accounts of the clashes around the Israeli embassy and of courtroom shenanigans.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2011 11:30:11 +0200</pubDate>
                    <enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4a/arabist.s3.amazonaws.com/podcasts/arabistpodcast11.m4a" length="25029753" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">F275F8FA-B0C3-4E9B-96E0-15BB5C6804D9</guid>
                    <itunes:author>Ursula Lindsey, Steve Negus, Samer Atrush</itunes:author>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:duration>50:44</itunes:duration>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>The Arabist Podcast #10: Libya and its consequences</title>
                    <description>We delayed this week's podcast to bring you two guests with expert knowledge of the Libyan war and its regional consequences: Steve Negus, who just returned from Tripoli and Benghazi, and Middle East correspondent for The Economist Max Rodenbeck. (Ashraf Khalil is off this week dealing with a looming book deadline.) We talk about why Tripoli fell so fast and how secure it is now, what might happen in Sirte and Sebha, the last Qadhafi strongholds, and what governance might look like in Libya for the foreseable future. We also discuss whether there is a Libyan model for humanitarian intervention, what it might mean for Syria, Qatar's steroid diplomacy, and still more. Finally, we discuss Libyan novelist Hisham Matar's novels and play a song from Libya's reggae-influenced pop music.</description>
                    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2011 09:59:15 +0200</pubDate>
                    <enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4a/arabist.s3.amazonaws.com/podcasts/podcast10.m4a" length="31687977" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">591CE45B-2E09-49D4-BAFE-7987A8E16248</guid>
                    <itunes:author>Issandr El Amrani, Ursula Lindsey, Steve Negus, Max Rodenbeck</itunes:author>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:duration>1:04:18</itunes:duration>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>The Arabist Podcast #9: Revolution Jetlag</title>
                    <description>We're back from our break and talk Tea Party politics, Mubarak trial, what's happening in Sinai, and the beginning of the end for Syria and Libya.</description>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2011 00:06:49 +0200</pubDate>
                    <enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4a/arabist.s3.amazonaws.com/podcasts/podcast9.m4a" length="25357226" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">992882A5-8B72-4BFA-9AF8-C58696121C68</guid>
                    <itunes:author>Issandr El Amrani, Ursula Lindsey, Ashraf Khalil</itunes:author>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:duration>51:25</itunes:duration>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>The Arabist Podcast #8: What's up in Sohag </title>
                    <description>In this week's podcast, more on the Tahrir Square sit-in, the never-ending cabinet shuffle, politics in Upper Egypt, the movies that defined the late Mubarak era, and new Arabic comics.</description>
                    <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2011 23:47:09 +0200</pubDate>
                    <enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4a/arabist.s3.amazonaws.com/podcasts/arabistpodcast8.m4a" length="21849324" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">644F34FB-3C57-40C1-8F6D-6E92EA6452B2</guid>
                    <itunes:author>Issandr El Amrani, Ursula Lindsey, Ashraf Khalil, Steve Negus</itunes:author>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:duration>44:16</itunes:duration>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>The Arabist Podcast #7: No Satisfaction </title>
                    <description>In this week’s podcast, Ashraf Khalil is given time off and we host the not-street-artist Ganzeer, one of the brains being Rolling Bulb and a series of murals honoring the martyrs of the revolution across Cairo. We discuss the current standoff between protestors camping in Tahrir Square and elsewhere, and review David Wolman’s The Instigators.</description>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2011 02:35:09 +0200</pubDate>
                    <enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4a/arabist.s3.amazonaws.com/podcasts/arabistpodcast7.m4a" length="23238029" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">CAF09962-CFF7-4D0B-8598-D54AA158BDCE</guid>
                    <itunes:author>Issandr El Amrani, Ursula Lindsey</itunes:author>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:duration>47:08</itunes:duration>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Arabist.net Podcast #1: Max Rodenbeck on Iran</title>
                    <description>Issandr El Amrani interviews Max Rodenbeck, Middle East correspondent for The Economist and contributor to the New York Review of Books, on Iran's political crisis.</description>
                    <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jun 2009 18:13:59 +0300</pubDate>
                    <enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4a/arabist.s3.amazonaws.com/podcasts/arabistpodcast1.m4a" length="14037968" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://web.me.com/issandr/podcasts/arabistpodcast1.m4a</guid>
                    <itunes:author>Issandr El Amrani</itunes:author>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Issandr El Amrani interviews Max Rodenbeck, Middle East correspondent for The Economist and contributor to the New York Review of Books, on Iran's political crisis.</itunes:subtitle>
                    <itunes:keywords>news, iran, politics, moussavi</itunes:keywords>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:duration>30:09</itunes:duration>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Arabist.net Podcast #2: Joshua Stacher on Gamal Mubarak</title>
                    <description>Ursula Lindsey interviews Joshua Stacher, Assistant Professor at Kent State University, on Gamal Mubarak's prospects as the next president of Egypt.</description>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2009 09:19:35 +0300</pubDate>
                    <enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4a/arabist.s3.amazonaws.com/podcasts/arabistpodcast2.m4a" length="14523264" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://web.me.com/issandr/podcasts/arabistpodcast2.m4a</guid>
                    <itunes:author>Issandr El Amrani</itunes:author>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Ursula Lindsey interviews Joshua Stacher, Assistant Professor at Kent State University, on Gamal Mubarak's prospects as the next president of Egypt.</itunes:subtitle>
                    <itunes:keywords>egypt, hosnimubarak, mubarak, gamalmubarak, gamal</itunes:keywords>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:duration>30:07</itunes:duration>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Arabist.net Podcast #3: The Where’s Waldo of Espionage</title>
                    <description>This week: ubiquitous Israeli spies, Mohamed ElBaradei and Amr Khaled, Saudi women drivers and “Messages from Tahrir”.</description>
                    <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2011 17:13:59 +0200</pubDate>
                    <enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4a/arabist.s3.amazonaws.com/podcasts/arabistpodcast3.m4a" length="14523264" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://web.me.com/issandr/podcasts/arabistpodcast-2011-06-17.m4a</guid>
                    <itunes:author>Issandr El Amrani, Ashraf Khalil, Ursula Lindsey</itunes:author>
                    <itunes:keywords>news, egypt, arab, elbaradei, saudi, women tahrir</itunes:keywords>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:duration>42:45</itunes:duration>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Lunch with the Arabist #1: Helena Cobban and William B. Quandt</title>
                    <description>Introducing Lunch with Arabist: conversations with Middle East experts and more. This week we talk to Helena Cobban of Just World Books and her husband William B. Quandt, professor of politics at the University of Virginia and one-time negotiator at the Camp David negotiations for US President Jimmy Carter.</description>
                    <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2011 02:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
                    <enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4a/arabist.s3.amazonaws.com/podcasts/lunchwiththearabist1.m4a" length="7281693" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">907E4F96-F513-4258-B891-1972CD168F30</guid>
                    <itunes:author>Issandr El Amrani, Ursula Lindsey</itunes:author>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:duration>14:42</itunes:duration>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Arabist.net Podcast #4: The Manchurian Candidate</title>
                    <description>In this week's podcast, we discuss the "Constitution First" vs. "Elections First" debate in Egypt and Sheikh al-Azhar's proposal, the silence surrounding Syria and Bahrain, the ADC's attempt to prevent Syrian artist Malek Jandani from playing a pro-uprising song and review the autobiography of Egyptian ex-Muslim Brother and presidential candidate Abdel Moneim Aboul Fotouh, and wonder if he's really been kicked out of the group.</description>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2011 09:37:43 +0200</pubDate>
                    <enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4a/arabist.s3.amazonaws.com/podcasts/arabistpodcast4.m4a" length="27075523" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">BC900DFA-911A-4AFB-824C-A4A3F08D8214</guid>
                    <itunes:author>Issandr El Amrani, Ursula Lindsey, Ashraf Khalil</itunes:author>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:duration>56:23</itunes:duration>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Lunch with the Arabist #2: Ibn Kafka</title>
                    <description>We eat sushi with Moroccan blogger Ibn Kafka and ask him his thoughts on the new constitution King Muhammad VI has proposed.</description>
                    <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2011 14:12:53 +0200</pubDate>
                    <enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4a/arabist.s3.amazonaws.com/podcasts/lunchwiththearabist2.m4a" length="5864978" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">9FA34291-6632-4023-B01A-D51FDBA3EF3B</guid>
                    <itunes:author>Issandr El Amrani</itunes:author>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:duration>11:50</itunes:duration>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>The Arabist Podcast #5: Justice deferred</title>
                    <description>This week, we look at the role the Khaled Said affair played in mobilizing Egyptians against police abuse, the recent clashes in Tahrir Square and the role of women in politics post-revolution.</description>
                    <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2011 11:19:01 +0200</pubDate>
                    <enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4a/arabist.s3.amazonaws.com/podcasts/arabistpodcast5.m4a" length="28332978" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">2E595271-075F-48AD-8559-473CC662C2CA</guid>
                    <itunes:author>Ursula Lindsey, Ashraf Khalil</itunes:author>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:duration>30:03</itunes:duration>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>The Arabist Podcast #6: It's hot out there</title>
                    <description>This week: Revolution 2.0 protest in Tahrir Square, the Greeks and the Gaza flotilla, and a new constitution in Morocco + Hoba Hoba Spirit's Bled Schizo.</description>
                    <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2011 11:26:14 +0200</pubDate>
                    <enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4a/arabist.s3.amazonaws.com/podcasts/arabistpodcast6.m4a" length="22509486" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">083AB84C-1CBD-41CB-927A-2ABB3FBA4798</guid>
                    <itunes:author>Issandr El Amrani, Ashraf Khalil, Ursula Lindsey</itunes:author>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:duration>45:44</itunes:duration>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Lunch with the Arabist #3: Steve Cook and Jonathan Tepperman</title>
                    <description>We talk to the Council of Foreign Relations' resident Egypt specialist, Steve Cook, and Foreign Affairs managing editor Jonathan Tepperman over a few Stellas at the Greek Club.</description>
                    <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2011 15:05:07 +0200</pubDate>
                    <enclosure url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.m4a/arabist.s3.amazonaws.com/podcasts/lunchwiththearabist3.m4a" length="10030624" type="audio/x-m4a"/>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">970BD7AF-7283-4687-B3DD-A6B686244E10</guid>
                    <itunes:author>Issandr El Amrani</itunes:author>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:duration>16:55</itunes:duration>
                </item>
            </channel>
        </rss>
    </httpclient:body>
</httpclient:response>