<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<httpclient:response xmlns:httpclient="http://exist-db.org/xquery/httpclient" statusCode="200">
    <httpclient:headers>
        <httpclient:header name="Server" value="Apache/2.2.22 (Ubuntu)"/>
        <httpclient:header name="X-Libsyn-Host" value="web-engine4.libsyn.com"/>
        <httpclient:header name="Vary" value="Accept-Encoding"/>
        <httpclient:header name="Content-Type" value="application/rss+xml"/>
        <httpclient:header name="last-modified" value="Mon, 18 Aug 2014 08:00:54 GMT"/>
        <httpclient:header name="Content-Length" value="10827"/>
        <httpclient:header name="Accept-Ranges" value="bytes"/>
        <httpclient:header name="Date" value="Wed, 20 Aug 2014 09:33:54 GMT"/>
        <httpclient:header name="X-Varnish" value="3094054979 3075228640"/>
        <httpclient:header name="Age" value="177932"/>
        <httpclient:header name="Via" value="1.1 varnish"/>
        <httpclient:header name="Connection" value="close"/>
        <httpclient:header name="X-Cache" value="HIT"/>
    </httpclient:headers>
    <httpclient:body mimetype="application/rss+xml" type="xml">
        <rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:cc="http://web.resource.org/cc/" version="2.0">
            <channel>
                <atom:link href="http://abetterlife.libsyn.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
                <title>A Better Life w/ Rachel Rofe - Personal Growth And Inspiration To Create An Amazing Life</title>
                <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2014 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
                <lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2014 08:00:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
                <generator>Libsyn WebEngine 2.0</generator>
                <link>http://abetterlife.libsyn.com/podcasts</link>
                <language>en</language>
                <copyright>© Rachel Rofe Enterprises 2014 all rights reserved</copyright>
                <docs>http://abetterlife.libsyn.com/podcasts</docs>
                <managingEditor>rachelreports@gmail.com (rachelreports@gmail.com)</managingEditor>
                <description>A Better Life is a podcast created for you, the person who wants to be living their best possible life. Rachel Rofe interviews inspiring people who have risen from hard situations and created lives they're very proud of. Learn the practical action steps people take to make their lives better, what they're working on right now (nobody's perfect!), and get weekly inspiration and motivation to live your best life. Rachel also throws in a lot of lifestyle hacks to make life feel easy, efficient, and energizing.</description>
                <image>
                    <url>http://assets.libsyn.com/content/7479555.jpg</url>
                    <title>A Better Life w/ Rachel Rofe - Personal Growth And Inspiration To Create An Amazing Life</title>
                    <link>http://abetterlife.libsyn.com/podcasts</link>
                </image>
                <itunes:author>Rachel Rofé interviews amazing people on inspiration, motivation, self confidence, and personal growth every week!</itunes:author>
                <itunes:keywords>abetterlife,buildconfidence,confidencebuilding,creatingadreamlife,creativity,dreamlife,entrepreneur,inspiration,inspirationalspeakers,inspirationalstories,inspire,leadershipdevelopment,leadershipskills,lifestyledesign,lifestylehacks,motivation,personalgrowth,personalimprovement,personalitydevelopment,rachelrofe,selfconfidence,selfdevelopment,selfimprovement,selfimprovementtips,spirituality,spiritualpower,spiritualwellness,success</itunes:keywords>
                <itunes:category text="Health"/>
                <itunes:category text="Society &amp; Culture"/>
                <itunes:category text="Education"/>
                <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/7479555.jpg"/>
                <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                <itunes:owner>
                    <itunes:name>Rachel Rofe</itunes:name>
                    <itunes:email>rachelreports@gmail.com</itunes:email>
                </itunes:owner>
                <itunes:summary>A Better Life is a podcast created for you, the person who wants to be living their best possible life. Rachel Rofe interviews inspiring people who have risen from hard situations and created lives they're very proud of. Learn the practical action steps people take to make their lives better, what they're working on right now (nobody's perfect!), and get weekly inspiration and motivation to live your best life. Rachel also throwns in a lot of lifestyle hacks to make life feel easy, efficient, and energizing.</itunes:summary>
                <itunes:subtitle>Personal Growth And Inspiration To Create An Amazing Life</itunes:subtitle>
                <item>
                    <title>Why we sabotage our happiness - and how to fix it</title>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2014 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">52e7ad4c0147ede92d1b202f57a933df</guid>
                    <link>http://abetterlife.libsyn.com/why-we-sabotage-our-happiness-and-how-to-fix-it</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/3016781"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Have you ever felt on top of the world, extremely happy to achieve something... only to find something to complain about 5 minutes later?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Or have you ever had one area of your life go great, while another went spectacularly wrong?&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This isn't by accident.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We all have success "comfort zones", and unless you consciously know what's happening, it's very easy to unknowingly sabotage the good things that happen to you.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This episode helps you understand what's going on when you upper limit yourself and how you can move past it in order to reach your full potential.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="14575098" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abetterlife/Rachel_Rofe_On_Upper_Limiting.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>15:09</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Upper Limiting</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Chad Hadsell on the 4 things you need if you want to be happy</title>
                    <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2014 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">251d2a1e3c2df21856b802a3fb57e905</guid>
                    <link>http://abetterlife.libsyn.com/chad-hadsell-on-the-4-things-you-need-if-you-want-to-be-happy</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/3010970"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;In this interview, Chad talks about how he went from depressed, burnt out and sleep deprived into a relationship he loves, a healthy body, and a career he's passionate about. After a whole lot of learning and experimenting, Chad believes that turning your life around can be boiled down to 4 things. He goes over all of them in this episode.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="53119601" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abetterlife/Rachel_Rofe_Interviews_Chad_Hadsell.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>55:18</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>In this interview, Chad talks about how he went from depressed, burnt out and sleep deprived into a relationship he loves, a healthy body, and a career he's passionate about. After a whole lot of learning and experimenting, Chad believes that turning...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Becca Piastrelli on how dabbling with lots of things can bring you happiness.</title>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2014 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">b626e02fe377629011ab30eaeff7ce37</guid>
                    <link>http://abetterlife.libsyn.com/becca-piastrelli-on-how-dabbling-with-lots-of-things-can-bring-you-happiness</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/3004887"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;In this interview, we talk to Becca Piastrelli about how having lots of passions can bring you a great happiness. Becca talks about how it's OK to dabble - and how you don't need to have some major end goal in everything you do. If you've been feeling like you don't have much space for fun in your life, listen to this interview. It will show you why fun will make you even MORE productive.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="32148931" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abetterlife/RRBecca.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>33:27</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>In this interview, we talk to Becca Piastrelli about how having lots of passions can bring you a great happiness. Becca talks about how it's OK to dabble - and how you don't need to have some major end goal in everything you do. If you've been feeling...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Melissa Ingold on how to juggle a successful business, motherhood, and marriage.</title>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2014 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">b590181b4be59ab3fc5b0a94b5f11806</guid>
                    <link>http://abetterlife.libsyn.com/melissa-ingold-on-how-to-juggle-a-successful-business-motherhood-and-marriage</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/3004792"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;This interview with Melissa is extremely inspiring. Melissa has gone through a lot - teenage pregnancy, extreme poverty, single parenting, the death of one of her children... and she STILL created a life she can be proud of. She built a highly sought after service business from the ground up, creates 100 plus new products every year, runs six different monthly membership programs, is an affiliate marketer and has created a slew of fun projects with amazing joint venture partners. She talks about how to outsource effectively, how to focus on Faith, Freedom, and Joy, and how to choose a life you're proud of.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="46471955" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abetterlife/RRMelissa.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>48:23</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>This interview with Melissa is extremely inspiring. Melissa has gone through a lot - teenage pregnancy, extreme poverty, single parenting, the death of one of her children... and she STILL created a life she can be proud of. She built a highly sought...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>10 Steps To Getting Your Inspiration Back - Even When  You’re Burnt Out, Cranky, and Would Rather Crawl Back Into Bed.</title>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2014 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">9a6f6e9b3603142858913c802476c609</guid>
                    <link>http://abetterlife.libsyn.com/10-steps-to-getting-your-inspiration-back-even-when-youre-burnt-out-cranky-and-would-rather-crawl-back-into-bed</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/3004716"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;If you've ever felt de-motivated and uninspired to make progress on your goals, listen to this episode. We cover 10 different steps you can take to feel excited again. You'll learn how to get back to your "why" (or how to create one), the best types of things to surround yourself with, how you can get accountability, how to have conversations with people you admire, and more. This is a quick listen, but it packs a lot of useful content. Enjoy!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="19741708" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abetterlife/RR10Inspire.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>20:32</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>If you've ever felt de-motivated and uninspired to make progress on your goals, listen to this episode. We cover 10 different steps you can take to feel excited again. You'll learn how to get back to your "why" (or how to create one), the best types...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
            </channel>
        </rss>
    </httpclient:body>
</httpclient:response>