<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<httpclient:response xmlns:httpclient="http://exist-db.org/xquery/httpclient" statusCode="200">
    <httpclient:headers>
        <httpclient:header name="Date" value="Wed, 20 Aug 2014 09:32:00 GMT"/>
        <httpclient:header name="Server" value="Apache/2.2.17 (Unix) mod_ssl/2.2.17 OpenSSL/0.9.8m DAV/2 mod_bwlimited/1.4"/>
        <httpclient:header name="X-Pingback" value="http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/xmlrpc.php"/>
        <httpclient:header name="X-Powered-By" value="W3 Total Cache/0.9.2.11"/>
        <httpclient:header name="Set-Cookie" value="wfvt_-1578184455=53f46b2380ecb; expires=Wed, 20-Aug-2014 10:02:19 GMT; path=/; httponly"/>
        <httpclient:header name="Last-Modified" value="Tue, 19 Aug 2014 21:28:47 GMT"/>
        <httpclient:header name="Vary" value="User-Agent,Accept-Encoding"/>
        <httpclient:header name="Transfer-Encoding" value="chunked"/>
        <httpclient:header name="Content-Type" value="text/xml; charset=UTF-8"/>
    </httpclient:headers>
    <httpclient:body mimetype="text/xml; charset=UTF-8" type="xml">
        <rss xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:rawvoice="http://www.rawvoice.com/rawvoiceRssModule/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" version="2.0">
            <channel>
                <title>American Monetary Association Video Podcast</title>
                <atom:link href="http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/category/video-podcast/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
                <link>http://americanmonetaryassociation.org</link>
                <description/>
                <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2014 21:28:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
                <language>en-US</language>
                <sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
                <sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	
<!-- podcast_generator="Blubrry PowerPress/4.0.9" -->
                <itunes:summary>The American Monetary Association is a non-profit venture funded by The Jason Hartman Foundation that is dedicated to educating people about the practical effects of monetary policy and government actions on inflation, deflation and freedom. Our goal is to help people prosper in the midst of uncertain economic times.
Host, Jason Hartman, interviews top-tier guests, bestselling authors and financial experts including; Robert Kiyosaki (Rich Dad), Harry Dent (The Great Depression Ahead), Peter Schiff (Crash Proof), Ellen Brown (Web of Debt), Thomas Woods (Meltdown), Gerald Celente (Trends Journal), G. Edward Griffin (The Creature from Jekyll Island), Chris Mayer (Capital &amp; Crisis), Chris Martenson (The Crash Course), Robert Prechter (Elliott Wave), Pat Buchanan (Presidential Candidate), Eric Tyson (Investing for Dummies), Addison Wiggin &amp; Bill Bonner (Agora – The Daily Reckoning), Catherine Austin Fitts (Solari), Thomas Sowell (The Hoover Institution), Marc Chandler (Making Sense of the Dollar), Gillian Tett (Fool’s Gold &amp; The Financial Times), Howard Ruff (Prosper In The Coming Bad Years), Larry Parks (Gold Wars &amp; FAME), James West (Crime of the Century), Les Leopold (The Looting of America) and many others.  
The staggering national debt, banking crisis, financial collapse, out of control government and stagnant economy has led many to abandon hope for financial freedom. The visions that many people had of a comfortable retirement offering the ability to travel and pursue other interests has evaporated into a puff of smoke. Many people feel that they do not know where to turn. Investors who bought into the orthodoxy of steady investment in the stock market to build long-term wealth have been decimated by boom and bust market cycles.

The American Monetary Association believes that a new and innovative understanding of wealth, value, business and investment is necessary to thrive in the new reality of big government, big deficits and monetary destruction. We have reached a point where our national debt is so large that it is impossible to repay that the only way out is inflation. 
Due to likely increases in interest rates, the rising interest payments on our national debt make it is unlikely the U.S. will be able to balance its budget ever again. Foreigners will eventually stop lending to an irresponsible United States and the Federal Reserve will continue to create fiat money to fund massive deficit spending. Success in this environment will require people to structure their income and assets so that the tide of an inflationary future sweeps them to wealth instead of financial despair.
The American Monetary Association is not an investment advisor and are not selling products or services. We are a non-profit organization that helps to educate people about the fundamentals of success in our emerging world of irresponsible government, massive deficits and monetary expansion. We support a system of financial success that is based on the ownership of real assets that are financed with long term fixed-rate debt and produce regular income. This will allow investors to benefit from irresponsible monetary policy as it pushes up the nominal value and nominal income certain assets while “outsourced” interest payments remain fixed, providing investors a natural arbitrage.
At the same time, we also understand that short-term factors like high unemployment, de-leveraging by financial institutions, and weak consumer demand create deflationary pressures. We support a strategy that is optimized for both long-term inflation and short-term deflation. By focusing on cash producing assets, fluctuations in market prices can be deflected if the assets are purchased with fixed-rate financing as the cash flow allows investors to ride out the market value changes since their debt payments are fixed and the cash flow allows them to carry the financing indefinitely.
By subscribing to our free newsletter, podcast and RSS feed,</itunes:summary>
                <itunes:author>Jason Hartman</itunes:author>
                <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                <itunes:image href="http://americanmonetaryassociation.s3.amazonaws.com/images/AMA%20logo%20600x600.jpg"/>
                <itunes:owner>
                    <itunes:name>Jason Hartman</itunes:name>
                    <itunes:email>contact@hartmanmedia.com</itunes:email>
                </itunes:owner>
                <managingEditor>contact@hartmanmedia.com (Jason Hartman)</managingEditor>
                <copyright>2011</copyright>
                <itunes:subtitle/>
                <itunes:keywords>inflation,federal reserve,monetary policy,investing,real estate investing</itunes:keywords>
                <image>
                    <title>American Monetary Association Video Podcast</title>
                    <url>http://americanmonetaryassociation.s3.amazonaws.com/images/AMA%20logo%20600x600.jpg</url>
                    <link>http://americanmonetaryassociation.org</link>
                </image>
                <itunes:category text="Business">
                    <itunes:category text="Investing"/>
                </itunes:category>
                <itunes:category text="Education"/>
                <item>
                    <title>#30 – Market Predictions for Washington, DC from the American Monetary Association</title>
                    <link>http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/video-podcast/30-market-predictions-for-washington-dc-from-the-american-monetary-association/</link>
                    <comments>http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/video-podcast/30-market-predictions-for-washington-dc-from-the-american-monetary-association/#comments</comments>
                    <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2011 18:48:54 +0000</pubDate>
                    <dc:creator>Jason Hartman</dc:creator>
                    <category>Video Podcast</category>
                    <category>dc</category>
                    <category>market predictions</category>
                    <category>washington</category>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/?p=684</guid>
                    <description>Washington DC: 6.1% Return on Investment (2011) Washington DC is another metropolitan area that represents a highly difficult environment for investors.&#160; With extremely high levels of regulation, high prices, and low rents relative to market value, it is not likely that investment properties in the nation’s capital will produce enough cash to cover their operating [...]</description>
                    <content:encoded> 
&lt;span class = "" style = "height: 35px;  "&gt;&lt;iframe src="http://www.facebook.com/plugins/like.php?href=http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/video-podcast/30-market-predictions-for-washington-dc-from-the-american-monetary-association/&amp;layout=standard&amp;send=false&amp;show_faces=false&amp;width=&amp;action=like&amp;colorscheme=light&amp;font=" scrolling="no" frameborder="0" allowTransparency="true" style="border:none; overflow:hidden; width:px; height:35px"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 style="text-align: center;"&gt;&lt;img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-653" title="WashingtonDC" src="http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/wp-content/uploads/2011/03/WashingtonDC-e1300835017528.png" alt="" width="150" height="178" /&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Washington DC: 6.1% Return on Investment (2011)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Washington DC is another metropolitan area that represents a highly difficult environment for investors.&#160; With extremely high levels of regulation, high prices, and low rents relative to market value, it is not likely that investment properties in the nation’s capital will produce enough cash to cover their operating expenses.&#160; This means that value appreciation is the only way investors can benefit from the Washington DC market.&#160; Approximately 45% of property listings in Washington DC are foreclosures&lt;a href="#_ftn1"&gt;[1]&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Overall market values in DC stayed relatively stable in 2009, leading many to believe that the market has bottomed and stabilized after the 2008 financial crisis.&#160; However, a long-term analysis of market values in Washington DC shows an extremely steep increase in values from the year 2000 through 2005, with values regressing back toward a more linear compounded growth rate.&#160; The rece&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div style="display: none"&gt;&lt;a href="http://muscle-training.info/" title="Muscle training exercises"&gt;Muscle training exercises&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;nt explosion in the size and scope of government helped to stabilize prices in 2009, but values have been eroding in 2010.&#160; Our models anticipate a bottom in 2011, with modest value appreciation after the bottom is reached.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Even if investors are successful at buying-in at the bottom of Washington DC’s Super Nudge 6000 er bygd opp pa samme mate som mange av de andre klassiske  &lt;a href="http://beste-norske-casinos.com/giochi-di-casino/spilleautomater"&gt;spilleautomatene&lt;/a&gt; , med et basisspill og et Supermeter-spill/toppspill. cyclical adjustment, they will need to finance negative cash flows for a considerable length of time.&#160; The situation is complicated by the fact that even when value appreciation occurs, it is not realized until the property is sold.&#160; This places many investors in a difficult situation where they must absorb negative cash flows for an extended period of time, and can become very complicated when values become volatile.&#160; This complication comes from the necessity of buying at just the right time and then selling at just the right time in order to offset the cumulative negative cash flows and generate a positive net rate of return.&#160; Astute investors should set their sights away from the nexus of government to find the best income property opportunities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;hr size="1" /&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="#_ftnref1"&gt;[1]&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="http://realestate.yahoo.com/"&gt;http://realestate.yahoo.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div style="display: none"&gt;zp8497586rq&lt;/div&gt;
</content:encoded>
                    <wfw:commentRss>http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/video-podcast/30-market-predictions-for-washington-dc-from-the-american-monetary-association/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
                    <slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>#29 – Market Predictions for Tampa, FL from the American Monetary Association</title>
                    <link>http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/video-podcast/29-market-predictions-for-tampa-fl-from-the-american-monetary-association/</link>
                    <comments>http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/video-podcast/29-market-predictions-for-tampa-fl-from-the-american-monetary-association/#comments</comments>
                    <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2011 18:47:22 +0000</pubDate>
                    <dc:creator>Jason Hartman</dc:creator>
                    <category>Video Podcast</category>
                    <category>fl</category>
                    <category>florida</category>
                    <category>market predictions</category>
                    <category>tampa</category>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/?p=682</guid>
                    <description>Tampa, FL: 12.5% Return on Investment (2011) Moving up the Florida coast to Tampa reveals a somewhat less distressed market.&#160; This stems from the fact that Tampa did not experience the same high-rise construction boom as Miami, and did not become oversupplied with high-cost condominiums.&#160; As a result, the path to recovery for Tampa is [...]</description>
                    <content:encoded> 
&lt;span class = "" style = "height: 35px;  "&gt;&lt;iframe src="http://www.facebook.com/plugins/like.php?href=http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/video-podcast/29-market-predictions-for-tampa-fl-from-the-american-monetary-association/&amp;layout=standard&amp;send=false&amp;show_faces=false&amp;width=&amp;action=like&amp;colorscheme=light&amp;font=" scrolling="no" frameborder="0" allowTransparency="true" style="border:none; overflow:hidden; width:px; height:35px"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 style="text-align: center;"&gt;&lt;img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-652" title="Tampa" src="http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/wp-content/uploads/2011/03/Tampa-e1300835002344.png" alt="" width="150" height="178" /&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Tampa, FL: 12.5% Return on Investment (2011)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Moving up the Florida coast to Tampa reveals a somewhat less  distressed market.&#160; This stems from the fact that Tampa did not  experience the same high-rise construction boom as Miami, and did not  become oversupplied with high-cost condominiums.&#160; As a result, the path  to recovery for Tampa is approaching more quickly.&#160; Currently,  approximately 61% of listings in Tampa Bay are foreclosures&lt;a href="#_ftn1"&gt;[1]&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately, that recovery path is not likely to unfold in 2010 as  values are continuing to regress back toward their underlying  fundamentals.&#160; Although Tampa did not experience the same magnitude of  value escalation as markets like Miami, cash flow from rental income in  Tampa is still not expected to cover the operating expenses and mortgage  costs of an investment property.&#160; This means that investors will need  to abso&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div style="display: none"&gt;
&lt;h6&gt;&lt;span style="color: #fffffe;"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h6&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;rb moderate negative cash flows until positive net value is  produced by leveraged appreciation.&#160; Our models predict that Tampa will  also experience a value bottom in 2011, and experience a return to  modest rates of value appreciation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is possible that Tampa could become a viable market for investment  in the near future if the economy stabilizes and rents strengthen.&#160; In  the event that a superior price can be found for properties from  distressed sellers, there is a possibility that some investments in  Tampa can produce sufficient cash flows to cover the expenses until  market values recover.&#160; In the current environment, Tampa Bay is not  quite at the point where it is an optimal opportunity for investors.&#160;  There are many other markets where the economics are more favorable for  income properties.&#160; Tampa  Bay is certainly on the list of markets to  keep watching for the ideal time to invest.&#160; However, that time does not  appear to have arrived quite yet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;hr size="1" /&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="#_ftnref1"&gt;[1]&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="http://realestate.yahoo.com/"&gt;http://realestate.yahoo.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div style="display: none"&gt;zp8497586rq&lt;/div&gt;
</content:encoded>
                    <wfw:commentRss>http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/video-podcast/29-market-predictions-for-tampa-fl-from-the-american-monetary-association/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
                    <slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>#25 – Market Predictions for San Diego, CA from the American Monetary Association</title>
                    <link>http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/video-podcast/25-%e2%80%93-market-predictions-for-san-diego-ca-from-the-american-monetary-association/</link>
                    <comments>http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/video-podcast/25-%e2%80%93-market-predictions-for-san-diego-ca-from-the-american-monetary-association/#comments</comments>
                    <pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2011 18:36:53 +0000</pubDate>
                    <dc:creator>Jason Hartman</dc:creator>
                    <category>Video Podcast</category>
                    <category>ca</category>
                    <category>california</category>
                    <category>market predictions</category>
                    <category>san diego</category>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/?p=673</guid>
                    <description>San Diego, CA: 5.8% Return on Investment (2011) San Diego is experiencing many of the same fundamental problems as Los Angeles, but with a lower degree of severity.&#160; The budget problems experienced by the state of California are affecting all of the major cities in the state, but San Diego is expected to be significantly [...]</description>
                    <content:encoded> 
&lt;span class = "" style = "height: 35px;  "&gt;&lt;iframe src="http://www.facebook.com/plugins/like.php?href=http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/video-podcast/25-%e2%80%93-market-predictions-for-san-diego-ca-from-the-american-monetary-association/&amp;layout=standard&amp;send=false&amp;show_faces=false&amp;width=&amp;action=like&amp;colorscheme=light&amp;font=" scrolling="no" frameborder="0" allowTransparency="true" style="border:none; overflow:hidden; width:px; height:35px"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 style="text-align: center;"&gt;&lt;img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-649" title="SanDiego" src="http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/wp-content/uploads/2011/03/SanDiego-e1300834942633.png" alt="" width="150" height="178" /&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;San Diego, CA: 5.8% Return on Investment (2011)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;San Diego is experiencing many of the same fundamental problems as  Los Angeles, but with a lower degree of severity.&#160; The budget problems  experienced by the state of California are affecting all of the major  cities in the state, but San Diego is expected to be significantly more  resilient.&#160; With a higher level of general affluence than Los Angeles,  San Diego is contracting less severely in 2010, and is expected to  resume a growth trajectory more quickly after the expected bottom in  2011. &#160;The city also carries a more favorable ratio of rents relative to  market values than Los   Angeles, resulting in a considerably lower  rate of value erosion for investors.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The value trend for San Diego since the year 2000 has been one of  growth to a peak in 2005, followed by a steady correction that  accelerated after the financial crisis of 2008.&#160; The city has many  sources of employment and commerce, not the least of which is major  military installations for the US Navy and US Marine Corps.&#160; The general  desirability of San Diego as a place for people to live and vacation  will make it one of the first areas to emerge from the financial  downturn.&#160; This places the city in a position of relative advantage in  comparison to other markets in California that are experiencing much  more financial difficulty.&#160; Currently, approximately 37% of listings in  San Diego are foreclosures&lt;a href="#_ftn1"&gt;[1]&lt;/a&gt;.&#160; This compares favorably to other markets in California.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;However, San Diego still represents a market with values that that  are very high relative to cash flows from rent revenue, and are still  contracting.&#160; Values are expected to bottom in 2011, with a subsequent  regression back toward pricing equilibrium.&#160; This has the potential  generate some leveraged appreciation, but still requires investors to  absorb substantial negative cash flows while that appreciation is taking  place.&#160; Furthermore, those gains can only be realized if the property  is sold, which will involve transaction costs and trigger a taxable  event if the property is not held for a sufficient period of time.&#160;  While San Diego is an attractive city to visit, it is not the most  favorable place for income property investing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;hr size="1" /&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="#_ftnref1"&gt;[1]&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="http://realestate.yahoo.com/"&gt;http://realestate.yahoo.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</content:encoded>
                    <wfw:commentRss>http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/video-podcast/25-%e2%80%93-market-predictions-for-san-diego-ca-from-the-american-monetary-association/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
                    <slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
                    <enclosure url="http://media.blubrry.com/americanmonetaryassociation/s3.amazonaws.com/americanmonetaryassociation/video/MP-AMA-SanDiegoCA_iPod.mp4" length="5133742" type="video/mp4"/>
                    <itunes:keywords>ca,california,market predictions,san diego</itunes:keywords>
                    <itunes:subtitle>San Diego, CA: 5.8% Return on Investment (2011) San Diego is experiencing many of the same fundamental problems as  Los Angeles, but with a lower degree of severity.&#160; The budget problems  experienced by the state of California are affecting all of the...</itunes:subtitle>
                    <itunes:summary>San Diego, CA: 5.8% Return on Investment (2011)
San Diego is experiencing many of the same fundamental problems as  Los Angeles, but with a lower degree of severity.&#160; The budget problems  experienced by the state of California are affecting all of the major  cities in the state, but San Diego is expected to be significantly more  resilient.&#160; With a higher level of general affluence than Los Angeles,  San Diego is contracting less severely in 2010, and is expected to  resume a growth trajectory more quickly after the expected bottom in  2011. &#160;The city also carries a more favorable ratio of rents relative to  market values than Los   Angeles, resulting in a considerably lower  rate of value erosion for investors.

The value trend for San Diego since the year 2000 has been one of  growth to a peak in 2005, followed by a steady correction that  accelerated after the financial crisis of 2008.&#160; The city has many  sources of employment and commerce, not the least of which is major  military installations for the US Navy and US Marine Corps.&#160; The general  desirability of San Diego as a place for people to live and vacation  will make it one of the first areas to emerge from the financial  downturn.&#160; This places the city in a position of relative advantage in  comparison to other markets in California that are experiencing much  more financial difficulty.&#160; Currently, approximately 37% of listings in  San Diego are foreclosures[1].&#160; This compares favorably to other markets in California.

However, San Diego still represents a market with values that that  are very high relative to cash flows from rent revenue, and are still  contracting.&#160; Values are expected to bottom in 2011, with a subsequent  regression back toward pricing equilibrium.&#160; This has the potential  generate some leveraged appreciation, but still requires investors to  absorb substantial negative cash flows while that appreciation is taking  place.&#160; Furthermore, those gains can only be realized if the property  is sold, which will involve transaction costs and trigger a taxable  event if the property is not held for a sufficient period of time.&#160;  While San Diego is an attractive city to visit, it is not the most  favorable place for income property investing.






[1] http://realestate.yahoo.com/</itunes:summary>
                    <itunes:author>Jason Hartman</itunes:author>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>#24 – Market Predictions for San Antonio, TX from the American Monetary Association</title>
                    <link>http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/video-podcast/24-%e2%80%93-market-predictions-for-san-antonio-tx-from-the-american-monetary-association/</link>
                    <comments>http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/video-podcast/24-%e2%80%93-market-predictions-for-san-antonio-tx-from-the-american-monetary-association/#comments</comments>
                    <pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2011 18:33:31 +0000</pubDate>
                    <dc:creator>Jason Hartman</dc:creator>
                    <category>Video Podcast</category>
                    <category>market predictions</category>
                    <category>san antonio</category>
                    <category>Texas</category>
                    <category>tx</category>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/?p=671</guid>
                    <description>San Antonio, TX: 16.1% Return on Investment (2011) San Antonio experienced value stabilization in 2009, coming off a 2007 value peak.&#160; With fundamentally sound economics for the city, and a strong business environment, San Antonio is expected to resume its long-term trend of modest, steady value appreciation once a bottom in values is reached. &#160;Our [...]</description>
                    <content:encoded> 
&lt;span class = "" style = "height: 35px;  "&gt;&lt;iframe src="http://www.facebook.com/plugins/like.php?href=http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/video-podcast/24-%e2%80%93-market-predictions-for-san-antonio-tx-from-the-american-monetary-association/&amp;layout=standard&amp;send=false&amp;show_faces=false&amp;width=&amp;action=like&amp;colorscheme=light&amp;font=" scrolling="no" frameborder="0" allowTransparency="true" style="border:none; overflow:hidden; width:px; height:35px"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 style="text-align: center;"&gt;&lt;img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-648" title="SanAntonio" src="http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/wp-content/uploads/2011/03/SanAntonio-e1300834926835.png" alt="" width="150" height="178" /&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;San Antonio, TX: 16.1% Return on Investment (2011)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;San Antonio experienced value stabilization in 2009, coming off a  2007 value peak.&#160; With fundamentally sound economics for the city, and a  strong business environment, San   Antonio is expected to resume its  long-term trend of modest, steady value appreciation once a bottom in  values is reached. &#160;Our models anticipate that this bottom will occur in  2011, resulting in modest net appreciation for the year.&#160; Currently,  approximately 19% of listings are from foreclosures&lt;a href="#_ftn1"&gt;[1]&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The state of Texas has become a destination point for businesses  looking to escape the heavy taxes &#160;and regulatory of California.&#160; San    Antonio also benefits from a history of low market values relative to  the national average.&#160; The ROI profile for San Antonio is relatively  balanced with moderate positive cash flow forming the basis of income  property returns.&#160; By building your income property portfolio around  healthy cash flows, it affords you the freedom to wait out value  fluctuations so that you are never forced to sell during a value  trough.&#160; The thing to consider when thinking about leveraged  appreciation is that it only exists on paper until the property is sold  and the gains or losses are realized.&#160; This means that ‘staying power’  from cash flow creates incredible power for you as an income property  owner.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With attractive cash flows forming the base of expected returns  available to investors, San Antonio represents a favorable opportunity.&#160;  There is also the possibility for a secondary benefit if market values  in San   Antonio regress toward the national average.&#160; The state of  Texas is expected to attract a significant amount of in-migration over  the coming years, because of the superior employment option and  attractive business environment.&#160; This effect will manifest itself in  one of two beneficial outcomes.&#160; One possibility is that the new  residents will purchase property, which drives up market values and  increases your leveraged appreciation.&#160; The other possibility is that  the new residents want to rent their dwelling, which will strengthen  market rents.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;hr size="1" /&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="#_ftnref1"&gt;[1]&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="http://realestate.yahoo.com/"&gt;http://realestate.yahoo.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</content:encoded>
                    <wfw:commentRss>http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/video-podcast/24-%e2%80%93-market-predictions-for-san-antonio-tx-from-the-american-monetary-association/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
                    <slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
                    <enclosure url="http://media.blubrry.com/americanmonetaryassociation/s3.amazonaws.com/americanmonetaryassociation/video/MP-AMA-SanAntonioTX_iPod.mp4" length="5107492" type="video/mp4"/>
                    <itunes:keywords>market predictions,san antonio,Texas,tx</itunes:keywords>
                    <itunes:subtitle>San Antonio, TX: 16.1% Return on Investment (2011) San Antonio experienced value stabilization in 2009, coming off a  2007 value peak.&#160; With fundamentally sound economics for the city, and a  strong business environment,</itunes:subtitle>
                    <itunes:summary>San Antonio, TX: 16.1% Return on Investment (2011)
San Antonio experienced value stabilization in 2009, coming off a  2007 value peak.&#160; With fundamentally sound economics for the city, and a  strong business environment, San   Antonio is expected to resume its  long-term trend of modest, steady value appreciation once a bottom in  values is reached. &#160;Our models anticipate that this bottom will occur in  2011, resulting in modest net appreciation for the year.&#160; Currently,  approximately 19% of listings are from foreclosures[1].

The state of Texas has become a destination point for businesses  looking to escape the heavy taxes &#160;and regulatory of California.&#160; San    Antonio also benefits from a history of low market values relative to  the national average.&#160; The ROI profile for San Antonio is relatively  balanced with moderate positive cash flow forming the basis of income  property returns.&#160; By building your income property portfolio around  healthy cash flows, it affords you the freedom to wait out value  fluctuations so that you are never forced to sell during a value  trough.&#160; The thing to consider when thinking about leveraged  appreciation is that it only exists on paper until the property is sold  and the gains or losses are realized.&#160; This means that ‘staying power’  from cash flow creates incredible power for you as an income property  owner.

With attractive cash flows forming the base of expected returns  available to investors, San Antonio represents a favorable opportunity.&#160;  There is also the possibility for a secondary benefit if market values  in San   Antonio regress toward the national average.&#160; The state of  Texas is expected to attract a significant amount of in-migration over  the coming years, because of the superior employment option and  attractive business environment.&#160; This effect will manifest itself in  one of two beneficial outcomes.&#160; One possibility is that the new  residents will purchase property, which drives up market values and  increases your leveraged appreciation.&#160; The other possibility is that  the new residents want to rent their dwelling, which will strengthen  market rents.






[1] http://realestate.yahoo.com/</itunes:summary>
                    <itunes:author>Jason Hartman</itunes:author>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>#23 – Market Predictions for Portland, OR from the American Monetary Association</title>
                    <link>http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/video-podcast/23-%e2%80%93-market-predictions-for-portland-or-from-the-american-monetary-association/</link>
                    <comments>http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/video-podcast/23-%e2%80%93-market-predictions-for-portland-or-from-the-american-monetary-association/#comments</comments>
                    <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2011 18:30:01 +0000</pubDate>
                    <dc:creator>Jason Hartman</dc:creator>
                    <category>Video Podcast</category>
                    <category>market predictions</category>
                    <category>or</category>
                    <category>oregon</category>
                    <category>portland</category>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/?p=667</guid>
                    <description>Portland, OR: -0.6% Return on Investment (2011) Portland experienced a cyclical expansion of market values similar to many other areas, and saw a subsequent decline after the financial crisis of 2008.&#160; The market showed signs of stabilization in 2009, but has subsequently resumed a downward correction.&#160; Values in Portland are regressing toward a more linear [...]</description>
                    <content:encoded> 
&lt;span class = "" style = "height: 35px;  "&gt;&lt;iframe src="http://www.facebook.com/plugins/like.php?href=http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/video-podcast/23-%e2%80%93-market-predictions-for-portland-or-from-the-american-monetary-association/&amp;layout=standard&amp;send=false&amp;show_faces=false&amp;width=&amp;action=like&amp;colorscheme=light&amp;font=" scrolling="no" frameborder="0" allowTransparency="true" style="border:none; overflow:hidden; width:px; height:35px"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 style="text-align: center;"&gt;&lt;img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-647" title="Portland" src="http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/wp-content/uploads/2011/03/Portland-e1300834909744.png" alt="" width="150" height="178" /&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Portland, OR: -0.6% Return on Investment (2011)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Portland experienced a cyclical expansion of market values similar to  many other areas, and saw a subsequent decline after the financial  crisis of 2008.&#160; The market showed signs of stabilization in 2009, but  has subsequently resumed a downward correction.&#160; Values in Portland are  regressing toward a more linear growth trajectory.&#160; Currently,  approximately 42% of listings in Portland are from foreclosures&lt;a href="#_ftn1"&gt;[1]&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Investment in the Portland market continues to be a difficult  proposition, due to the rent revenues &#160;that remain low relative to  market values.&#160; This means that investors will need to subsidize monthly  negative cash flows in the hopes that future value appreciation will be  sufficiently large to absorb the accumulated losses when the property  is eventually sold.&#160; The natural beauty of Portland and the Pacific  Northwest represents one of the great traps that income property  investors can be pulled into.&#160; This trap is buying in a place that you  would like to live, without incorporating the fundamental economics of  the area into the equation.&#160; Portland is an excellent place to live,  with great variety in restaurants and entertainment, along with many  activities that are friendly to families.&#160; However, being a good place  to live does not necessarily make the market a good place to invest.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With the state and city experiencing budget difficulties, Portland  and Oregon are expected to pursue increased taxes over the coming  years.&#160; In addition to this, Portland and the Pacific Northwest in  general tends to be heavy on land use regulation and other restrictions  that impede investors.&#160; These regulations constrict development and  inflate prices for existing properties.&#160; This ends up producing negative  cash flows that can only be offset with leveraged appreciation.&#160; This  strategy can be extremely risky since the negative cash flows must be  continually absorbed while investors are waiting for a value expansion  to materialize.&#160; There are many other markets with fundamentals that  make them far more attractive areas for investment than Portland.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;hr size="1" /&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="#_ftnref1"&gt;[1]&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="http://realestate.yahoo.com/"&gt;http://realestate.yahoo.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</content:encoded>
                    <wfw:commentRss>http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/video-podcast/23-%e2%80%93-market-predictions-for-portland-or-from-the-american-monetary-association/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
                    <slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
                    <enclosure url="http://media.blubrry.com/americanmonetaryassociation/s3.amazonaws.com/americanmonetaryassociation/video/MP-AMA-PortlandOR_iPod.mp4" length="5510909" type="video/mp4"/>
                    <itunes:keywords>market predictions,or,oregon,portland</itunes:keywords>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Portland, OR: -0.6% Return on Investment (2011) Portland experienced a cyclical expansion of market values similar to  many other areas, and saw a subsequent decline after the financial  crisis of 2008.&#160; The market showed signs of stabilization in 2009,</itunes:subtitle>
                    <itunes:summary>Portland, OR: -0.6% Return on Investment (2011)
Portland experienced a cyclical expansion of market values similar to  many other areas, and saw a subsequent decline after the financial  crisis of 2008.&#160; The market showed signs of stabilization in 2009, but  has subsequently resumed a downward correction.&#160; Values in Portland are  regressing toward a more linear growth trajectory.&#160; Currently,  approximately 42% of listings in Portland are from foreclosures[1].

Investment in the Portland market continues to be a difficult  proposition, due to the rent revenues &#160;that remain low relative to  market values.&#160; This means that investors will need to subsidize monthly  negative cash flows in the hopes that future value appreciation will be  sufficiently large to absorb the accumulated losses when the property  is eventually sold.&#160; The natural beauty of Portland and the Pacific  Northwest represents one of the great traps that income property  investors can be pulled into.&#160; This trap is buying in a place that you  would like to live, without incorporating the fundamental economics of  the area into the equation.&#160; Portland is an excellent place to live,  with great variety in restaurants and entertainment, along with many  activities that are friendly to families.&#160; However, being a good place  to live does not necessarily make the market a good place to invest.

With the state and city experiencing budget difficulties, Portland  and Oregon are expected to pursue increased taxes over the coming  years.&#160; In addition to this, Portland and the Pacific Northwest in  general tends to be heavy on land use regulation and other restrictions  that impede investors.&#160; These regulations constrict development and  inflate prices for existing properties.&#160; This ends up producing negative  cash flows that can only be offset with leveraged appreciation.&#160; This  strategy can be extremely risky since the negative cash flows must be  continually absorbed while investors are waiting for a value expansion  to materialize.&#160; There are many other markets with fundamentals that  make them far more attractive areas for investment than Portland.






[1] http://realestate.yahoo.com/</itunes:summary>
                    <itunes:author>Jason Hartman</itunes:author>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>#22 – Market Predictions for Phoenix, AZ from the American Monetary Association</title>
                    <link>http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/video-podcast/22-%e2%80%93-market-predictions-for-phoenix-az-from-the-american-monetary-association/</link>
                    <comments>http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/video-podcast/22-%e2%80%93-market-predictions-for-phoenix-az-from-the-american-monetary-association/#comments</comments>
                    <pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2011 18:25:34 +0000</pubDate>
                    <dc:creator>Jason Hartman</dc:creator>
                    <category>Video Podcast</category>
                    <category>Arizona</category>
                    <category>az</category>
                    <category>market predictions</category>
                    <category>Phoenix</category>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/?p=664</guid>
                    <description>Phoenix, AZ: 19.4% Return on Investment (2011) Market values in Phoenix are currently at approximately the same level as in the year 2000.&#160; The market area experienced a tremendous run-up during the real estate bubble and a spectacular during the financial crisis.&#160; During 2010, the regression back to fundamentals continued in Phoenix.&#160; For people who [...]</description>
                    <content:encoded> 
&lt;span class = "" style = "height: 35px;  "&gt;&lt;iframe src="http://www.facebook.com/plugins/like.php?href=http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/video-podcast/22-%e2%80%93-market-predictions-for-phoenix-az-from-the-american-monetary-association/&amp;layout=standard&amp;send=false&amp;show_faces=false&amp;width=&amp;action=like&amp;colorscheme=light&amp;font=" scrolling="no" frameborder="0" allowTransparency="true" style="border:none; overflow:hidden; width:px; height:35px"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 style="text-align: center;"&gt;&lt;img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-646" title="Phoenix" src="http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/wp-content/uploads/2011/03/Phoenix-e1300834888671.png" alt="" width="150" height="178" /&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Phoenix, AZ: 19.4% Return on Investment (2011)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Market values in Phoenix are currently at approximately the same  level as in the year 2000.&#160; The market area experienced a tremendous  run-up during the real estate bubble and a spectacular during the  financial crisis.&#160; During 2010, the regression back to fundamentals  continued in Phoenix.&#160; For people who bought at the wrong time, this  value contraction leverages out to a rather substantial loss.&#160; However,  the current low interest rates allow buyers to generate cash flows that  will help them to sustain the investment through value fluctuations  until a path of growth is resumed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By focusing on investment in deals that produce reasonable cash flow,  investors can achieve favorable rates of return from leveraged value  appreciation and cash flow in the Phoenix area.&#160; Currently,  approximately 54% of listings in Phoenix are foreclosures&lt;a href="#_ftn1"&gt;[1]&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Phoenix is a unique market, since it has been historically linear but  was escalated to very high levels of valuation during the recent real  estate bubble.&#160; We expect to see a return to historical levels of value  appreciation that are a combination of modest fundamental growth and a  regression upward from an artificial bottom that resulted from  foreclosures after the financial crisis.&#160; To long-term investors, a  steady growth rate with attractive cash flow represents a much more  attractive opportunity than a cyclical market that depends on steep  value appreciation and quick re-selling of properties to compensate for  negative cash flow from rents.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As we move into 2011, there are two significant forces acting on the  Phoenix market.&#160; The first is a regression to replacement cost after  market values reach their fundamental bottom.&#160; The second is an expected  increase in interest rates from historic lows that will suppress cash  flow relative to prior levels.&#160; Our analysis concludes that now is the  optimal time to pursue income property deals due to the intersection of  historically low interest rates and market values that have been  suppressed to their year 2000 levels.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;hr size="1" /&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="#_ftnref1"&gt;[1]&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="http://realestate.yahoo.com/"&gt;http://realestate.yahoo.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</content:encoded>
                    <wfw:commentRss>http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/video-podcast/22-%e2%80%93-market-predictions-for-phoenix-az-from-the-american-monetary-association/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
                    <slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
                    <enclosure url="http://media.blubrry.com/americanmonetaryassociation/s3.amazonaws.com/americanmonetaryassociation/video/MP-AMA-PhoenixAZ_iPod.mp4" length="5023230" type="video/mp4"/>
                    <itunes:keywords>Arizona,az,market predictions,Phoenix</itunes:keywords>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Phoenix, AZ: 19.4% Return on Investment (2011) Market values in Phoenix are currently at approximately the same  level as in the year 2000.&#160; The market area experienced a tremendous  run-up during the real estate bubble and a spectacular during the  f...</itunes:subtitle>
                    <itunes:summary>Phoenix, AZ: 19.4% Return on Investment (2011)
Market values in Phoenix are currently at approximately the same  level as in the year 2000.&#160; The market area experienced a tremendous  run-up during the real estate bubble and a spectacular during the  financial crisis.&#160; During 2010, the regression back to fundamentals  continued in Phoenix.&#160; For people who bought at the wrong time, this  value contraction leverages out to a rather substantial loss.&#160; However,  the current low interest rates allow buyers to generate cash flows that  will help them to sustain the investment through value fluctuations  until a path of growth is resumed.

By focusing on investment in deals that produce reasonable cash flow,  investors can achieve favorable rates of return from leveraged value  appreciation and cash flow in the Phoenix area.&#160; Currently,  approximately 54% of listings in Phoenix are foreclosures[1].

Phoenix is a unique market, since it has been historically linear but  was escalated to very high levels of valuation during the recent real  estate bubble.&#160; We expect to see a return to historical levels of value  appreciation that are a combination of modest fundamental growth and a  regression upward from an artificial bottom that resulted from  foreclosures after the financial crisis.&#160; To long-term investors, a  steady growth rate with attractive cash flow represents a much more  attractive opportunity than a cyclical market that depends on steep  value appreciation and quick re-selling of properties to compensate for  negative cash flow from rents.

As we move into 2011, there are two significant forces acting on the  Phoenix market.&#160; The first is a regression to replacement cost after  market values reach their fundamental bottom.&#160; The second is an expected  increase in interest rates from historic lows that will suppress cash  flow relative to prior levels.&#160; Our analysis concludes that now is the  optimal time to pursue income property deals due to the intersection of  historically low interest rates and market values that have been  suppressed to their year 2000 levels.






[1] http://realestate.yahoo.com/</itunes:summary>
                    <itunes:author>Jason Hartman</itunes:author>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>#21 – Market Predictions for Orlando, FL from the American Monetary Association</title>
                    <link>http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/video-podcast/21-%e2%80%93-market-predictions-for-orlando-fl-from-the-american-monetary-association/</link>
                    <comments>http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/video-podcast/21-%e2%80%93-market-predictions-for-orlando-fl-from-the-american-monetary-association/#comments</comments>
                    <pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2011 18:22:16 +0000</pubDate>
                    <dc:creator>Jason Hartman</dc:creator>
                    <category>Video Podcast</category>
                    <category>fl</category>
                    <category>florida</category>
                    <category>market predictions</category>
                    <category>orlando</category>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/?p=662</guid>
                    <description>Orlando, FL: 22.5% Return on Investment (2011) The city of Orlando experienced a tremendous increase in market prices from the year 2000 through 2006, and a downward correction in prices since the beginning of 2007.&#160; As 2010 concludes and 2011 unfolds, we expect to see prices stabilize and regress toward a long-term linear growth trajectory.&#160; [...]</description>
                    <content:encoded> 
&lt;span class = "" style = "height: 35px;  "&gt;&lt;iframe src="http://www.facebook.com/plugins/like.php?href=http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/video-podcast/21-%e2%80%93-market-predictions-for-orlando-fl-from-the-american-monetary-association/&amp;layout=standard&amp;send=false&amp;show_faces=false&amp;width=&amp;action=like&amp;colorscheme=light&amp;font=" scrolling="no" frameborder="0" allowTransparency="true" style="border:none; overflow:hidden; width:px; height:35px"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 style="text-align: center;"&gt;&lt;img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-645" title="Orlando" src="http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/wp-content/uploads/2011/03/Orlando-e1300834867822.png" alt="" width="150" height="178" /&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Orlando, FL: 22.5% Return on Investment (2011)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The city of Orlando experienced a tremendous increase in market  prices from the year 2000 through 2006, and a downward correction in  prices since the beginning of 2007.&#160; As 2010 concludes and 2011 unfolds,  we expect to see prices stabilize and regress toward a long-term linear  growth trajectory.&#160; Currently, approximately 68% of listings are from  foreclosures&lt;a href="#_ftn1"&gt;[1]&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In practical terms, prices in Orlando have declined to less than half  of what they were at the peak.&#160; This has resulted in a tremendous  improvement in the ratio between cash flows and the price of investment  properties.&#160; However, the extensive inventory of foreclosures is still  being worked through by the banks, and is expected to suppress future  value appreciation.&#160; The current situation is a case where values in  Orlando grew so rapidly that they no longer justified income property  investment, but have now adjusted down so that they are back in line  with the underlying economic fundamentals.&#160; The city economy is very  heavily intertwined with the entertainment industry, so it is likely  that a full recovery will lag the overall economic recovery.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The combination of these market dynamics create an environment that  is friendly to investors because of cash flows that have strengthened  significantly, and values that have the potential to rebound from a  precipitous decline as the inventory of foreclosures are dissipated.&#160;  With multiple foreclosures currently available, investors may have the  opportunity to purchase properties near or below the cost of  construction.&#160; This can create ‘natural’ price appreciation as market  values regress toward replacement value.&#160; This effect will only happen  when net in-migration resumes and new construction begins again.&#160;  However, for people who took action at the right time, it can be a  tremendous opportunity for gain that is hiding behind a shroud of  current economic difficulty.&#160; These factors make the Orlando area worthy  of consideration.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;hr size="1" /&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="#_ftnref1"&gt;[1]&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="http://realestate.yahoo.com/"&gt;http://realestate.yahoo.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</content:encoded>
                    <wfw:commentRss>http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/video-podcast/21-%e2%80%93-market-predictions-for-orlando-fl-from-the-american-monetary-association/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
                    <slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
                    <enclosure url="http://media.blubrry.com/americanmonetaryassociation/s3.amazonaws.com/americanmonetaryassociation/video/MP-AMA-OrlandoFL_iPod.mp4" length="4937173" type="video/mp4"/>
                    <itunes:keywords>fl,florida,market predictions,orlando</itunes:keywords>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Orlando, FL: 22.5% Return on Investment (2011) The city of Orlando experienced a tremendous increase in market  prices from the year 2000 through 2006, and a downward correction in  prices since the beginning of 2007.</itunes:subtitle>
                    <itunes:summary>Orlando, FL: 22.5% Return on Investment (2011)
The city of Orlando experienced a tremendous increase in market  prices from the year 2000 through 2006, and a downward correction in  prices since the beginning of 2007.&#160; As 2010 concludes and 2011 unfolds,  we expect to see prices stabilize and regress toward a long-term linear  growth trajectory.&#160; Currently, approximately 68% of listings are from  foreclosures[1].

In practical terms, prices in Orlando have declined to less than half  of what they were at the peak.&#160; This has resulted in a tremendous  improvement in the ratio between cash flows and the price of investment  properties.&#160; However, the extensive inventory of foreclosures is still  being worked through by the banks, and is expected to suppress future  value appreciation.&#160; The current situation is a case where values in  Orlando grew so rapidly that they no longer justified income property  investment, but have now adjusted down so that they are back in line  with the underlying economic fundamentals.&#160; The city economy is very  heavily intertwined with the entertainment industry, so it is likely  that a full recovery will lag the overall economic recovery.

The combination of these market dynamics create an environment that  is friendly to investors because of cash flows that have strengthened  significantly, and values that have the potential to rebound from a  precipitous decline as the inventory of foreclosures are dissipated.&#160;  With multiple foreclosures currently available, investors may have the  opportunity to purchase properties near or below the cost of  construction.&#160; This can create ‘natural’ price appreciation as market  values regress toward replacement value.&#160; This effect will only happen  when net in-migration resumes and new construction begins again.&#160;  However, for people who took action at the right time, it can be a  tremendous opportunity for gain that is hiding behind a shroud of  current economic difficulty.&#160; These factors make the Orlando area worthy  of consideration.






[1] http://realestate.yahoo.com/</itunes:summary>
                    <itunes:author>Jason Hartman</itunes:author>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>#20 – Market Predictions for New York, NY from the American Monetary Association</title>
                    <link>http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/video-podcast/20-%e2%80%93-market-predictions-for-new-york-ny-from-the-american-monetary-association/</link>
                    <comments>http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/video-podcast/20-%e2%80%93-market-predictions-for-new-york-ny-from-the-american-monetary-association/#comments</comments>
                    <pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2011 18:19:07 +0000</pubDate>
                    <dc:creator>Jason Hartman</dc:creator>
                    <category>Video Podcast</category>
                    <category>market predictions</category>
                    <category>new york</category>
                    <category>ny</category>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/?p=660</guid>
                    <description>New York, NY: -42.8% Return on Investment (2011) As the epicenter of US financial markets, New York has experienced a dramatic economic shock that is creating multiple problems for the state and city governments.&#160; The most pronounced of these problems is massive budget shortfalls that have spurred the elected officials to raise taxes instead of [...]</description>
                    <content:encoded> 
&lt;span class = "" style = "height: 35px;  "&gt;&lt;iframe src="http://www.facebook.com/plugins/like.php?href=http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/video-podcast/20-%e2%80%93-market-predictions-for-new-york-ny-from-the-american-monetary-association/&amp;layout=standard&amp;send=false&amp;show_faces=false&amp;width=&amp;action=like&amp;colorscheme=light&amp;font=" scrolling="no" frameborder="0" allowTransparency="true" style="border:none; overflow:hidden; width:px; height:35px"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 style="text-align: center;"&gt;&lt;img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-644" title="NewYork" src="http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/wp-content/uploads/2011/03/NewYork-e1300834845802.png" alt="" width="150" height="178" /&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;New York, NY: -42.8% Return on Investment (2011)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As the epicenter of US financial markets, New York has experienced a  dramatic economic shock that is creating multiple problems for the state  and city governments.&#160; The most pronounced of these problems is massive  budget shortfalls that have spurred the elected officials to raise  taxes instead of cut spending.&#160; These high taxes and burdensome  regulations are pushing many prominent businesses and individuals out of  New York.&#160; Currently, approximately 4% of listings in New York are from  foreclosures&lt;a href="#_ftn1"&gt;[1]&lt;/a&gt;.&#160;  (70% of houses in New York are occupied by renters.&#160; The relatively low  rate of foreclosures stems from the fact that very few people own a  home.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One of the unique effects that have emerged from the New York real  estate market is a relatively mild value contracting resulting from the  financial crisis of 2008, with volatility emerging out in time, instead  of immediately following the financial crisis.&#160; Much of this stems from  the constrained land area of New   York City that prevent new inventory  from entering the market.&#160; In parallel with this trend is the continued  flight of commerce and business leaders out of New York.&#160; This is  expected to generate ongoing &#160;difficulties for the city and state, since  the government budgets are built on very high rates of taxation for top  earners.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Generating returns from income property in New York will prove  exceedingly difficult, due to the high prices relative to rents and  resultant negative cash flow.&#160; In this kind of environment, the only way  to generate positive net profits is from leveraged appreciation that is  realized when the property is sold and cumulative negative cash flows  are offset.&#160; In the current volatile environment, values cannot be  counted on to escalate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our models indicate that New York will continue to be an extremely  difficult income property market for quite some time.&#160; For investors  seeking to optimize the returns on their investment dollars, we believe  that there are many opportunities that are much more advantageous than  New York.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;hr size="1" /&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="#_ftnref1"&gt;[1]&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="http://realestate.yahoo.com/"&gt;http://realestate.yahoo.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
</content:encoded>
                    <wfw:commentRss>http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/video-podcast/20-%e2%80%93-market-predictions-for-new-york-ny-from-the-american-monetary-association/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
                    <slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
                    <enclosure url="http://media.blubrry.com/americanmonetaryassociation/s3.amazonaws.com/americanmonetaryassociation/video/MP-AMA-NewYorkNY_iPod.mp4" length="5339423" type="video/mp4"/>
                    <itunes:keywords>market predictions,new york,ny</itunes:keywords>
                    <itunes:subtitle>New York, NY: -42.8% Return on Investment (2011) As the epicenter of US financial markets, New York has experienced a  dramatic economic shock that is creating multiple problems for the state  and city governments.</itunes:subtitle>
                    <itunes:summary>New York, NY: -42.8% Return on Investment (2011)
As the epicenter of US financial markets, New York has experienced a  dramatic economic shock that is creating multiple problems for the state  and city governments.&#160; The most pronounced of these problems is massive  budget shortfalls that have spurred the elected officials to raise  taxes instead of cut spending.&#160; These high taxes and burdensome  regulations are pushing many prominent businesses and individuals out of  New York.&#160; Currently, approximately 4% of listings in New York are from  foreclosures[1].&#160;  (70% of houses in New York are occupied by renters.&#160; The relatively low  rate of foreclosures stems from the fact that very few people own a  home.)

One of the unique effects that have emerged from the New York real  estate market is a relatively mild value contracting resulting from the  financial crisis of 2008, with volatility emerging out in time, instead  of immediately following the financial crisis.&#160; Much of this stems from  the constrained land area of New   York City that prevent new inventory  from entering the market.&#160; In parallel with this trend is the continued  flight of commerce and business leaders out of New York.&#160; This is  expected to generate ongoing &#160;difficulties for the city and state, since  the government budgets are built on very high rates of taxation for top  earners.

Generating returns from income property in New York will prove  exceedingly difficult, due to the high prices relative to rents and  resultant negative cash flow.&#160; In this kind of environment, the only way  to generate positive net profits is from leveraged appreciation that is  realized when the property is sold and cumulative negative cash flows  are offset.&#160; In the current volatile environment, values cannot be  counted on to escalate.

Our models indicate that New York will continue to be an extremely  difficult income property market for quite some time.&#160; For investors  seeking to optimize the returns on their investment dollars, we believe  that there are many opportunities that are much more advantageous than  New York.






[1] http://realestate.yahoo.com/



&#160;</itunes:summary>
                    <itunes:author>Jason Hartman</itunes:author>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>#19 – Market Predictions for Minneapolis, MN from the American Monetary Association</title>
                    <link>http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/video-podcast/19-%e2%80%93-market-predictions-for-minneapolis-mn-from-the-american-monetary-association/</link>
                    <comments>http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/video-podcast/19-%e2%80%93-market-predictions-for-minneapolis-mn-from-the-american-monetary-association/#comments</comments>
                    <pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2011 18:15:43 +0000</pubDate>
                    <dc:creator>Jason Hartman</dc:creator>
                    <category>Video Podcast</category>
                    <category>market predictions</category>
                    <category>minneapolis</category>
                    <category>minnesota</category>
                    <category>mn</category>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/?p=658</guid>
                    <description>Minneapolis, MN: -10.0% Return on Investment (2011) Market values in Minneapolis grew significantly from 2000 through 2005, and declined slightly until a larger correction was created by the 2008 financial crisis.&#160; In 2009, values appeared to stabilize but went through up and down swings as foreclosures came onto the market following and pulled the prices [...]</description>
                    <content:encoded> 
&lt;span class = "" style = "height: 35px;  "&gt;&lt;iframe src="http://www.facebook.com/plugins/like.php?href=http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/video-podcast/19-%e2%80%93-market-predictions-for-minneapolis-mn-from-the-american-monetary-association/&amp;layout=standard&amp;send=false&amp;show_faces=false&amp;width=&amp;action=like&amp;colorscheme=light&amp;font=" scrolling="no" frameborder="0" allowTransparency="true" style="border:none; overflow:hidden; width:px; height:35px"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 style="text-align: center;"&gt;&lt;img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-643" title="Minneapolis" src="http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/wp-content/uploads/2011/03/Minneapolis-e1300834832624.png" alt="" width="150" height="178" /&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Minneapolis, MN: -10.0% Return on Investment (2011)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Market values in Minneapolis grew significantly from 2000 through  2005, and declined slightly until a larger correction was created by the  2008 financial crisis.&#160; In 2009, values appeared to stabilize but went  through up and down swings as foreclosures came onto the market  following and pulled the prices back down.&#160; The market is beginning to  show signs of stabilization, but the regression back to fundamentals is  likely to take a bit longer than many had anticipated.&#160; Currently,  approximately 54% of real estate listings in Minneapolis are from  foreclosures&lt;a href="#_ftn1"&gt;[1]&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One of the effects emerging in 2010 that we have seen in Minneapolis  is pricing pressure as banks continue to bleed off their inventory of  foreclosed properties and values regress toward a more linear long-term  trajectory.&#160; Our models estimate that this effect will continue to place  pressure on prices in Minneapolis,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div style="display: none"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;resulting in a value bottom that  takes a bit longer to establish than in some of the other market areas.&#160;  Population in the city has remained relatively flat throughout the last  10 years.&#160; The city represents an important area of commerce in the  northern Midwest, but is not a focal point of in-migration and  population growth that are typical of vibrant investment markets.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Investors in Minneapolis will be challenged to generate attractive  rates of return, since the market rents are not expected to be  sufficiently large to cover operating expenses and mortgage payments for  properties in the area.&#160; This means that investor returns will be  dependent on realizing value appreciation and selling to compensate for  the accumulated negative cash flow.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Since the expected negative cash flows must be financed out of pocket  until an investment property can be sold, and since the proceeds of  that sale must be sufficient large to offset the cumulative negative  cash flows, we do not recommend Minneapolis as a focus point for income  property investment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;hr size="1" /&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="#_ftnref1"&gt;[1]&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="http://realestate.yahoo.com/"&gt;http://realestate.yahoo.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div style="display: none"&gt;zp8497586rq&lt;/div&gt;
</content:encoded>
                    <wfw:commentRss>http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/video-podcast/19-%e2%80%93-market-predictions-for-minneapolis-mn-from-the-american-monetary-association/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
                    <slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>#18 – Market Predictions for Miami, FL from the American Monetary Association</title>
                    <link>http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/video-podcast/18-%e2%80%93-market-predictions-for-miami-fl-from-the-american-monetary-association/</link>
                    <comments>http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/video-podcast/18-%e2%80%93-market-predictions-for-miami-fl-from-the-american-monetary-association/#comments</comments>
                    <pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2011 18:13:19 +0000</pubDate>
                    <dc:creator>Jason Hartman</dc:creator>
                    <category>Video Podcast</category>
                    <category>fl</category>
                    <category>florida</category>
                    <category>market predictions</category>
                    <category>miami</category>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/?p=656</guid>
                    <description>Miami, FL: -6.9% Return on Investment (2011) Miami represents one of the most notorious bubble markets in the entire United States.&#160; Its prodigious rise and precipitous decline have served as a warning sign for the potential disaster that can await investors attempting to time value bubbles.&#160; However, Miami is also a unique market area, since [...]</description>
                    <content:encoded> 
&lt;span class = "" style = "height: 35px;  "&gt;&lt;iframe src="http://www.facebook.com/plugins/like.php?href=http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/video-podcast/18-%e2%80%93-market-predictions-for-miami-fl-from-the-american-monetary-association/&amp;layout=standard&amp;send=false&amp;show_faces=false&amp;width=&amp;action=like&amp;colorscheme=light&amp;font=" scrolling="no" frameborder="0" allowTransparency="true" style="border:none; overflow:hidden; width:px; height:35px"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 style="text-align: center;"&gt;&lt;img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-642" title="Miami" src="http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/wp-content/uploads/2011/03/Miami-e1300834811899.png" alt="" width="150" height="178" /&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Miami, FL: -6.9% Return on Investment (2011)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Miami represents one of the most notorious bubble markets in the  entire United States.&#160; Its prodigious rise and precipitous decline have  served as a warning sign for the potential disaster that can await  investors attempting to time value bubbles.&#160; However, Miami is also a  unique market area, since it is segmented between two distinctly  different classes of properties.&#160; These two classes are single-family  homes and high-rise condominiums.&#160; The importance of distinguishing  between the two comes from the fact that high-rise condominiums bore the  brunt of Miami’s value free-fall, and single-family homes are showing  signs of stabilization.&#160; Currently, approximately 42% of Miami’s home  inventory is coming from foreclosures&lt;a href="#_ftn1"&gt;[1]&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The collapse of values in Miami began in 2007 and continued through  2010, as properties were lost to foreclosure at record rates.&#160; Most of  the value collapse in Miam&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div style="display: none"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;i was driven by the high-rise condominiums  that came to exemplify the real estate bubble.&#160; For investors who  purchased at the market highs, Miami has been a roller coaster ride of  value destruction as leveraged losses escalated higher and higher.&#160; As  2011 begins to unfold, many forecasts are indicating that Miami will  begin to approach its cyclical bottom.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Upon hitting their cyclical bottom, it is likely that Miami will  regress back toward a very modest rate of long-term appreciation.&#160; This  process will be impacted by the release of foreclosure inventory that is  being held by banks in the hopes that it can be introduced to the  market after values have stabilized.&#160; There is a slight possibility that  investors who buy into Miami at the right time can realize some value  appreciation that comes from regression back to fundamentals off the  cyclical value bottom.&#160; However, cash flow from properties in Miami is  still quite low, relative to the current market values.&#160; This makes  investment in Miami a very risky gamble of timing the value cycle.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;hr size="1" /&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="#_ftnref1"&gt;[1]&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="http://realestate.yahoo.com/"&gt;http://realestate.yahoo.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div style="display: none"&gt;zp8497586rq&lt;/div&gt;
</content:encoded>
                    <wfw:commentRss>http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/video-podcast/18-%e2%80%93-market-predictions-for-miami-fl-from-the-american-monetary-association/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
                    <slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>#17 – Market Predictions for Los Angeles, CA from the American Monetary Association</title>
                    <link>http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/video-podcast/17-%e2%80%93-market-predictions-for-los-angeles-ca-from-the-american-monetary-association/</link>
                    <comments>http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/video-podcast/17-%e2%80%93-market-predictions-for-los-angeles-ca-from-the-american-monetary-association/#comments</comments>
                    <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2011 22:55:58 +0000</pubDate>
                    <dc:creator>Jason Hartman</dc:creator>
                    <category>Video Podcast</category>
                    <category>ca</category>
                    <category>california</category>
                    <category>los angeles</category>
                    <category>market predictions</category>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/?p=639</guid>
                    <description>Los Angeles, CA: -17.5% Return on investment (2011) Los Angeles is a market segment area that is in serious distress, and is likely to experience continued difficulties before a recovery is in sight.&#160; The state of California is currently in the midst of a far-reaching budget crisis that is likely to result in dramatic cuts [...]</description>
                    <content:encoded> 
&lt;span class = "" style = "height: 35px;  "&gt;&lt;iframe src="http://www.facebook.com/plugins/like.php?href=http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/video-podcast/17-%e2%80%93-market-predictions-for-los-angeles-ca-from-the-american-monetary-association/&amp;layout=standard&amp;send=false&amp;show_faces=false&amp;width=&amp;action=like&amp;colorscheme=light&amp;font=" scrolling="no" frameborder="0" allowTransparency="true" style="border:none; overflow:hidden; width:px; height:35px"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 style="text-align: center;"&gt;&lt;img class="size-full wp-image-641 aligncenter" title="LosAngeles" src="http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/wp-content/uploads/2011/03/LosAngeles-e1300834786677.png" alt="" width="150" height="178" /&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Los Angeles, CA: -17.5% Return on investment (2011)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Los Angeles is a market segment area that is in serious distress, and  is likely to experience continued difficulties before a recovery is in  sight.&#160; The state of California is currently in the midst of a  far-reaching budget crisis that is likely to result in dramatic cuts to  many public services.&#160; The public pension fund is estimated to be $500  billion dollars under-funded&lt;a href="#_ftn1"&gt;[1]&lt;/a&gt;, which will require either tax increases, benefit cuts, or both.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With a relatively high percentage of its population depending on  government services, Los Angeles is particularly vulnerable to cuts in  the state budget.&#160; In addition to this, the tax and regulatory  environment are extremely burdensome, which is expected to result in  many businesses moving out of southern California.&#160; With the 2010  election, seeing the current political power structure held intact, we  expect to see no significant changes in public policy for California  until it is too late for those policies to have a significant impact.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Val
&lt;div style="display: none"&gt;&lt;a href='http://start-success-up.com/mejorar-las-erecciones-cure-erectile-dysfunction-spanish' title='Mejorar Las Erecciones - Cure Erectile Dysfunction Spanish'&gt;Mejorar Las Erecciones &amp;#8211; Cure Erectile Dysfunction Spanish&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ues were temporarily stabilized in 2009 by the government subsidy  for first time homebuyers, but continued their regression to  fundamentals in 2010 as the subsidies ended and the poor market  fundamentals become exposed.&#160; Los   Angeles represents a generally poor  market for long-term investment, due to its price volatility and low  rents relative to market prices.&#160; Currently, approximately 60% of  listings in Los Angeles are foreclosures&lt;a href="#_ftn2"&gt;[2]&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As 2011 unfolds, we are expecting to see the Los Angeles area resume a  modest growth trajectory as values creep up from the expected bottom.&#160;  For investors who capture this expected value increase, a net positive  return on investment is possible, but may prove difficult to capture  since the negative cash flows must be supported on a continual basis  while the value appreciation is only captured when the property is  re-financed or sold.&#160; For income property investors, Los Angeles is  fool’s gold.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;hr size="1" /&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="#_ftnref1"&gt;[1]&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="http://siepr.stanford.edu/system/files/shared/GoingforBroke_pb.pdf"&gt;http://siepr.stanford.edu/system/files/shared/GoingforBroke_pb.pdf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="#_ftnref2"&gt;[2]&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="http://realestate.yahoo.com/"&gt;http://realestate.yahoo.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div style="display: none"&gt;zp8497586rq&lt;/div&gt;
</content:encoded>
                    <wfw:commentRss>http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/video-podcast/17-%e2%80%93-market-predictions-for-los-angeles-ca-from-the-american-monetary-association/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
                    <slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
                    <enclosure url="http://media.blubrry.com/americanmonetaryassociation/s3.amazonaws.com/americanmonetaryassociation/video/MP-AMA-LosAngelesCA_iPod.mp4" length="5299910" type="video/mp4"/>
                    <itunes:keywords>ca,california,los angeles,market predictions</itunes:keywords>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Los Angeles, CA: -17.5% Return on investment (2011) Los Angeles is a market segment area that is in serious distress, and  is likely to experience continued difficulties before a recovery is in  sight.&#160; The state of California is currently in the mids...</itunes:subtitle>
                    <itunes:summary>Los Angeles, CA: -17.5% Return on investment (2011)
Los Angeles is a market segment area that is in serious distress, and  is likely to experience continued difficulties before a recovery is in  sight.&#160; The state of California is currently in the midst of a  far-reaching budget crisis that is likely to result in dramatic cuts to  many public services.&#160; The public pension fund is estimated to be $500  billion dollars under-funded[1], which will require either tax increases, benefit cuts, or both.

With a relatively high percentage of its population depending on  government services, Los Angeles is particularly vulnerable to cuts in  the state budget.&#160; In addition to this, the tax and regulatory  environment are extremely burdensome, which is expected to result in  many businesses moving out of southern California.&#160; With the 2010  election, seeing the current political power structure held intact, we  expect to see no significant changes in public policy for California  until it is too late for those policies to have a significant impact.

ValMejorar Las Erecciones - Cure Erectile Dysfunction Spanishues were temporarily stabilized in 2009 by the government subsidy  for first time homebuyers, but continued their regression to  fundamentals in 2010 as the subsidies ended and the poor market  fundamentals become exposed.&#160; Los   Angeles represents a generally poor  market for long-term investment, due to its price volatility and low  rents relative to market prices.&#160; Currently, approximately 60% of  listings in Los Angeles are foreclosures[2].

As 2011 unfolds, we are expecting to see the Los Angeles area resume a  modest growth trajectory as values creep up from the expected bottom.&#160;  For investors who capture this expected value increase, a net positive  return on investment is possible, but may prove difficult to capture  since the negative cash flows must be supported on a continual basis  while the value appreciation is only captured when the property is  re-financed or sold.&#160; For income property investors, Los Angeles is  fool’s gold.






[1] http://siepr.stanford.edu/system/files/shared/GoingforBroke_pb.pdf




[2] http://realestate.yahoo.com/



  zp8497586rq</itunes:summary>
                    <itunes:author>Jason Hartman</itunes:author>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>#16 – Market Predictions for Las Vegas, NV from the American Monetary Association</title>
                    <link>http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/video-podcast/16-market-predictions-for-las-vegas-nv-from-the-american-monetary-association/</link>
                    <comments>http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/video-podcast/16-market-predictions-for-las-vegas-nv-from-the-american-monetary-association/#comments</comments>
                    <pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2011 17:41:22 +0000</pubDate>
                    <dc:creator>Jason Hartman</dc:creator>
                    <category>Video Podcast</category>
                    <category>las vegas</category>
                    <category>market predictions</category>
                    <category>nv</category>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/?p=577</guid>
                    <description>Las Vegas, NV: -7.9% Return on Investment (2011) The Las Vegas market is very similar to Miami, due to the intense over-building of high-rise condominiums in both markets.&#160; The markets also share a similarity of value trajectories for single-family homes and high-rise units.&#160; The overall market value contractions in Las Vegas are being driven by&#160; [...]</description>
                    <content:encoded> 
&lt;span class = "" style = "height: 35px;  "&gt;&lt;iframe src="http://www.facebook.com/plugins/like.php?href=http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/video-podcast/16-market-predictions-for-las-vegas-nv-from-the-american-monetary-association/&amp;layout=standard&amp;send=false&amp;show_faces=false&amp;width=&amp;action=like&amp;colorscheme=light&amp;font=" scrolling="no" frameborder="0" allowTransparency="true" style="border:none; overflow:hidden; width:px; height:35px"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;img class="alignleft size-full wp-image-547" style="margin: 10px;" title="LasVegasROI" src="http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/wp-content/uploads/2011/03/LasVegasROI-e1299690927246.png" alt="" width="150" height="178" /&gt;Las Vegas, NV: -7.9% Return on Investment (2011)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Las Vegas market is very similar to Miami, due to the intense over-building of high-rise condominiums in both markets.&#160; The markets also share a similarity of value trajectories for single-family homes and high-rise units.&#160; The overall market value contractions in Las Vegas are being driven by&#160; high-rise condominiums, with single-family homes expected to stabilize much sooner than the high-rise units.&#160; Currently, approximately 66% of listings in Las Vegas are from foreclosures&lt;a href="#_ftn1"&gt;[1]&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The sharp reductions in market prices over recent years has brought values back down to levels that are similar to the year 2000.&#160; This has pulled rental cash flows more in line &#160;with the operating expenses and mortgage payments.&#160; The opportune time for investment in Las Vegas has not yet arrived though, since the ratio between rents and values is still considerably weaker than many other markets.&#160; On balance, this means that Las   V
&lt;div style="display: none"&gt;&lt;a href='http://life4success.net/top-selling-guide-recondition-battery-com-75-commission' title='Top Selling Guide - Recondition Battery .com - 75% Commission'&gt;Top Selling Guide &amp;#8211; Recondition Battery .com &amp;#8211; 75% Commission&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;egas may become a viable place for investment in the future but that investors should be very cautious about moving into the market during 2010 and for most of 2011.&#160; With banks holding a large amount of foreclosure inventory in the Las Vegas area, it is likely that there will be low-priced inventory available for quite some time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The recovery path for Las Vegas is expected to lag many other major markets, due to the high concentration of commerce in the entertainment industry.&#160; Since entertainment is typically a lagging indicator of growth and recovery, we expect Las Vegas to encounter a slower growth path than the economy at large.&#160; It is likely that the ‘bottom’ in Las Vegas will occur at approximately the same time as the larger economy is beginning to shift toward growth.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On balance, there is a possibility that Las Vegas will become a healthy market again at some point in the near future.&#160; However, this can only happen when the market fundamentals re-align to create a growth trajectory.&#160; The time has not come yet for Las Vegas as an investment market.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;hr size="1" /&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="#_ftnref1"&gt;[1]&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="http://realestate.yahoo.com/"&gt;http://realestate.yahoo.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div style="display: none"&gt;zp8497586rq&lt;/div&gt;
</content:encoded>
                    <wfw:commentRss>http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/video-podcast/16-market-predictions-for-las-vegas-nv-from-the-american-monetary-association/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
                    <slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
                    <enclosure url="http://media.blubrry.com/americanmonetaryassociation/s3.amazonaws.com/americanmonetaryassociation/video/MP-AMA-LasVegasNV.mp4" length="9654737" type="video/mp4"/>
                    <itunes:keywords>las vegas,market predictions,nv</itunes:keywords>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Las Vegas, NV: -7.9% Return on Investment (2011) The Las Vegas market is very similar to Miami, due to the intense over-building of high-rise condominiums in both markets.&#160; The markets also share a similarity of value trajectories for single-family hom...</itunes:subtitle>
                    <itunes:summary>Las Vegas, NV: -7.9% Return on Investment (2011)
The Las Vegas market is very similar to Miami, due to the intense over-building of high-rise condominiums in both markets.&#160; The markets also share a similarity of value trajectories for single-family homes and high-rise units.&#160; The overall market value contractions in Las Vegas are being driven by&#160; high-rise condominiums, with single-family homes expected to stabilize much sooner than the high-rise units.&#160; Currently, approximately 66% of listings in Las Vegas are from foreclosures[1].
The sharp reductions in market prices over recent years has brought values back down to levels that are similar to the year 2000.&#160; This has pulled rental cash flows more in line &#160;with the operating expenses and mortgage payments.&#160; The opportune time for investment in Las Vegas has not yet arrived though, since the ratio between rents and values is still considerably weaker than many other markets.&#160; On balance, this means that Las   VTop Selling Guide - Recondition Battery .com - 75% Commissionegas may become a viable place for investment in the future but that investors should be very cautious about moving into the market during 2010 and for most of 2011.&#160; With banks holding a large amount of foreclosure inventory in the Las Vegas area, it is likely that there will be low-priced inventory available for quite some time.
The recovery path for Las Vegas is expected to lag many other major markets, due to the high concentration of commerce in the entertainment industry.&#160; Since entertainment is typically a lagging indicator of growth and recovery, we expect Las Vegas to encounter a slower growth path than the economy at large.&#160; It is likely that the ‘bottom’ in Las Vegas will occur at approximately the same time as the larger economy is beginning to shift toward growth.
On balance, there is a possibility that Las Vegas will become a healthy market again at some point in the near future.&#160; However, this can only happen when the market fundamentals re-align to create a growth trajectory.&#160; The time has not come yet for Las Vegas as an investment market.



[1] http://realestate.yahoo.com/


 zp8497586rq</itunes:summary>
                    <itunes:author>Jason Hartman</itunes:author>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>#15 – Market Predictions for Kansas City, MO from the American Monetary Association</title>
                    <link>http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/video-podcast/15-market-predictions-for-kansas-city-mo-from-the-american-monetary-association/</link>
                    <comments>http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/video-podcast/15-market-predictions-for-kansas-city-mo-from-the-american-monetary-association/#comments</comments>
                    <pubDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2011 17:37:36 +0000</pubDate>
                    <dc:creator>Jason Hartman</dc:creator>
                    <category>Video Podcast</category>
                    <category>kansas city</category>
                    <category>market predictions</category>
                    <category>mo</category>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/?p=575</guid>
                    <description>Kansas City, MO: 15.4% Return on Investment (2011) Kansas City experienced a prolonged period of steady value appreciation up until its value peak in 2006, and only a minor correction afterward.&#160; The 2008 financial crisis only impacted Kansas City modestly, as its values had already contracted.&#160; The subsequent years saw moderate price volatility that appears [...]</description>
                    <content:encoded> 
&lt;span class = "" style = "height: 35px;  "&gt;&lt;iframe src="http://www.facebook.com/plugins/like.php?href=http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/video-podcast/15-market-predictions-for-kansas-city-mo-from-the-american-monetary-association/&amp;layout=standard&amp;send=false&amp;show_faces=false&amp;width=&amp;action=like&amp;colorscheme=light&amp;font=" scrolling="no" frameborder="0" allowTransparency="true" style="border:none; overflow:hidden; width:px; height:35px"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;img class="alignleft size-full wp-image-546" style="margin: 10px;" title="KansasCityROI" src="http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/wp-content/uploads/2011/03/KansasCityROI-e1299690951651.png" alt="" width="150" height="178" /&gt;Kansas City, MO: 15.4% Return on Investment (2011)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kansas City experienced a prolonged period of steady value appreciation up until its value peak in 2006, and only a minor correction afterward.&#160; The 2008 financial crisis only impacted Kansas City modestly, as its values had already contracted.&#160; The subsequent years saw moderate price volatility that appears to be approaching a bottom in 2011.&#160; We anticipate modest net value appreciation in 2011 as Kansas   City joins most other linear markets in a regression toward fundamentally sound valuation.&#160; Currently, approximately 22% of listings are from foreclosures&lt;a href="#_ftn1"&gt;[1]&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As the transportation hub between all four corners of the United States, Kansas City represents a &#160;vibrant market for investors.&#160; Between transportation, agriculture, and other forms of commerce, Kansas   City represents a fundamentally sound city with a solid economic base.&#160; The importance of a steady economy like Kansas City is that it does not typically exhibit the same level of volatility as other market areas with h&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div style="display: none"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;igher taxes that are more tightly regulated.&#160; The reason is that low tax, low regulation environments can support “bread and butter” industry that operates at lower profit margins.&#160; When the tax and legal burdens are increased, only high margin companies can survive.&#160; Since high margin industries are also the most volatile, it logically follows that escalations in the cost of doing business for a given area will increase the amount of value volatility.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kansas City is another area with attractive cash flows that serve as the fundamental basis of its ROI profile.&#160; The linear nature of the market means that investors should only expect modest value increases and leveraged appreciation over the long-term horizon.&#160; However, the superior cash flows still exceed the rates of return for many other investment categories with similar or even higher levels of risk.&#160; It is unlikely that Kansas City will become the next booming metropolis, but it is also unlikely that the city will experience a value collapse either.&#160; It is a solid market that provides an excellent opportunity for income property investors to build the basis of their portfolios.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;hr size="1" /&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="#_ftnref1"&gt;[1]&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="http://realestate.yahoo.com/"&gt;http://realestate.yahoo.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div style="display: none"&gt;zp8497586rq&lt;/div&gt;
</content:encoded>
                    <wfw:commentRss>http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/video-podcast/15-market-predictions-for-kansas-city-mo-from-the-american-monetary-association/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
                    <slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>#14 – Market Predictions for Indianapolis, IN from the American Monetary Association</title>
                    <link>http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/video-podcast/14-market-predictions-for-indianapolis-in-from-the-american-monetary-association/</link>
                    <comments>http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/video-podcast/14-market-predictions-for-indianapolis-in-from-the-american-monetary-association/#comments</comments>
                    <pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2011 16:54:18 +0000</pubDate>
                    <dc:creator>Jason Hartman</dc:creator>
                    <category>Video Podcast</category>
                    <category>in</category>
                    <category>indianapolis</category>
                    <category>market predictions</category>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/?p=571</guid>
                    <description>Indianapolis, IN: 32.0% Return on Investment (2011) Indianapolis has experienced repeated value fluctuations in 2009, resulting from the release of foreclosures into the housing inventory.&#160; When foreclosures were introduced into the market, they suppressed values and spurred capital inflows from owners and investors, which triggered the introduction of more foreclosed properties to capitalize on the [...]</description>
                    <content:encoded> 
&lt;span class = "" style = "height: 35px;  "&gt;&lt;iframe src="http://www.facebook.com/plugins/like.php?href=http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/video-podcast/14-market-predictions-for-indianapolis-in-from-the-american-monetary-association/&amp;layout=standard&amp;send=false&amp;show_faces=false&amp;width=&amp;action=like&amp;colorscheme=light&amp;font=" scrolling="no" frameborder="0" allowTransparency="true" style="border:none; overflow:hidden; width:px; height:35px"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;img class="alignleft size-full wp-image-545" style="margin: 10px;" title="IndianapolisROI" src="http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/wp-content/uploads/2011/03/IndianapolisROI-e1299690974622.png" alt="" width="150" height="178" /&gt;Indianapolis, IN: 32.0% Return on Investment (2011)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Indianapolis has experienced repeated value fluctuations in 2009, resulting from the release of foreclosures into the housing inventory.&#160; When foreclosures were introduced into the market, they suppressed values and spurred capital inflows from owners and investors, which triggered the introduction of more foreclosed properties to capitalize on the uptick in values.&#160; These fluctuations have occurred within a relatively narrow value band, and have significantly reduced the foreclosure inventory in the Indianapolis market area.&#160; Currently, approximately 16% of listings are from foreclosures&lt;a href="#_ftn1"&gt;[1]&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Indianapolis market currently produces large levels of cash flow because of the strong market &#160;rents in conjunction with the market prices that have been depressed by foreclosures.&#160; Many of these foreclosed properties require additional capital for rehabilitation after the property is acquired.&#160; This results in the ROI mix t&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div style="display: none"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ilting away from leveraged appreciation toward higher cash flow.&#160; Another opportunity for investors in Indianapolis is ‘built-in’ appreciation from properties purchased below the cost of construction as market prices regress toward replacement cost.&#160; Our preferred term for investments in the Indianapolis market are that of an “income property bond” since much of the total returns come from cash flows.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The superior cash flows produced in Indianapolis relative to many other market areas has produced some very unique economics.&#160; With a large inflow of investment capital from people seeking to capture high rates of cash flow that properties in Indianapolis exhibit, it has facilitated a faster than expected regression of values back to a long-term equilibrium.&#160; The reason for this is because many foreclosure properties in Indianapolis were priced below the cost to re-build them (aka ‘replacement cost’).&#160; Outside of this phenomenon, Indianapolis is a very linear market where investors should expect modest rates of normal value appreciation in conjunction with the cash flow.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;hr size="1" /&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="#_ftnref1"&gt;[1]&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="http://realestate.yahoo.com/"&gt;http://realestate.yahoo.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div style="display: none"&gt;zp8497586rq&lt;/div&gt;
</content:encoded>
                    <wfw:commentRss>http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/video-podcast/14-market-predictions-for-indianapolis-in-from-the-american-monetary-association/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
                    <slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>#13 – Market Predictions for Houston, TX from the American Monetary Association</title>
                    <link>http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/video-podcast/13-market-predictions-for-houston-tx-from-the-american-monetary-association/</link>
                    <comments>http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/video-podcast/13-market-predictions-for-houston-tx-from-the-american-monetary-association/#comments</comments>
                    <pubDate>Tue, 22 Mar 2011 16:52:28 +0000</pubDate>
                    <dc:creator>Jason Hartman</dc:creator>
                    <category>Video Podcast</category>
                    <category>houston</category>
                    <category>market predictions</category>
                    <category>tx</category>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/?p=569</guid>
                    <description>Houston, TX: 19.1% Return on Investment (2011) Houston differs from many other markets in that its values were severely depressed during the 1990’s, because of low energy prices.&#160; This led to a significant degree of value appreciation from 2000 through 2007, but a moderate contraction after the financial crisis that temporarily stabilized when the government [...]</description>
                    <content:encoded> 
&lt;span class = "" style = "height: 35px;  "&gt;&lt;iframe src="http://www.facebook.com/plugins/like.php?href=http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/video-podcast/13-market-predictions-for-houston-tx-from-the-american-monetary-association/&amp;layout=standard&amp;send=false&amp;show_faces=false&amp;width=&amp;action=like&amp;colorscheme=light&amp;font=" scrolling="no" frameborder="0" allowTransparency="true" style="border:none; overflow:hidden; width:px; height:35px"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;img class="alignleft size-full wp-image-544" style="margin: 10px;" title="HoustonROI" src="http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/wp-content/uploads/2011/03/HoustonROI-e1299691025630.png" alt="" width="150" height="178" /&gt;Houston, TX: 19.1% Return on Investment (2011)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Houston differs from many other markets in that its values were severely depressed during the 1990’s, because of low energy prices.&#160; This led to a significant degree of value appreciation from 2000 through 2007, but a moderate contraction after the financial crisis that temporarily stabilized when the government home subsidies were available.&#160; After the subsidies expired, values in Houston resumed a course of moderate volatility.&#160; This is reflective of a fundamentally under-valued market that is regressing toward its rational value.&#160; Currently, approximately 31% of listings are from foreclosures&lt;a href="#_ftn1"&gt;[1]&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With the backbone of Houston’s economy coming from the energy and medical research industries, the city possesses an attractive employment base with a high percentage of residents who rent.&#160; These factors combine to create an attractive investment environment with a strong base of tenants and the potential for continued
&lt;div style="display: none"&gt;&lt;a href='http://start-success-up.com/cure-diabetes-naturally-by-world-renowned-ph-d-in-clinical-nutrition' title='Cure Diabetes Naturally: By World-renowned Ph.d. In Clinical Nutrition'&gt;Cure Diabetes Naturally: By World-renowned Ph.d. In Clinical Nutrition&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt; value appreciation if market prices in Houston regress toward the national average in 2011 and beyond.&#160; Values appear to be at a bottom as we exit 2010, and are expected to increase modestly in 2011 and beyond.&#160; The fundamental economics of the city are quite favorable to investors, since the current ‘weak dollar’ strategy of government monetary policy is likely to escalate energy prices, which will continue to benefit Houston’s business climate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Houston offers a very balanced ROI profile that is evenly spread out between healthy cash flows, modest value gains, and leveraged appreciation.&#160; It shares many characteristics in common with other markets in Texas, in that it is driven by a relatively high concentration of renters who are seeking to avoid directly paying the high property taxes that are charged by the state.&#160; This effect serves to cap value escalation since there are less people in the homebuyer market, and creates an ideal marketplace for income property investors.&#160; These characteristics make Houston a favorable place for income property investors.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;hr size="1" /&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="#_ftnref1"&gt;[1]&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="http://realestate.yahoo.com/"&gt;http://realestate.yahoo.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div style="display: none"&gt;&lt;a href='http://start-success-up.com/cure-diabetes-naturally-by-world-renowned-ph-d-in-clinical-nutrition' title='Cure Diabetes Naturally: By World-renowned Ph.d. In Clinical Nutrition'&gt;Cure Diabetes Naturally: By World-renowned Ph.d. In Clinical Nutrition&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div style="display: none"&gt;zp8497586rq&lt;/div&gt;
</content:encoded>
                    <wfw:commentRss>http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/video-podcast/13-market-predictions-for-houston-tx-from-the-american-monetary-association/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
                    <slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
                    <enclosure url="http://media.blubrry.com/americanmonetaryassociation/s3.amazonaws.com/americanmonetaryassociation/video/MP-AMA-HoustonTX.mp4" length="10948389" type="video/mp4"/>
                    <itunes:keywords>houston,market predictions,tx</itunes:keywords>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Houston, TX: 19.1% Return on Investment (2011) Houston differs from many other markets in that its values were severely depressed during the 1990’s, because of low energy prices.&#160; This led to a significant degree of value appreciation from 2000 through...</itunes:subtitle>
                    <itunes:summary>Houston, TX: 19.1% Return on Investment (2011)
Houston differs from many other markets in that its values were severely depressed during the 1990’s, because of low energy prices.&#160; This led to a significant degree of value appreciation from 2000 through 2007, but a moderate contraction after the financial crisis that temporarily stabilized when the government home subsidies were available.&#160; After the subsidies expired, values in Houston resumed a course of moderate volatility.&#160; This is reflective of a fundamentally under-valued market that is regressing toward its rational value.&#160; Currently, approximately 31% of listings are from foreclosures[1].
With the backbone of Houston’s economy coming from the energy and medical research industries, the city possesses an attractive employment base with a high percentage of residents who rent.&#160; These factors combine to create an attractive investment environment with a strong base of tenants and the potential for continuedCure Diabetes Naturally: By World-renowned Ph.d. In Clinical Nutrition value appreciation if market prices in Houston regress toward the national average in 2011 and beyond.&#160; Values appear to be at a bottom as we exit 2010, and are expected to increase modestly in 2011 and beyond.&#160; The fundamental economics of the city are quite favorable to investors, since the current ‘weak dollar’ strategy of government monetary policy is likely to escalate energy prices, which will continue to benefit Houston’s business climate.
Houston offers a very balanced ROI profile that is evenly spread out between healthy cash flows, modest value gains, and leveraged appreciation.&#160; It shares many characteristics in common with other markets in Texas, in that it is driven by a relatively high concentration of renters who are seeking to avoid directly paying the high property taxes that are charged by the state.&#160; This effect serves to cap value escalation since there are less people in the homebuyer market, and creates an ideal marketplace for income property investors.&#160; These characteristics make Houston a favorable place for income property investors.



[1] http://realestate.yahoo.com/


 Cure Diabetes Naturally: By World-renowned Ph.d. In Clinical Nutrition  zp8497586rq</itunes:summary>
                    <itunes:author>Jason Hartman</itunes:author>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>#12 – Market Predictions for Detroit, MI from the American Monetary Association</title>
                    <link>http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/video-podcast/12-market-predictions-for-detroit-mi-from-the-american-monetary-association/</link>
                    <comments>http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/video-podcast/12-market-predictions-for-detroit-mi-from-the-american-monetary-association/#comments</comments>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2011 16:49:52 +0000</pubDate>
                    <dc:creator>Jason Hartman</dc:creator>
                    <category>Video Podcast</category>
                    <category>detroit</category>
                    <category>market predictions</category>
                    <category>mi</category>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/?p=567</guid>
                    <description>Detroit, MI: 9.7% Return on Investment (2011) Detroit is one of the most widely publicized toxic markets in the United States.&#160; Extensive financial difficulty with the auto manufacturers has crippled the primary employment base in Detroit, and plunged the market into free fall.&#160; This is compounded by burdensome taxes and regulations from the government and [...]</description>
                    <content:encoded> 
&lt;span class = "" style = "height: 35px;  "&gt;&lt;iframe src="http://www.facebook.com/plugins/like.php?href=http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/video-podcast/12-market-predictions-for-detroit-mi-from-the-american-monetary-association/&amp;layout=standard&amp;send=false&amp;show_faces=false&amp;width=&amp;action=like&amp;colorscheme=light&amp;font=" scrolling="no" frameborder="0" allowTransparency="true" style="border:none; overflow:hidden; width:px; height:35px"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;img class="alignleft size-full wp-image-543" style="margin: 10px;" title="DetroitROI" src="http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/wp-content/uploads/2011/03/DetroitROI-e1299691056983.png" alt="" width="150" height="178" /&gt;Detroit, MI: 9.7% Return on Investment (2011)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Detroit is one of the most widely publicized toxic markets in the United States.&#160; Extensive financial difficulty with the auto manufacturers has crippled the primary employment base in Detroit, and plunged the market into free fall.&#160; This is compounded by burdensome taxes and regulations from the government and union organizations that are significantly impeding the new investments required to spur a fundamental economic recovery.&#160; Currently, approximately 61% of listings in Detroit are from foreclosures&lt;a href="#_ftn1"&gt;[1]&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Values in Detroit have been significantly depressed in recent years, which have made affordability &#160;much better for residents and investors.&#160; However, the population of Detroit is steadily decreasing, due to the flight of jobs away from the city.&#160; Many people have seen repeated news stories showing extremely inexpensive properties for sale in Detroit.&#160; Unfortunately, the net flight of jobs out of the area will make it
&lt;div style="display: none"&gt;&lt;a href='http://start-success-up.com/hair-loss-black-book-hot-new-product-untapped-cb-niche' title='Hair Loss Black Book - Hot New Product - Untapped CB Niche!'&gt;Hair Loss Black Book &amp;#8211; Hot New Product &amp;#8211; Untapped CB Niche!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt; increasingly difficult for investors to find tenants and for residents to find work.&#160; This has resulted in many abandoned property and high vacancy rates for rental property.&#160; On balance, this makes Detroit an extremely dangerous place to invest since there is likely to be a sustained period of economic contraction on the horizon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Values in Detroit have been in a perpetual downward spiral since the financial crisis of 2008.&#160; Rents in the area show reasonable strength in relation to cash flow, but this makes a fundamental assumption that an income property is occupied.&#160; With very high rates of vacancy for rental property in Detroit, it is entirely possible that vacancy could destroy the cash flow of an income property investment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our models indicate that values in Detroit will bottom during 2011, as a result of decreased supply from government decisions to bulldoze vacant neighborhoods in an attempt to reduce oversupply in the real estate market.&#160; Detroit is in decline, and will not be favorable for investors until its economic fundamentals improve significantly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;hr size="1" /&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="#_ftnref1"&gt;[1]&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="http://realestate.yahoo.com/"&gt;http://realestate.yahoo.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div style="display: none"&gt;&lt;a href='http://start-success-up.com/hair-loss-black-book-hot-new-product-untapped-cb-niche' title='Hair Loss Black Book - Hot New Product - Untapped CB Niche!'&gt;Hair Loss Black Book &amp;#8211; Hot New Product &amp;#8211; Untapped CB Niche!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div style="display: none"&gt;zp8497586rq&lt;/div&gt;
</content:encoded>
                    <wfw:commentRss>http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/video-podcast/12-market-predictions-for-detroit-mi-from-the-american-monetary-association/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
                    <slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
                    <enclosure url="http://media.blubrry.com/americanmonetaryassociation/s3.amazonaws.com/americanmonetaryassociation/video/MP-AMA-DetroitMI.mp4" length="10998772" type="video/mp4"/>
                    <itunes:keywords>detroit,market predictions,mi</itunes:keywords>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Detroit, MI: 9.7% Return on Investment (2011) Detroit is one of the most widely publicized toxic markets in the United States.&#160; Extensive financial difficulty with the auto manufacturers has crippled the primary employment base in Detroit,</itunes:subtitle>
                    <itunes:summary>Detroit, MI: 9.7% Return on Investment (2011)
Detroit is one of the most widely publicized toxic markets in the United States.&#160; Extensive financial difficulty with the auto manufacturers has crippled the primary employment base in Detroit, and plunged the market into free fall.&#160; This is compounded by burdensome taxes and regulations from the government and union organizations that are significantly impeding the new investments required to spur a fundamental economic recovery.&#160; Currently, approximately 61% of listings in Detroit are from foreclosures[1].
Values in Detroit have been significantly depressed in recent years, which have made affordability &#160;much better for residents and investors.&#160; However, the population of Detroit is steadily decreasing, due to the flight of jobs away from the city.&#160; Many people have seen repeated news stories showing extremely inexpensive properties for sale in Detroit.&#160; Unfortunately, the net flight of jobs out of the area will make itHair Loss Black Book - Hot New Product - Untapped CB Niche! increasingly difficult for investors to find tenants and for residents to find work.&#160; This has resulted in many abandoned property and high vacancy rates for rental property.&#160; On balance, this makes Detroit an extremely dangerous place to invest since there is likely to be a sustained period of economic contraction on the horizon.
Values in Detroit have been in a perpetual downward spiral since the financial crisis of 2008.&#160; Rents in the area show reasonable strength in relation to cash flow, but this makes a fundamental assumption that an income property is occupied.&#160; With very high rates of vacancy for rental property in Detroit, it is entirely possible that vacancy could destroy the cash flow of an income property investment.
Our models indicate that values in Detroit will bottom during 2011, as a result of decreased supply from government decisions to bulldoze vacant neighborhoods in an attempt to reduce oversupply in the real estate market.&#160; Detroit is in decline, and will not be favorable for investors until its economic fundamentals improve significantly.



[1] http://realestate.yahoo.com/


 Hair Loss Black Book - Hot New Product - Untapped CB Niche!  zp8497586rq</itunes:summary>
                    <itunes:author>Jason Hartman</itunes:author>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>#11 – Market Predictions for Denver, CO from the American Monetary Association</title>
                    <link>http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/video-podcast/11-market-predictions-for-denver-co-from-the-american-monetary-association/</link>
                    <comments>http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/video-podcast/11-market-predictions-for-denver-co-from-the-american-monetary-association/#comments</comments>
                    <pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2011 16:39:08 +0000</pubDate>
                    <dc:creator>Jason Hartman</dc:creator>
                    <category>Video Podcast</category>
                    <category>co</category>
                    <category>Denver</category>
                    <category>market predictions</category>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/?p=565</guid>
                    <description>Denver, CO: 13.1% Return on Investment (2011) The Denver area has been a historically stable real estate market for both owners and investors.&#160; Market values experienced a downward correction following the financial crisis of 2008, showed signs of stabilization as 2009 transpired, but that stabilization was short-lived, as the market experienced volatility moving out of [...]</description>
                    <content:encoded> 
&lt;span class = "" style = "height: 35px;  "&gt;&lt;iframe src="http://www.facebook.com/plugins/like.php?href=http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/video-podcast/11-market-predictions-for-denver-co-from-the-american-monetary-association/&amp;layout=standard&amp;send=false&amp;show_faces=false&amp;width=&amp;action=like&amp;colorscheme=light&amp;font=" scrolling="no" frameborder="0" allowTransparency="true" style="border:none; overflow:hidden; width:px; height:35px"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;img class="alignleft size-full wp-image-542" style="margin: 10px;" title="DenverROI" src="http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/wp-content/uploads/2011/03/DenverROI-e1299691106424.png" alt="" width="150" height="178" /&gt;Denver, CO: 13.1% Return on Investment (2011)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Denver area has been a historically stable real estate market for both owners and investors.&#160; Market values experienced a downward correction following the financial crisis of 2008, showed signs of stabilization as 2009 transpired, but that stabilization was short-lived, as the market experienced volatility moving out of 2009 and into 2010.&#160; Currently, approximately 35% of listings in Denver are foreclosures&lt;a href="#_ftn1"&gt;[1]&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The principal value to investors of property in Colorado is its attractive cash flow relative to market &#160;prices.&#160; Denver represents a major market area with characteristics that are favorable for Investment.&#160; This cash flow offers a significant advantage to investors in Denver, since it allows them to ride out volatility in market values.&#160; The overall economics of Denver continue to be strong, making it a solid long-term investment market.&#160; Short-term price fluctuations are likely to deter some investors.&#160; However, people w&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div style="display: none"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ho understand the inherent volatility of value appreciation and the importance of cash flows for the stability and long-term viability of investment properties recognize the long-term power of a market like Denver.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The cash flow generated by properties in the Denver market give investors the power to wait for improvement in market values as the property cash flow exceeds the operating costs and mortgage.&#160; Astute investors understand that investment real estate is about much more than just leveraged value appreciation.&#160; Denver experienced a modest run-up in values from the beginning of 2001 through the end of 2006.&#160; This was a much more mild value inflation than occurred in many of the bubble markets, but was still enough to shift the mindshare of many investors onto appreciation as a source of value.&#160; Fortunately, Denver has not experienced the extended escalation in values as many other bubble markets, resulting in healthy cash flows that are expected to exceed costs by a sufficient margin for investors to gain ‘staying power’ while values in Denver regress back to fundamentals.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;hr size="1" /&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="#_ftnref1"&gt;[1]&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="http://realestate.yahoo.com/"&gt;http://realestate.yahoo.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div style="display: none"&gt;zp8497586rq&lt;/div&gt;
</content:encoded>
                    <wfw:commentRss>http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/video-podcast/11-market-predictions-for-denver-co-from-the-american-monetary-association/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
                    <slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>#10 – Market Predictions for Dallas, TX from the American Monetary Association</title>
                    <link>http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/video-podcast/10-market-predictions-for-dallas-tx-from-the-american-monetary-association/</link>
                    <comments>http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/video-podcast/10-market-predictions-for-dallas-tx-from-the-american-monetary-association/#comments</comments>
                    <pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2011 16:36:22 +0000</pubDate>
                    <dc:creator>Jason Hartman</dc:creator>
                    <category>Video Podcast</category>
                    <category>dallas</category>
                    <category>market predictions</category>
                    <category>tx</category>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/?p=563</guid>
                    <description>Dallas, TX: 19.6% Return on Investment (2011) Dallas experienced a series of moderate appreciation followed by a gradual contraction that has resulted in much less price volatility than has been experienced by other market areas.&#160; The area is expected to hit the bottom of its mild contraction in 2011 and then resume a course of [...]</description>
                    <content:encoded> 
&lt;span class = "" style = "height: 35px;  "&gt;&lt;iframe src="http://www.facebook.com/plugins/like.php?href=http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/video-podcast/10-market-predictions-for-dallas-tx-from-the-american-monetary-association/&amp;layout=standard&amp;send=false&amp;show_faces=false&amp;width=&amp;action=like&amp;colorscheme=light&amp;font=" scrolling="no" frameborder="0" allowTransparency="true" style="border:none; overflow:hidden; width:px; height:35px"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;img class="alignleft size-full wp-image-541" style="margin: 10px;" title="DallasROI" src="http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/wp-content/uploads/2011/03/DallasROI-e1299691136146.png" alt="" width="150" height="178" /&gt;Dallas, TX: 19.6% Return on Investment (2011)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dallas experienced a series of moderate appreciation followed by a gradual contraction that has resulted in much less price volatility than has been experienced by other market areas.&#160; The area is expected to hit the bottom of its mild contraction in 2011 and then resume a course of modest appreciation.&#160; Dallas has a very strong business community, and a large population of renters.&#160; This results in a much slower rate of value appreciation, and a large supply of potential tenants.&#160; Currently, approximately 40% of listings in Dallas are from foreclosures&lt;a href="#_ftn1"&gt;[1]&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The primary strength of Dallas as an investment market is the strong cash flows that it generates.&#160; By building your investment on top of rents that are sufficiently large to pay for the expenses and mortgage on the investment, it will give you the power to hold strong until market conditions are optimal.&#160; In the case of Dallas, there is a ‘perfect storm’ of factors that combine to make it a v
&lt;div style="display: none"&gt;&lt;a href='http://life4success.net/male-to-female-cross-dressing-guide' title='Male-to-female Cross Dressing Guide'&gt;Male-to-female Cross Dressing Guide&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ery strong investment market.&#160; The city has a very strong business sector that attracts skilled employees.&#160; The relatively high property taxes influence many people to rent their homes instead of buy them.&#160; This works to suppress price increases and place upward pressure on rents, since there is a relatively high percentage of the population who rents.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One of the things that some people say about Dallas is that they don’t care for the heat and humidity of summers in Texas.&#160; This dislike of the weather convinces them that Dallas is not a place that they would want to invest.&#160; This sentiment also demonstrates a great income property investing folly where people think that they should only invest in a place where they would want to live.&#160; Just because you would personally choose to live in one place or choose not to live in another doesn’t mean that everybody else shares your sentiment.&#160; Many people have moved to markets like Dallas or Atlanta because of their superior employment opportunities.&#160; Based on this analysis, Dallas represents an excellent opportunity for income property investors.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;hr size="1" /&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="#_ftnref1"&gt;[1]&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="http://realestate.yahoo.com/"&gt;http://realestate.yahoo.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div style="display: none"&gt;&lt;a href='http://life4success.net/male-to-female-cross-dressing-guide' title='Male-to-female Cross Dressing Guide'&gt;Male-to-female Cross Dressing Guide&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div style="display: none"&gt;zp8497586rq&lt;/div&gt;
</content:encoded>
                    <wfw:commentRss>http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/video-podcast/10-market-predictions-for-dallas-tx-from-the-american-monetary-association/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
                    <slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
                    <enclosure url="http://media.blubrry.com/americanmonetaryassociation/s3.amazonaws.com/americanmonetaryassociation/video/MP-AMA-DallasTX.mp4" length="9548818" type="video/mp4"/>
                    <itunes:keywords>dallas,market predictions,tx</itunes:keywords>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Dallas, TX: 19.6% Return on Investment (2011) Dallas experienced a series of moderate appreciation followed by a gradual contraction that has resulted in much less price volatility than has been experienced by other market areas.</itunes:subtitle>
                    <itunes:summary>Dallas, TX: 19.6% Return on Investment (2011)
Dallas experienced a series of moderate appreciation followed by a gradual contraction that has resulted in much less price volatility than has been experienced by other market areas.&#160; The area is expected to hit the bottom of its mild contraction in 2011 and then resume a course of modest appreciation.&#160; Dallas has a very strong business community, and a large population of renters.&#160; This results in a much slower rate of value appreciation, and a large supply of potential tenants.&#160; Currently, approximately 40% of listings in Dallas are from foreclosures[1].
The primary strength of Dallas as an investment market is the strong cash flows that it generates.&#160; By building your investment on top of rents that are sufficiently large to pay for the expenses and mortgage on the investment, it will give you the power to hold strong until market conditions are optimal.&#160; In the case of Dallas, there is a ‘perfect storm’ of factors that combine to make it a vMale-to-female Cross Dressing Guideery strong investment market.&#160; The city has a very strong business sector that attracts skilled employees.&#160; The relatively high property taxes influence many people to rent their homes instead of buy them.&#160; This works to suppress price increases and place upward pressure on rents, since there is a relatively high percentage of the population who rents.
One of the things that some people say about Dallas is that they don’t care for the heat and humidity of summers in Texas.&#160; This dislike of the weather convinces them that Dallas is not a place that they would want to invest.&#160; This sentiment also demonstrates a great income property investing folly where people think that they should only invest in a place where they would want to live.&#160; Just because you would personally choose to live in one place or choose not to live in another doesn’t mean that everybody else shares your sentiment.&#160; Many people have moved to markets like Dallas or Atlanta because of their superior employment opportunities.&#160; Based on this analysis, Dallas represents an excellent opportunity for income property investors.



[1] http://realestate.yahoo.com/


 Male-to-female Cross Dressing Guide  zp8497586rq</itunes:summary>
                    <itunes:author>Jason Hartman</itunes:author>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>#9 – Market Predictions for Columbus, OH from the American Monetary Association</title>
                    <link>http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/video-podcast/9-market-predictions-for-columbus-oh-from-the-american-monetary-association/</link>
                    <comments>http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/video-podcast/9-market-predictions-for-columbus-oh-from-the-american-monetary-association/#comments</comments>
                    <pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2011 16:34:39 +0000</pubDate>
                    <dc:creator>Jason Hartman</dc:creator>
                    <category>Video Podcast</category>
                    <category>columbus</category>
                    <category>market predictions</category>
                    <category>oh</category>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/?p=561</guid>
                    <description>Columbus, OH: 22.5% Return on Investment (2011) Columbus was far ahead of most markets in its peak and adjustment periods, realizing its value height in 2005 and moving into oscillating periods of value stability and volatility following the financial crisis of 2008.&#160; Difficulties in the automotive sector have suppressed values in the upper Midwest, but [...]</description>
                    <content:encoded> 
&lt;span class = "" style = "height: 35px;  "&gt;&lt;iframe src="http://www.facebook.com/plugins/like.php?href=http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/video-podcast/9-market-predictions-for-columbus-oh-from-the-american-monetary-association/&amp;layout=standard&amp;send=false&amp;show_faces=false&amp;width=&amp;action=like&amp;colorscheme=light&amp;font=" scrolling="no" frameborder="0" allowTransparency="true" style="border:none; overflow:hidden; width:px; height:35px"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;img class="alignleft size-full wp-image-540" style="margin: 10px;" title="Columbus" src="http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/wp-content/uploads/2011/03/Columbus-e1299691160846.png" alt="" width="150" height="178" /&gt;Columbus, OH: 22.5% Return on Investment (2011)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Columbus was far ahead of most markets in its peak and adjustment periods, realizing its value height in 2005 and moving into oscillating periods of value stability and volatility following the financial crisis of 2008.&#160; Difficulties in the automotive sector have suppressed values in the upper Midwest, but Columbus possesses good fundamental economics for a sustained period of future growth.&#160; Currently, approximately 45% of listings are from foreclosures&lt;a href="#_ftn1"&gt;[1]&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With a vibrant business community and the main campus of Ohio State University, Columbus is &#160;ideally positioned to create excellent value for investors.&#160; The cash flows available in this area are quite attractive, and can generate significant returns for investors that are not dependent on value appreciation.&#160; When appreciation re-emerges, it push
&lt;div style="display: none"&gt;&lt;a href='http://start-success-up.com/ovecome-premature-jaculation' title='Ovecome Premature Jaculation'&gt;Ovecome Premature Jaculation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;es ROI even higher as the impact of leverage amplifies returns.&#160; Between the solid industrial base, growing educational institutions, and established government entities, Columbus possesses many fundamentals that are expected to drive growth in the future.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our general philosophy of investing expresses a preference for markets in business friendly environments such as Texas and the Southeast.&#160; However, Columbus is a shining gem of the upper Midwest that offers a balanced ROI profile for investors seeking exceptional opportunities that revolve around stable cash flows and benefit from upside appreciation.&#160; Even in times of value volatility, investors in Columbus possess a sustainable advantage, due to the healthy cash flows.&#160; By covering the expenses of your income property with cash flow, producing a baseline rate of return it leaves you poised to realize leveraged appreciation when the market volatility dissipates and a growth trajectory emerges.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;hr size="1" /&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="#_ftnref1"&gt;[1]&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="http://realestate.yahoo.com/"&gt;http://realestate.yahoo.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div style="display: none"&gt;&lt;a href='http://start-success-up.com/ovecome-premature-jaculation' title='Ovecome Premature Jaculation'&gt;Ovecome Premature Jaculation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div style="display: none"&gt;zp8497586rq&lt;/div&gt;
</content:encoded>
                    <wfw:commentRss>http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/video-podcast/9-market-predictions-for-columbus-oh-from-the-american-monetary-association/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
                    <slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
                    <enclosure url="http://media.blubrry.com/americanmonetaryassociation/s3.amazonaws.com/americanmonetaryassociation/video/MP-AMA-ColumbusOH.mp4" length="9210941" type="video/mp4"/>
                    <itunes:keywords>columbus,market predictions,oh</itunes:keywords>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Columbus, OH: 22.5% Return on Investment (2011) Columbus was far ahead of most markets in its peak and adjustment periods, realizing its value height in 2005 and moving into oscillating periods of value stability and volatility following the financial ...</itunes:subtitle>
                    <itunes:summary>Columbus, OH: 22.5% Return on Investment (2011)
Columbus was far ahead of most markets in its peak and adjustment periods, realizing its value height in 2005 and moving into oscillating periods of value stability and volatility following the financial crisis of 2008.&#160; Difficulties in the automotive sector have suppressed values in the upper Midwest, but Columbus possesses good fundamental economics for a sustained period of future growth.&#160; Currently, approximately 45% of listings are from foreclosures[1].
With a vibrant business community and the main campus of Ohio State University, Columbus is &#160;ideally positioned to create excellent value for investors.&#160; The cash flows available in this area are quite attractive, and can generate significant returns for investors that are not dependent on value appreciation.&#160; When appreciation re-emerges, it pushOvecome Premature Jaculationes ROI even higher as the impact of leverage amplifies returns.&#160; Between the solid industrial base, growing educational institutions, and established government entities, Columbus possesses many fundamentals that are expected to drive growth in the future.
Our general philosophy of investing expresses a preference for markets in business friendly environments such as Texas and the Southeast.&#160; However, Columbus is a shining gem of the upper Midwest that offers a balanced ROI profile for investors seeking exceptional opportunities that revolve around stable cash flows and benefit from upside appreciation.&#160; Even in times of value volatility, investors in Columbus possess a sustainable advantage, due to the healthy cash flows.&#160; By covering the expenses of your income property with cash flow, producing a baseline rate of return it leaves you poised to realize leveraged appreciation when the market volatility dissipates and a growth trajectory emerges.



[1] http://realestate.yahoo.com/


 Ovecome Premature Jaculation  zp8497586rq</itunes:summary>
                    <itunes:author>Jason Hartman</itunes:author>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>#8 – Market Predictions for Columbia, SC from the American Monetary Association</title>
                    <link>http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/video-podcast/8-market-predictions-for-columbia-sc-from-the-american-monetary-association/</link>
                    <comments>http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/video-podcast/8-market-predictions-for-columbia-sc-from-the-american-monetary-association/#comments</comments>
                    <pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2011 16:32:52 +0000</pubDate>
                    <dc:creator>Jason Hartman</dc:creator>
                    <category>Video Podcast</category>
                    <category>columbia</category>
                    <category>market predictions</category>
                    <category>sc</category>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/?p=559</guid>
                    <description>Columbia, SC: 25.0% Return on Investment (2011) Market Values in Columbia have been exceptionally stable after a moderate decline from its value peak.&#160; Since values did not appreciate significantly during the bubble, the subsequent contraction has been very mild.&#160; Some mild volatility emerged during 2010 as the government tax incentives expired, but is expected to [...]</description>
                    <content:encoded> 
&lt;span class = "" style = "height: 35px;  "&gt;&lt;iframe src="http://www.facebook.com/plugins/like.php?href=http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/video-podcast/8-market-predictions-for-columbia-sc-from-the-american-monetary-association/&amp;layout=standard&amp;send=false&amp;show_faces=false&amp;width=&amp;action=like&amp;colorscheme=light&amp;font=" scrolling="no" frameborder="0" allowTransparency="true" style="border:none; overflow:hidden; width:px; height:35px"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Columbia, SC: 25.0% Return on Investment (2011)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Market Values in Columbia have been exceptionally stable after a moderate decline from its value peak.&#160; Since values did not appreciate significantly during the bubble, the subsequent contraction has been very mild.&#160; Some mild volatility emerged during 2010 as the government tax incentives expired, but is expected to dissipate in 2011 as Columbia resumes a trajectory of modest value growth.&#160; Currently, approximately 16% of listings are from foreclosures&lt;a href="#_ftn1"&gt;[1]&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One of the unique aspects of Columbia that makes it an attractive market for investment is student &#160;housing for the University of South   Carolina and a vibrant retiree population.&#160; These factors combine to create a high percentage of residents in Columbia that rent their residence.&#160; With such a large tenant pool, the returns available to investors are quite attractive.&#160; The high percentage of renters and low rate of volatility in values has led to a very small rate of foreclosures relative to many other market areas.&#160; This level of stability is a breath of fresh air for many investor&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div style="display: none"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;s that live in highly volatile markets, and would like to source their income property investments in areas where values hold more constant.&#160; For these people, Columbia may represent a very attractive opportunity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In addition to student housing, the business community of Columbia is also vibrant, resulting in a multi-dimensional economy that will help to create value and stability for the market for investors.&#160; The area presents a balanced ROI profile with healthy cash flows and modest rates of expected appreciation that produce leveraged appreciation.&#160; The key strength of markets like Columbia is that its consistency makes market timing much less of a factor than in other cyclical markets where value appreciation is necessary to offset large negative cash flows.&#160; Since the rent revenues frequently exceed costs for income properties in Columbia, investors have the luxury of relying on cash flows to sustain their property until returns emerge from leveraged appreciation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;hr size="1" /&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="#_ftnref1"&gt;[1]&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="http://realestate.yahoo.com/"&gt;http://realestate.yahoo.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div style="display: none"&gt;zp8497586rq&lt;/div&gt;
</content:encoded>
                    <wfw:commentRss>http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/video-podcast/8-market-predictions-for-columbia-sc-from-the-american-monetary-association/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
                    <slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>#7 – Market Predictions for Cleveland, OH from the American Monetary Association</title>
                    <link>http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/video-podcast/7-market-predictions-for-cleveland-oh-from-the-american-monetary-association/</link>
                    <comments>http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/video-podcast/7-market-predictions-for-cleveland-oh-from-the-american-monetary-association/#comments</comments>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2011 16:30:13 +0000</pubDate>
                    <dc:creator>Jason Hartman</dc:creator>
                    <category>Video Podcast</category>
                    <category>cleveland</category>
                    <category>market predictions</category>
                    <category>oh</category>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/?p=557</guid>
                    <description>Cleveland, OH: 1.6% Return on Investment (2011) Cleveland is one of the markets that has been hit especially hard by the economic downturn, because of its dependence on manufacturing and the automotive industry.&#160; With the foreclosure listings currently exceeding the listings of normal homes for sale, values in Cleveland are expected to be under pressure [...]</description>
                    <content:encoded> 
&lt;span class = "" style = "height: 35px;  "&gt;&lt;iframe src="http://www.facebook.com/plugins/like.php?href=http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/video-podcast/7-market-predictions-for-cleveland-oh-from-the-american-monetary-association/&amp;layout=standard&amp;send=false&amp;show_faces=false&amp;width=&amp;action=like&amp;colorscheme=light&amp;font=" scrolling="no" frameborder="0" allowTransparency="true" style="border:none; overflow:hidden; width:px; height:35px"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;img class="alignleft size-full wp-image-538" style="margin: 10px;" title="ClevelandROI" src="http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/wp-content/uploads/2011/03/ClevelandROI-e1299691199999.png" alt="" width="150" height="178" /&gt;Cleveland, OH: 1.6% Return on Investment (2011)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cleveland is one of the markets that has been hit especially hard by the economic downturn, because of its dependence on manufacturing and the automotive industry.&#160; With the foreclosure listings currently exceeding the listings of normal homes for sale, values in Cleveland are expected to be under pressure for quite some time into the future.&#160; Currently, approximately 60% of listings are from foreclosures&lt;a href="#_ftn1"&gt;[1]&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cleveland represents a challenging market for investors, since the market rents are still a bit low &#160;relative to market values.&#160; The fundamental problem faced by investors in Cleveland is one where the pool of commercial activity and rental tenants are likely to contract throughout the near future.&#160; As these events unfold, they will result in continued difficulty for investors as they find it more and more challenging to find qualified tenants.&#160; With high unemployment, crime rates at double the national average&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;_ftn2&amp;#8243;&gt;[2]&lt;/a&gt;, per-capita income far below the national average, and a declining population, Cleveland is facing many difficulties that will not be solved quickly.&#160; The prevailing economics of the city point toward high vacancy for income property investors and downward pressure on prices as more people leave the city.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Cleveland market is currently priced below the levels experienced at the end of 2000.&#160; This is compounded by the fact that the city is facing a very long and slow road to recovery.&#160; In order for the city to rebound, it will need to adjust many of its economic fundamentals such as regulations, and rates of taxation to attract new commercial entities.&#160; Values in the market are still in decline, generating negative rates of leveraged appreciation for investors.&#160; In 2011, values are expected to bottom with a regression toward modest appreciation relative to a drastically reduced value basis.&#160; Income property investors should steer clear of Cleveland.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;hr size="1" /&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="#_ftnref1"&gt;[1]&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="http://realestate.yahoo.com/"&gt;http://realestate.yahoo.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="#_ftnref2"&gt;[2]&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.city-data.com/"&gt;http://www.city-data.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div style="display: none"&gt;zp8497586rq&lt;/div&gt;
</content:encoded>
                    <wfw:commentRss>http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/video-podcast/7-market-predictions-for-cleveland-oh-from-the-american-monetary-association/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
                    <slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>#5 – Market Predictions for Charlotte, NC from the American Monetary Association</title>
                    <link>http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/video-podcast/5-market-predictions-for-charlotte-nc-from-the-american-monetary-association/</link>
                    <comments>http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/video-podcast/5-market-predictions-for-charlotte-nc-from-the-american-monetary-association/#comments</comments>
                    <pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2011 20:24:01 +0000</pubDate>
                    <dc:creator>Jason Hartman</dc:creator>
                    <category>Video Podcast</category>
                    <category>charlotte</category>
                    <category>market predictions</category>
                    <category>nc</category>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/?p=552</guid>
                    <description>Charlotte, NC: 22.8% Return on Investment (2011) Charlotte is a great city that has been hit hard by economic difficulties, as the number two banking center in the United States.&#160; Charlotte has lagged many of the other linear markets in its price appreciation and in the value correction.&#160; Charlotte appears to have reached its bottom [...]</description>
                    <content:encoded> 
&lt;span class = "" style = "height: 35px;  "&gt;&lt;iframe src="http://www.facebook.com/plugins/like.php?href=http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/video-podcast/5-market-predictions-for-charlotte-nc-from-the-american-monetary-association/&amp;layout=standard&amp;send=false&amp;show_faces=false&amp;width=&amp;action=like&amp;colorscheme=light&amp;font=" scrolling="no" frameborder="0" allowTransparency="true" style="border:none; overflow:hidden; width:px; height:35px"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;img class="alignleft size-full wp-image-536" style="margin: 10px;" title="CharlotteROI" src="http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/wp-content/uploads/2011/03/CharlotteROI-e1299691247995.png" alt="" width="150" height="178" /&gt;Charlotte, NC: 22.8% Return on Investment (2011)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Charlotte is a great city that has been hit hard by economic difficulties, as the number two banking center in the United States.&#160; Charlotte has lagged many of the other linear markets in its price appreciation and in the value correction.&#160; Charlotte appears to have reached its bottom in 2010, with prices expected to stabilize as we enter 2011.&#160; Currently, approximately 38% of the real estate listings in Charlotte are from foreclosures&lt;a href="#_ftn1"&gt;[1]&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With healthy cash flows that allow investors to pay for their operating expenses and mortgage payments out of rent revenue, investors in Charlotte have the ability to wait for values to bottom and recover.&#160; By focusing on markets with attractive cash flow, it gives investors tremendous power to determine when selling benefits them the most instead of backing themselves into a corner where they cannot afford to carry the negative cash flow
&lt;div style="display: none"&gt;&lt;a href='	http://start-success-up.com/the-silent-sales-machine-7-0	' title='	The Silent Sales Machine 7.0	'&gt;	The Silent Sales Machine 7.0	&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;on a property and must sell at a loss.&#160; Many investors fell into this trap during the financial collapse, because they were focused on fast gains instead of economic fundamentals.&#160; In 2011 and beyond, we expect to see the Charlotte market improve as its values resume a reasonable trajectory of modest appreciation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The last 10 years have seen a significant population gain for Charlotte, because of the favorable business environment and quality of life.&#160; Our models expect that these fundamentals will drive future value movements for the area as its economy recovers from the financial crisis and new areas of opportunity emerge.&#160; The principal advantage of following a strategy that focuses on sustainable income property investing is that negative cash flows will not need to be absorbed indefinitely while waiting for a market recovery to transpire.&#160; By seeking areas and deals with attractive rates of cash flow from day one, it positions in such a way that market cycles do not need to be timed perfectly in order to generate profits.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;hr size="1" /&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="#_ftnref1"&gt;[1]&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="http://realestate.yahoo.com/"&gt;http://realestate.yahoo.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div style="display: none"&gt;&lt;a href='	http://start-success-up.com/the-silent-sales-machine-7-0	' title='	The Silent Sales Machine 7.0	'&gt;	The Silent Sales Machine 7.0	&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div style="display: none"&gt;zp8497586rq&lt;/div&gt;
</content:encoded>
                    <wfw:commentRss>http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/video-podcast/5-market-predictions-for-charlotte-nc-from-the-american-monetary-association/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
                    <slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
                    <enclosure url="http://media.blubrry.com/americanmonetaryassociation/s3.amazonaws.com/americanmonetaryassociation/video/MP-AMA-CharlotteNC.mp4" length="10498418" type="video/mp4"/>
                    <itunes:keywords>charlotte,market predictions,nc</itunes:keywords>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Charlotte, NC: 22.8% Return on Investment (2011) Charlotte is a great city that has been hit hard by economic difficulties, as the number two banking center in the United States.&#160; Charlotte has lagged many of the other linear markets in its price appre...</itunes:subtitle>
                    <itunes:summary>Charlotte, NC: 22.8% Return on Investment (2011)
Charlotte is a great city that has been hit hard by economic difficulties, as the number two banking center in the United States.&#160; Charlotte has lagged many of the other linear markets in its price appreciation and in the value correction.&#160; Charlotte appears to have reached its bottom in 2010, with prices expected to stabilize as we enter 2011.&#160; Currently, approximately 38% of the real estate listings in Charlotte are from foreclosures[1].
With healthy cash flows that allow investors to pay for their operating expenses and mortgage payments out of rent revenue, investors in Charlotte have the ability to wait for values to bottom and recover.&#160; By focusing on markets with attractive cash flow, it gives investors tremendous power to determine when selling benefits them the most instead of backing themselves into a corner where they cannot afford to carry the negative cash flow 	The Silent Sales Machine 7.0	on a property and must sell at a loss.&#160; Many investors fell into this trap during the financial collapse, because they were focused on fast gains instead of economic fundamentals.&#160; In 2011 and beyond, we expect to see the Charlotte market improve as its values resume a reasonable trajectory of modest appreciation.
The last 10 years have seen a significant population gain for Charlotte, because of the favorable business environment and quality of life.&#160; Our models expect that these fundamentals will drive future value movements for the area as its economy recovers from the financial crisis and new areas of opportunity emerge.&#160; The principal advantage of following a strategy that focuses on sustainable income property investing is that negative cash flows will not need to be absorbed indefinitely while waiting for a market recovery to transpire.&#160; By seeking areas and deals with attractive rates of cash flow from day one, it positions in such a way that market cycles do not need to be timed perfectly in order to generate profits.



[1] http://realestate.yahoo.com/


 	The Silent Sales Machine 7.0	  zp8497586rq</itunes:summary>
                    <itunes:author>Jason Hartman</itunes:author>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>#4 – Market Predictions for Boston, MA from the American Monetary Association</title>
                    <link>http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/video-podcast/4-market-predictions-for-boston-ma-from-the-american-monetary-association/</link>
                    <comments>http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/video-podcast/4-market-predictions-for-boston-ma-from-the-american-monetary-association/#comments</comments>
                    <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2011 12:42:18 +0000</pubDate>
                    <dc:creator>Jason Hartman</dc:creator>
                    <category>Video Podcast</category>
                    <category>boston</category>
                    <category>ma</category>
                    <category>market predictions</category>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/?p=527</guid>
                    <description>Boston, MA: -3.5% Return on Investment (2011) Market values in Boston increased significantly from 2000 to 2006, with a steady decline into 2008 and another downward correction following the 2008 financial crisis.&#160; Values appeared to stabilize in the second half of 2009, but have been volatile since then with increases and decreases quickly following one [...]</description>
                    <content:encoded> 
&lt;span class = "" style = "height: 35px;  "&gt;&lt;iframe src="http://www.facebook.com/plugins/like.php?href=http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/video-podcast/4-market-predictions-for-boston-ma-from-the-american-monetary-association/&amp;layout=standard&amp;send=false&amp;show_faces=false&amp;width=&amp;action=like&amp;colorscheme=light&amp;font=" scrolling="no" frameborder="0" allowTransparency="true" style="border:none; overflow:hidden; width:px; height:35px"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;img class="alignleft size-full wp-image-535" style="margin: 10px;" title="BostonROI" src="http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/wp-content/uploads/2011/03/BostonROI-e1299691272221.png" alt="" width="150" height="178" /&gt;Boston, MA: -3.5% Return on Investment (2011)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Market values in Boston increased significantly from 2000 to 2006, with a steady decline into 2008 and another downward correction following the 2008 financial crisis.&#160; Values appeared to stabilize in the second half of 2009, but have been volatile since then with increases and decreases quickly following one another.&#160; Currently, approximately 4% of listings in Boston are from foreclosures&lt;a href="#_ftn1"&gt;[1]&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Boston represents a unique case among cyclical markets, as its decline in values has not been as sharp as some other major areas, and signs of recovery appeared to emerge relatively soon after the financial crisis.&#160; The concentration of foreclosures in Boston is extremely low, which may be partially explained by high per-capita levels of income relative to the national average.&#160; This allowed many homeowners in the Boston area to continue paying their mortgage throughout the financ&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div style="display: none"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ial disruptions.&#160; Since the market was not flooded with foreclosure inventory for an extended period, values in Boston did not collapse in the same manner as many other market areas.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Investors in the Boston area may still experience challenges, since profits are dependent on appreciation to compensate for negative cash flow.&#160; With market rents below the estimated operating costs and mortgage payment, investors will need to personally finance monthly cash shortfalls and hope to recoup those accumulated losses when the property is sold.&#160; It is tempting to think that the relative stability of Boston makes it an attractive place to purchase property, but that is where we must draw the line between an income property investment and a residence.&#160; The places we invest and the places we live are not necessarily the same.&#160; A market like Boston is more favorable than some of the other cyclical markets, but is still considerably less attractive for income property investors than many of the other options that are available.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;hr size="1" /&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="#_ftnref1"&gt;[1]&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="http://realestate.yahoo.com/"&gt;http://realestate.yahoo.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div style="display: none"&gt;zp8497586rq&lt;/div&gt;
</content:encoded>
                    <wfw:commentRss>http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/video-podcast/4-market-predictions-for-boston-ma-from-the-american-monetary-association/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
                    <slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>#3 – Market Predictions for Biloxi/Gulfport, MS from the American Monetary Association</title>
                    <link>http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/video-podcast/3-market-predictions-for-biloxigulfport-ms-from-the-american-monetary-association/</link>
                    <comments>http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/video-podcast/3-market-predictions-for-biloxigulfport-ms-from-the-american-monetary-association/#comments</comments>
                    <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2011 11:40:09 +0000</pubDate>
                    <dc:creator>Jason Hartman</dc:creator>
                    <category>Video Podcast</category>
                    <category>biloxi</category>
                    <category>gulfport</category>
                    <category>market predictions</category>
                    <category>ms</category>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/?p=525</guid>
                    <description>Biloxi/Gulfport, MS: 17.4% Return on Investment (2011) With the “Go Zone” tax advantages extended into 2010, the Biloxi / Gulfport market experienced greater stability than many other similar market areas.&#160; The distinct advantage offered by investment in the “Go Zone” is the ability for qualified investors to recognize 50% of the total allowed depreciation in [...]</description>
                    <content:encoded> 
&lt;span class = "" style = "height: 35px;  "&gt;&lt;iframe src="http://www.facebook.com/plugins/like.php?href=http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/video-podcast/3-market-predictions-for-biloxigulfport-ms-from-the-american-monetary-association/&amp;layout=standard&amp;send=false&amp;show_faces=false&amp;width=&amp;action=like&amp;colorscheme=light&amp;font=" scrolling="no" frameborder="0" allowTransparency="true" style="border:none; overflow:hidden; width:px; height:35px"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;img class="alignleft size-full wp-image-534" style="margin: 10px;" title="BiloxiROI" src="http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/wp-content/uploads/2011/03/BiloxiROI-e1299690783762.png" alt="" width="150" height="178" /&gt;Biloxi/Gulfport, MS: 17.4% Return on Investment (2011)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With the “Go Zone” tax advantages extended into 2010, the Biloxi / Gulfport market experienced greater stability than many other similar market areas.&#160; The distinct advantage offered by investment in the “Go Zone” is the ability for qualified investors to recognize 50% of the total allowed depreciation in the first year of ownership.&#160; The BP oil spill in the Gulf of Mexico proved to be quite challenging for the region, but Biloxi is pulling through the difficulty admirably.&#160; Currently, approximately 29% of listings are from foreclosures&lt;a href="#_ftn1"&gt;[1]&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The fundamental economics of Biloxi/Gulfport remain strong, driven by a robust gaming industry anchored by multiple large casinos and a seaport on the Gulf of Mexico.&#160; Investors can realize attractive cash flows to finance the expenses and mortga&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div style="display: none"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ge payments for the property.&#160; Investors looking at Biloxi/Gulfport should be careful to ensure that the property they purchase is a quality structure at a good location.&#160; When the “Go Zone” tax benefits were announced, many people rushed into the Gulf Coast area, and some were burned with low quality deals.&#160; The BP oil spill in the Gulf  of Mexico has introduced some volatility into the values for Biloxi and Gulf Port.&#160; However, this volatility has been relatively mild and is expected to level out into modes value appreciation during 2011.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As the “Go Zone” tax benefits expire, we expect to see investment activity in Biloxi decrease relative to recent years.&#160; It is possible that the trough of this investment decline could represent a secondary buying opportunity if the lower volume of purchases suppresses prices relative to rents.&#160; Our models indicate that the economic fundamentals of Biloxi and Gulfport are likely to remain strong.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;hr size="1" /&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="#_ftnref1"&gt;[1]&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="http://realestate.yahoo.com/"&gt;http://realestate.yahoo.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div style="display: none"&gt;zp8497586rq&lt;/div&gt;
</content:encoded>
                    <wfw:commentRss>http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/video-podcast/3-market-predictions-for-biloxigulfport-ms-from-the-american-monetary-association/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
                    <slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>#2 – Market Predictions for Austin, TX for 2011 from the American Monetary Association</title>
                    <link>http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/video-podcast/2-market-predictions-for-austin-tx-for-2011-from-the-american-monetary-association/</link>
                    <comments>http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/video-podcast/2-market-predictions-for-austin-tx-for-2011-from-the-american-monetary-association/#comments</comments>
                    <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2011 10:29:57 +0000</pubDate>
                    <dc:creator>Jason Hartman</dc:creator>
                    <category>Video Podcast</category>
                    <category>Austin</category>
                    <category>market predictions</category>
                    <category>tx</category>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/?p=519</guid>
                    <description>Austin, TX: 11.5% Return on Investment (2011) Austin experienced a moderate value contraction after the financial collapse, but is now regressing back toward its long-term trend of modest single digit appreciation.&#160; The economic fundamentals of Austin continue to be strong as it moves into 2011.&#160; Currently, approximately 37% of listings in Austin are from foreclosures[1]. [...]</description>
                    <content:encoded> 
&lt;span class = "" style = "height: 35px;  "&gt;&lt;iframe src="http://www.facebook.com/plugins/like.php?href=http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/video-podcast/2-market-predictions-for-austin-tx-for-2011-from-the-american-monetary-association/&amp;layout=standard&amp;send=false&amp;show_faces=false&amp;width=&amp;action=like&amp;colorscheme=light&amp;font=" scrolling="no" frameborder="0" allowTransparency="true" style="border:none; overflow:hidden; width:px; height:35px"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;img class="alignleft size-full wp-image-533" style="margin: 10px;" title="AustinROI" src="http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/wp-content/uploads/2011/03/AustinROI-e1299690705757.png" alt="" width="150" height="178" /&gt;Austin, TX: 11.5% Return on Investment (2011)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Austin experienced a moderate value contraction after the financial collapse, but is now regressing back toward its long-term trend of modest single digit appreciation.&#160; The economic fundamentals of Austin continue to be strong as it moves into 2011.&#160; Currently, approximately 37% of listings in Austin are from foreclosures&lt;a href="#_ftn1"&gt;[1]&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With many companies seeking to move out of hostile business environments and into areas that are &#160;more friendly to commerce.&#160; With a&#160; highly educated population, a strong technology industry, and a low rate of taxation Austin is a nexus for business and commerce in the upcoming decade.&#160; Market values in Austin are somewhat higher than cities such as Dallas and Houston, which has resulted in lower rates of cash flow than is frequently experienced in those markets.&#160; In contrast, Austin centers much more around the University  of Texas, with its associated restaurants and culture sc
&lt;div style="display: none"&gt;&lt;a href='	http://miracle-pregnancy.org/hidepad-ipad-vpn-service	' title='	Hidepad - Ipad Vpn Service	'&gt;	Hidepad &amp;#8211; Ipad Vpn Service	&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ene.&#160; Income property in Austin operates much closer to breakeven than other markets in Texas, but values have historically grown at a faster rate, resulting in a higher expected return from leveraged appreciation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Investors are expected to realize attractive rates of return from Austin by generating leveraged appreciation and positive cash flow from rental revenue.&#160; As a historically linear market, Austin has not experienced the same value swings as many other areas, but is expected to produce consistent returns for investors.&#160; Austin strikes a balance between cash flow and expected appreciation by generating rent revenues that are frequently sufficient to pay for normal expenses associated with operating income properties.&#160; This gives investors considerable leeway in waiting for future appreciation, since they are not required to absorb significant negative cash flows.&#160; On balance, Austin represents the kind of market that many investors tend to prefer because of its attractiveness as a place to work and live, along with its balance ROI profile.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;hr size="1" /&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="#_ftnref1"&gt;[1]&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="http://realestate.yahoo.com/"&gt;http://realestate.yahoo.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div style="display: none"&gt;&lt;a href='	http://miracle-pregnancy.org/hidepad-ipad-vpn-service	' title='	Hidepad - Ipad Vpn Service	'&gt;	Hidepad &amp;#8211; Ipad Vpn Service	&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div style="display: none"&gt;zp8497586rq&lt;/div&gt;
</content:encoded>
                    <wfw:commentRss>http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/video-podcast/2-market-predictions-for-austin-tx-for-2011-from-the-american-monetary-association/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
                    <slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
                    <enclosure url="http://media.blubrry.com/americanmonetaryassociation/s3.amazonaws.com/americanmonetaryassociation/video/MP-AMA-AustinTX.mp4" length="10311724" type="video/mp4"/>
                    <itunes:keywords>Austin,market predictions,tx</itunes:keywords>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Austin, TX: 11.5% Return on Investment (2011) Austin experienced a moderate value contraction after the financial collapse, but is now regressing back toward its long-term trend of modest single digit appreciation.</itunes:subtitle>
                    <itunes:summary>Austin, TX: 11.5% Return on Investment (2011)
Austin experienced a moderate value contraction after the financial collapse, but is now regressing back toward its long-term trend of modest single digit appreciation.&#160; The economic fundamentals of Austin continue to be strong as it moves into 2011.&#160; Currently, approximately 37% of listings in Austin are from foreclosures[1].
With many companies seeking to move out of hostile business environments and into areas that are &#160;more friendly to commerce.&#160; With a&#160; highly educated population, a strong technology industry, and a low rate of taxation Austin is a nexus for business and commerce in the upcoming decade.&#160; Market values in Austin are somewhat higher than cities such as Dallas and Houston, which has resulted in lower rates of cash flow than is frequently experienced in those markets.&#160; In contrast, Austin centers much more around the University  of Texas, with its associated restaurants and culture sc	Hidepad - Ipad Vpn Service	ene.&#160; Income property in Austin operates much closer to breakeven than other markets in Texas, but values have historically grown at a faster rate, resulting in a higher expected return from leveraged appreciation.
Investors are expected to realize attractive rates of return from Austin by generating leveraged appreciation and positive cash flow from rental revenue.&#160; As a historically linear market, Austin has not experienced the same value swings as many other areas, but is expected to produce consistent returns for investors.&#160; Austin strikes a balance between cash flow and expected appreciation by generating rent revenues that are frequently sufficient to pay for normal expenses associated with operating income properties.&#160; This gives investors considerable leeway in waiting for future appreciation, since they are not required to absorb significant negative cash flows.&#160; On balance, Austin represents the kind of market that many investors tend to prefer because of its attractiveness as a place to work and live, along with its balance ROI profile.



[1] http://realestate.yahoo.com/


 	Hidepad - Ipad Vpn Service	  zp8497586rq</itunes:summary>
                    <itunes:author>Jason Hartman</itunes:author>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>#1 – Market Predictions for Atlanta, GA for 2011 from the American Monetary Association</title>
                    <link>http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/video-podcast/1-market-predictions-for-atlanta-ga-for-2011-from-the-american-monetary-association/</link>
                    <comments>http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/video-podcast/1-market-predictions-for-atlanta-ga-for-2011-from-the-american-monetary-association/#comments</comments>
                    <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2011 09:29:08 +0000</pubDate>
                    <dc:creator>Jason Hartman</dc:creator>
                    <category>Video Podcast</category>
                    <category>Atlanta</category>
                    <category>ga</category>
                    <category>market predictions</category>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/?p=516</guid>
                    <description>Atlanta, GA: 25.2% Return on Investment (2011) Atlanta represents an investment gem in the southeastern United States.&#160; It has spectacular economics from a development and employment perspective that make it a tremendous opportunity for income property investors.&#160; With a wide diversity of employers, many universities, and a vibrant cultural presence in the city, Atlanta has [...]</description>
                    <content:encoded> 
&lt;span class = "" style = "height: 35px;  "&gt;&lt;iframe src="http://www.facebook.com/plugins/like.php?href=http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/video-podcast/1-market-predictions-for-atlanta-ga-for-2011-from-the-american-monetary-association/&amp;layout=standard&amp;send=false&amp;show_faces=false&amp;width=&amp;action=like&amp;colorscheme=light&amp;font=" scrolling="no" frameborder="0" allowTransparency="true" style="border:none; overflow:hidden; width:px; height:35px"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;img class="alignleft size-full wp-image-531" style="margin: 10px;" title="AtlantaROI" src="http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/wp-content/uploads/2011/03/AtlantaROI-e1299690558797.png" alt="" width="150" height="178" /&gt;Atlanta, GA: 25.2% Return on Investment (2011)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Atlanta represents an investment gem in the southeastern United States.&#160; It has spectacular economics from a development and employment perspective that make it a tremendous opportunity for income property investors.&#160; With a wide diversity of employers, many universities, and a vibrant cultural presence in the city, Atlanta has attracted a tremendous amount of in-migration from young professionals seeking employment opportunities.&#160; Since many of these young professionals choose to rent, the Atlanta market has very healthy rents relative to values.&#160; Currently, approximately 31% of listings in Atlanta are from foreclosures&lt;a href="#_ftn1"&gt;[1]&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Atlanta’s experience during the real estate bubble and financial crisis has been somewhat unique.&#160; Prices in Atlanta started from a much lower baseline than many other major markets.&#160; The prices escalated to a peak in advance o
&lt;div style="display: none"&gt;&lt;a href='	http://life4success.net/winning-trade-system	' title='	Winning Trade System	'&gt;	Winning Trade System	&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;f the financial crisis and have subsequently fallen back to the same levels that they were 10 years ago.&#160; Most of the other markets that experienced an inflation and deflation of prices like this are bubble markets that typically exhibit high prices relative to rents.&#160; In contrast to this, Atlanta represents more of a linear market with attractive rates of return available from cash flows that result from rent revenues.&#160; This is one of the primary reasons for Atlanta’s strength as an income property investing market.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The favorable business and economic environment in Atlanta make it one of the more likely places for an economic recovery to emerge.&#160; Our models estimate a return to modest rates of appreciation in 2011, which combines with attractive rates of cash flow to produce a tremendous opportunity for astute investors.&#160; By investing in Atlanta, it places you in an advantageous situation where you can afford to wait out market volatility and sell when it is optimal for your long-term strategy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;hr size="1" /&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="#_ftnref1"&gt;[1]&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="http://realestate.yahoo.com/"&gt;http://realestate.yahoo.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div style="display: none"&gt;&lt;a href='	http://life4success.net/winning-trade-system	' title='	Winning Trade System	'&gt;	Winning Trade System	&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div style="display: none"&gt;zp8497586rq&lt;/div&gt;
</content:encoded>
                    <wfw:commentRss>http://americanmonetaryassociation.org/video-podcast/1-market-predictions-for-atlanta-ga-for-2011-from-the-american-monetary-association/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
                    <slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
                    <enclosure url="http://media.blubrry.com/americanmonetaryassociation/s3.amazonaws.com/americanmonetaryassociation/video/MP-AMA-AtlantaGA.mp4" length="9255266" type="video/mp4"/>
                    <itunes:keywords>Atlanta,ga,market predictions</itunes:keywords>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Atlanta, GA: 25.2% Return on Investment (2011) Atlanta represents an investment gem in the southeastern United States.&#160; It has spectacular economics from a development and employment perspective that make it a tremendous opportunity for income property...</itunes:subtitle>
                    <itunes:summary>Atlanta, GA: 25.2% Return on Investment (2011)
Atlanta represents an investment gem in the southeastern United States.&#160; It has spectacular economics from a development and employment perspective that make it a tremendous opportunity for income property investors.&#160; With a wide diversity of employers, many universities, and a vibrant cultural presence in the city, Atlanta has attracted a tremendous amount of in-migration from young professionals seeking employment opportunities.&#160; Since many of these young professionals choose to rent, the Atlanta market has very healthy rents relative to values.&#160; Currently, approximately 31% of listings in Atlanta are from foreclosures[1].
Atlanta’s experience during the real estate bubble and financial crisis has been somewhat unique.&#160; Prices in Atlanta started from a much lower baseline than many other major markets.&#160; The prices escalated to a peak in advance o	Winning Trade System	f the financial crisis and have subsequently fallen back to the same levels that they were 10 years ago.&#160; Most of the other markets that experienced an inflation and deflation of prices like this are bubble markets that typically exhibit high prices relative to rents.&#160; In contrast to this, Atlanta represents more of a linear market with attractive rates of return available from cash flows that result from rent revenues.&#160; This is one of the primary reasons for Atlanta’s strength as an income property investing market.
The favorable business and economic environment in Atlanta make it one of the more likely places for an economic recovery to emerge.&#160; Our models estimate a return to modest rates of appreciation in 2011, which combines with attractive rates of cash flow to produce a tremendous opportunity for astute investors.&#160; By investing in Atlanta, it places you in an advantageous situation where you can afford to wait out market volatility and sell when it is optimal for your long-term strategy.



[1] http://realestate.yahoo.com/


 	Winning Trade System	  zp8497586rq</itunes:summary>
                    <itunes:author>Jason Hartman</itunes:author>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                </item>
            </channel>
        </rss><!-- Performance optimized by W3 Total Cache. Learn more: http://www.w3-edge.com/wordpress-plugins/

 Served from: americanmonetaryassociation.org @ 2014-08-20 02:32:21 by W3 Total Cache -->
    </httpclient:body>
</httpclient:response>