<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<httpclient:response xmlns:httpclient="http://exist-db.org/xquery/httpclient" statusCode="200">
    <httpclient:headers>
        <httpclient:header name="Server" value="Apache/2.2.22 (Ubuntu)"/>
        <httpclient:header name="X-Libsyn-Host" value="web-engine3.libsyn.com"/>
        <httpclient:header name="Vary" value="Accept-Encoding"/>
        <httpclient:header name="Content-Type" value="application/rss+xml"/>
        <httpclient:header name="last-modified" value="Thu, 14 Aug 2014 07:40:06 GMT"/>
        <httpclient:header name="Content-Length" value="69314"/>
        <httpclient:header name="Accept-Ranges" value="bytes"/>
        <httpclient:header name="Date" value="Wed, 20 Aug 2014 09:17:48 GMT"/>
        <httpclient:header name="X-Varnish" value="2975473870 2922451065"/>
        <httpclient:header name="Age" value="524803"/>
        <httpclient:header name="Via" value="1.1 varnish"/>
        <httpclient:header name="Connection" value="close"/>
        <httpclient:header name="X-Cache" value="HIT"/>
    </httpclient:headers>
    <httpclient:body mimetype="application/rss+xml" type="xml">
        <rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:cc="http://web.resource.org/cc/" version="2.0">
            <channel>
                <atom:link href="http://aciworldwide.libsyn.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
                <title>ACI Worldwide Podcast Series</title>
                <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2014 21:05:58 +0000</pubDate>
                <lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2014 07:40:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
                <generator>Libsyn WebEngine 2.0</generator>
                <link>http://www.aciworldwide.com</link>
                <language>en</language>
                <copyright>ACI Worldwide</copyright>
                <docs>http://www.aciworldwide.com</docs>
                <managingEditor>andrew.cox@aciworldwide.com (andrew.cox@aciworldwide.com)</managingEditor>
                <description>ACI Worldwide powers electronic payments, enabling $13 trillion in payments each day, processing transactions for more than 250 of the leading global retailers, and 21 of the world’s 25 largest banks.</description>
                <image>
                    <url>http://assets.libsyn.com/content/6824810.jpg</url>
                    <title>ACI Worldwide Podcast Series</title>
                    <link>http://www.aciworldwide.com</link>
                </image>
                <itunes:author>ACI Worldwide</itunes:author>
                <itunes:keywords>atm,bank,banking,bankingtechnology,electronic,financial,global,mobile,payment,payments,paymentsystems,platforms,regulations,retail,services,transactions,wholesale</itunes:keywords>
                <itunes:category text="Technology">
                    <itunes:category text="Podcasting"/>
                </itunes:category>
                <itunes:category text="Business">
                    <itunes:category text="Business News"/>
                </itunes:category>
                <itunes:category text="Technology"/>
                <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/6824810.jpg"/>
                <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
                <itunes:owner>
                    <itunes:name>ACI Worldwide</itunes:name>
                    <itunes:email>andrew.cox@aciworldwide.com</itunes:email>
                </itunes:owner>
                <itunes:summary>ACI Worldwide powers electronic payments for financial institutions, retailers and processors around the world with its broad and integrated suite of electronic payment software.</itunes:summary>
                <itunes:subtitle>ACI Worldwide: The Leader in Universal Payments</itunes:subtitle>
                <item>
                    <title>Utility Provider LCEC Saves $3M a Year with ACI Solutions</title>
                    <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2014 21:05:58 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">3608cb1e33bc793d1a7cc052d5f3523f</guid>
                    <link>http://aciworldwide.libsyn.com/utility-provider-lcec-saves-3m-a-year-with-aci-solutions</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/7175571"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: arial, sans, sans-serif; font-size: 13px; font-weight: bold;"&gt;ACI Worldwide software powers electronic transactions for financial institutions, processors and retailers around the world - all the time, without fail. Learn more:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a style="color: #1155cc; font-family: arial, sans, sans-serif; font-size: 13px; font-weight: bold;" href="http://www.aciworldwide.com/" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.aciworldwide.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="yj6qo ajU" style="cursor: pointer; outline: none; padding: 10px 0px; width: 22px; font-family: arial, sans, sans-serif; font-size: 13px; font-weight: bold;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="2192531" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/aciworldwide/Utility_Provider_LCEC_Saves_3M_a_Year_with_ACI_Solutions.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>02:17</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>ACI Worldwide software powers electronic transactions for financial institutions, processors and retailers around the world - all the time, without fail. Learn more:http://www.aciworldwide.com
&amp;nbsp;</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Leveraging the post-Sepa environment</title>
                    <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2014 20:08:38 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">c3d6d44372bf085aa354f8e8e74dafae</guid>
                    <link>http://aciworldwide.libsyn.com/leveraging-the-post-sepa-environment</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/7162927"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;ACI Worldwide software powers electronic transactions for financial institutions, processors and retailers around the world - all the time, without fail. Learn more: http://www.aciworldwide.com&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="2033079" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/aciworldwide/Leveraging_the_post-Sepa_environment.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>04:14</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords>payments,worldwide,sepa,aci</itunes:keywords>
                    <itunes:subtitle>ACI Worldwide software powers electronic transactions for financial institutions, processors and retailers around the world - all the time, without fail. Learn more: http://www.aciworldwide.com</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Payment Switching Investment ROI- Ovum Market Update and Vendor Review</title>
                    <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2014 18:44:32 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">2ac5664abd8e5a910ed460f2602847c1</guid>
                    <link>http://aciworldwide.libsyn.com/payment-switching-investment-roi-ovum-market-update-and-vendor-review</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/7162396"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;ACI Worldwide software powers electronic transactions for financial institutions, processors and retailers around the world - all the time, without fail. Learn more: http://www.aciworldwide.com&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="25081648" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/aciworldwide/Payment_Switching_Investment_ROI-_Ovum_Market_Update_and_Vendor_Review.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>52:15</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords>update,payments,market,worldwide,ovum,aci</itunes:keywords>
                    <itunes:subtitle>ACI Worldwide software powers electronic transactions for financial institutions, processors and retailers around the world - all the time, without fail. Learn more: http://www.aciworldwide.com</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Take Advantage of the Evolving Nordic Issuing Market</title>
                    <pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2014 15:31:48 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">62b7a5d58abbfdb925f65b581100cc93</guid>
                    <link>http://aciworldwide.libsyn.com/take-advantage-of-the-evolving-nordic-issuing-market</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/7100957"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Today you are going to look at-take advantage of-the evolving Nordic issuing markets for banks and other financial institutions in our various markets. So, lets go ahead with that. So, we are going to cover 5 areas in this webinar. First we are going to look at some trends in Europe, then, we are going to look at the Nordic trends. The challenge in this issue is in the Nordic trends, which is a combination of both the trends that are affecting them and some potential strategies for success. And then lastly we are going to tell you is about ACI, which, my colleague, Fredrick Rotvolnoph will do.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, payment for a long while didn't see a great deal of innovation in terms of these magnetic stripe card move to chip in the 90's. But really, from there, and online started, but really it's since 2000 that a number of new players have entered the market. So this slide is to show that the banking and payments landscape is now changing at a great pace. Increasing consumer demands for quick and easy access to accounts via mobile, the web, etc, have lead to a greater reliance on technology for banks and consequently, innovation such as mobile and e-commerce are developing at a faster rate than the traditional card brace systems. New players, new devices, and new channels will all challenge these traditional payment methods. This is an exciting time for the industry.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;However, the increasing consumer demands for speed and easy use in the finance sector is putting banks under a great deal of pressure. Banks are required to ensure that N-commerce and e-commerce transactions run seamlessly and are secure. All the while, facing growing competition from new banks and new payment institutions which are now allowed under the regulation that's in place - and more on regulation later-and also new players, be these retailers also taking banking licenses, new banks and Metro Bank in the U.K. are an example of this and ING direct, and corporates such as Google, Facebook and Paypal. And most banks perceive these as the biggest threats to their business because they don't have the system limitations and legacy systems that banks have, and so can produce innovative offerings quite quickly. I mean, an example of that is the Google Wallet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, these are the trends that are shaping payments in Europe. And these are a subset really of what I mentioned earlier in the global system. So, take for example, we have already spoken about new competitors, and some of the examples are there. Regulation is increasingly shaping payments and we will discuss that in a bit more detail later. Price pressure which comes in two-fold, one in terms of the customer will require some incentive to take up a new technology, and also reductions in interchange. And we are seeing consolidation in the marketplace with banks joining together and also, aquirerers, PSP's and processors coming together. NFC is still in the marketplace, and has really been the coming next big thing for about 5 years now. It's still likely to come soon. I think it's being moved forward perhaps a bit more slowly than most players wanted. The smart phone has developed and the e-wallet is an integral part of things going forward.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;However, again, there is some discrepancy there. Visa and Mastercard both have a wallet, so do different retailers and so does Google, and really the concern here is for the customer, in terms of how many wallets will the customer actually want? And what will he want in his wallets? And how will this work? So, will he want loyalty cards, his bank card, his credit card, and more particularly how does he decide which card to use in each case with the wallet. So the customer wants to work in a multi-channel environment now. He wants, in some situations, to still use the card, he wants, in some situations, to pay by cash, and even in some markets, check. Any player now has to offer a multiple part of channels to the customer base. There is still pressure to reduce fraud in Europe. EMV was a tremendous success when it was implemented, but it was designed for the face to face environment. And there will be new challenges, and we've seen when internet banking came along, and internet shopping came along, the frauds took advantage of the weakness that was perceived there, which, had to be addressed by particular codes and etc.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="40254821" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/aciworldwide/Take_Advantage_of_the_Evolving_Nordic_Issuing_Market.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>41:56</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>This webinar discusses Nordic trends in issuing markets for banks and other financial institutions and some potential strategies for success. http://www.aciworldwide.com/</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Mobile Fraud Alerts- Improve Customer Service and Fraud Operations</title>
                    <pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2014 15:23:51 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">949ef467159aa65d37f3afedc5212249</guid>
                    <link>http://aciworldwide.libsyn.com/mobile-fraud-alerts-improve-customer-service-and-fraud-operations</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/7100909"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #333333; font-family: arial, sans-serif; font-size: 13.333333969116211px; line-height: 17px;"&gt;Today we're going to give you some background on Spectrum and ACI's relationship with Spectrum. We're going to talk a little bit about the market insight on how mobile alerting affects consumer relationships with their banks and issuers. We're going to cover some practical applications of ACI mobile alerting with the various ACI solutions, and we're going to cover off some real world examples of how global institutions have successfully deployed the solutions and some results related. At the end we'll spend some time for some Q&amp;amp;A.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br style="color: #333333; font-family: arial, sans-serif; font-size: 13.333333969116211px; line-height: 17px;" /&gt;&lt;br style="color: #333333; font-family: arial, sans-serif; font-size: 13.333333969116211px; line-height: 17px;" /&gt;&lt;span style="color: #333333; font-family: arial, sans-serif; font-size: 13.333333969116211px; line-height: 17px;"&gt;So, first up, I wanted to spend a moment to talk a little bit about Spectrum Message Services. Specializing in flow-driven financial and telecom traffic, they are a technology company that offers several solutions including MoneyGuard SMS and Mobile payments platform, their Technocall IVR and Call Centre solution, and Floware SOA business process management solution. ACI mobile alerting solution is powered by their MoneyGuard solution.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br style="color: #333333; font-family: arial, sans-serif; font-size: 13.333333969116211px; line-height: 17px;" /&gt;&lt;br style="color: #333333; font-family: arial, sans-serif; font-size: 13.333333969116211px; line-height: 17px;" /&gt;&lt;span style="color: #333333; font-family: arial, sans-serif; font-size: 13.333333969116211px; line-height: 17px;"&gt;Spectrum has been around for ten years. They originally started in Hungary in 1993, and now also have offices in Australia. The relationship between Spectrum and ACI dates back to 1999 when Spectrum first integrated its MoneyGuard mobile alerting solution on the Base24 payments platform at OTP Bank in Hungary.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br style="color: #333333; font-family: arial, sans-serif; font-size: 13.333333969116211px; line-height: 17px;" /&gt;&lt;br style="color: #333333; font-family: arial, sans-serif; font-size: 13.333333969116211px; line-height: 17px;" /&gt;&lt;span style="color: #333333; font-family: arial, sans-serif; font-size: 13.333333969116211px; line-height: 17px;"&gt;We then also started working with them on our payments risk management solution, Proactive Risk Manager, in 2006 at that same entity. In 2008 we entered a formal partnership with them in the Amir region, and then expanded that to include offerings in the Americas and Asia Pacific as well.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br style="color: #333333; font-family: arial, sans-serif; font-size: 13.333333969116211px; line-height: 17px;" /&gt;&lt;br style="color: #333333; font-family: arial, sans-serif; font-size: 13.333333969116211px; line-height: 17px;" /&gt;&lt;span style="color: #333333; font-family: arial, sans-serif; font-size: 13.333333969116211px; line-height: 17px;"&gt;I'm going to move on to a little bit of market information related to mobile alerting from a fraud and consumer service perspective. Last year, ACI embarked on a third global card fraud study. We surveyed 5,200 consumers in 17 countries around the world. We teamed with U.S.-based analyst research firm, AITE, to interpret and report on the findings, and publish a formal report.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br style="color: #333333; font-family: arial, sans-serif; font-size: 13.333333969116211px; line-height: 17px;" /&gt;&lt;br style="color: #333333; font-family: arial, sans-serif; font-size: 13.333333969116211px; line-height: 17px;" /&gt;&lt;span style="color: #333333; font-family: arial, sans-serif; font-size: 13.333333969116211px; line-height: 17px;"&gt;The result is a comprehensive picture of consumer attitudes and experiences with credit, debit, and other forms of card fraud. We conducted the survey last year to help our banking and retail clients better understand what consumers think about fraud, their experiences with fraud, and to help them understand the impact fraud has on existing and future relationships with the financial institutions.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br style="color: #333333; font-family: arial, sans-serif; font-size: 13.333333969116211px; line-height: 17px;" /&gt;&lt;br style="color: #333333; font-family: arial, sans-serif; font-size: 13.333333969116211px; line-height: 17px;" /&gt;&lt;span style="color: #333333; font-family: arial, sans-serif; font-size: 13.333333969116211px; line-height: 17px;"&gt;So, the survey includes some key findings. 27% experienced card fraud in the last five years, so just a little more than one in four experiencing card fraud. 82% said that they were very interested in being notified prior to the bank taking action. But we'll get into that a little bit more in the next couple of slides. 74% prefer that no additional transactions are posted until they respond to a fraud alert, and 21% of cardholders said that they would leave their institution after experiencing fraud.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br style="color: #333333; font-family: arial, sans-serif; font-size: 13.333333969116211px; line-height: 17px;" /&gt;&lt;br style="color: #333333; font-family: arial, sans-serif; font-size: 13.333333969116211px; line-height: 17px;" /&gt;&lt;span style="color: #333333; font-family: arial, sans-serif; font-size: 13.333333969116211px; line-height: 17px;"&gt;So, if you kind of look at that at a high level what does that mean? Fraud is being experienced by many of your customers. The majority of them want to be informed and want real-time action to be taken based on their instructions, and 20% of the customer base could leave as a result of fraud. So that's not an insignificant number.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br style="color: #333333; font-family: arial, sans-serif; font-size: 13.333333969116211px; line-height: 17px;" /&gt;&lt;br style="color: #333333; font-family: arial, sans-serif; font-size: 13.333333969116211px; line-height: 17px;" /&gt;&lt;span style="color: #333333; font-family: arial, sans-serif; font-size: 13.333333969116211px; line-height: 17px;"&gt;As we look at some of the credit card fraud rates by country, you'll see the 17 countries that were included in the survey broken out here. The U.S. and Mexico lead the way and have been the unfortunate benefactors of fraud, as we are the last back end to roll out EMV and still employing the signature versus more secure PIN verification methodology.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br style="color: #333333; font-family: arial, sans-serif; font-size: 13.333333969116211px; line-height: 17px;" /&gt;&lt;br style="color: #333333; font-family: arial, sans-serif; font-size: 13.333333969116211px; line-height: 17px;" /&gt;&lt;span style="color: #333333; font-family: arial, sans-serif; font-size: 13.333333969116211px; line-height: 17px;"&gt;But even in some of the EMV countries like the UK, almost a third of consumers surveyed experienced some form of credit card fraud in the past five years. As you can see, also on the other end of the spectrum, Holland enjoys very low card rates at less than 10% as do Germany and Sweden hovering right around the same area.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br style="color: #333333; font-family: arial, sans-serif; font-size: 13.333333969116211px; line-height: 17px;" /&gt;&lt;br style="color: #333333; font-family: arial, sans-serif; font-size: 13.333333969116211px; line-height: 17px;" /&gt;&lt;span style="color: #333333; font-family: arial, sans-serif; font-size: 13.333333969116211px; line-height: 17px;"&gt;When we look at the debit card fraud rates by country, the rates are a little bit lower in general. That's largely influenced by the nature of PIN transactions associated with a debit card.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="54900111" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/aciworldwide/Mobile_Fraud_Alerts-_Improve_Customer_Service_and_Fraud_Operations.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>57:11</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>ACI presents market insight on how mobile alerting affects consumer relationships with banks and issuers. http://www.aciworldwide.com/overview/mobile-payments/mobile-alerting.aspx</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Payments Risk Management for Postilion for Issuer - Acquirer - Retailer Webinar</title>
                    <pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2014 15:23:29 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">0255a0c7ff35a3a4b4e0a6c854a3197b</guid>
                    <link>http://aciworldwide.libsyn.com/payments-risk-management-for-postilion-for-issuer-acquirer-retailer-webinar</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/7100914"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;As indicated previously, please send those questions to us as soon as you have them throughout the webinar, and we'll address those as time permits at the end. This session is intended to be a primer for ACI payments risk management solution for Postilion customers, as we begin to release a solution, [A3], at the end of this month which will address the integration between the two products.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So let's begin with some market challenges faced by financial institutions today. We recognize that managing fraud is much more than identifying risky transactions. Obviously reducing fraud losses is key. But doing so in a manner that impacts your good customers less is equally important, and some in your organization may say is more important. Additional challenges that we're facing may include integration to other products, disparate or siloed risk management solutions employed today, lack of cross-channel views within your organization, and overall flexibility within your fraud management solution.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now it seems we've become a little numb to the articles that have come out in the news, things related to compromises. But it's clear that card fraud continues to make headlines across the globe. As long as there's money to be stolen and the FI's have sub-par fraud management solutions in place, this trend is going to continue to occur. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Card fraud trends that we've been battling for years remain consistent. But as new regions look to adopt the chip and PIN methodology, this fraud will migrate to paths of least resistance. Similar to fraud managers, [inaudible 00:02:20] in their own right have ROIs tied to their investments that they've made in stolen card stock. Until that chip and PIN is universally adopted across the globe, counterfeit will continue to be top of mind for risk managers. That's going to be our greatest exposure of risk.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ACI conducted a fraud survey aimed at understanding the concerns and attitudes of consumers towards fraud. This annual survey which looks primarily at card fraud was developed with our customers, which include both the banks, processors, and retailers to understand where their mindset is in terms of fraud. What we found was that a quarter of all customers have experienced fraud in the last five years. I'm not immune to this as well. As a fraud manager myself, I've had multiple fraud attempts against my business card or my debit card over the past.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Over half of the customers have used alternative methods once they've had a fraud incident occur, whether it be cash or whether it be another form of payment, maybe by check or by using a credit card instead of a debit card. Also 21% of our customers who experienced fraud have left their provider. We're not immune to attrition.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So as customers see fraud, they obviously think that there is the potential that the fraud is not necessarily being perpetrated just by the [fraudster]. They feel that maybe there's poor business practices being performed at their financial institution. So they're always looking to find a more secure way to protect their assets.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finally, 74% of the customers prefer to be involved in the fraud detection practice. What this means is they want to be notified when a fraud or when a risky transaction has been identified. This could be in means of an email. Traditionally, phone calls are made to the customer, as well as we're starting to get more involved in doing SMS text to customers to have them either approve or decline whether or not the transaction is legitimate or not.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now, you might imagine on the last few slides, we're finding that fraud initiatives are amongst the top ten areas in which banks are investing their time and efforts. This is seen from the graphic from CEB TowerGroup. Financial institutions are looking to strengthen their risk management practices, find better ways to protect their data, and look for ways to expand their product offerings to NFC, EMV, and eventually mobile.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So for our first polling question, "Do you currently have a fraud management solution today?" The options are "No." "Yes, but we have a homegrown solution." "Yes, but we have a purchased solution that we're running on premise." "Yes, we have an outsourced solution that's hosted." Or, "No, I don't know or this is not my area of responsibility."&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;http://www.aciworldwide.com/products-and-services/retail-payments/payments-processing/postilion-for-banks-and-processors.aspx&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="34623239" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/aciworldwide/Payments_Risk_Management_for_Postilion_for_Issuer_-_Acquirer_-_Retailer_Webinar.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>36:04</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>This session addresses the integration between ACI Payments Risk Management solution and Postilion.  http://www.aciworldwide.com/products-and-services/retail-payments/payments-processing/postilion-for-banks-and-processors.aspx</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Enterprise Payments- Thriving in a Growing and Fragmented Payments Marke</title>
                    <pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2014 15:18:42 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">3e154fe26330072804fa981a5ae51b59</guid>
                    <link>http://aciworldwide.libsyn.com/enterprise-payments-thriving-in-a-growing-and-fragmented-payments-marke</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/7100919"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #333333; font-family: arial, sans-serif; font-size: 13.333333969116211px; line-height: 17px;"&gt;Now, there are three main topics that I will be talking to you about before I hand over to Craig. The first is the challenges that are facing the financial services industry today. The second is why an enterprise approach to payments can help address many of these challenges. And, of course, how you can create revenue via an enterprise payment strategy.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br style="color: #333333; font-family: arial, sans-serif; font-size: 13.333333969116211px; line-height: 17px;" /&gt;&lt;br style="color: #333333; font-family: arial, sans-serif; font-size: 13.333333969116211px; line-height: 17px;" /&gt;&lt;span style="color: #333333; font-family: arial, sans-serif; font-size: 13.333333969116211px; line-height: 17px;"&gt;So let's talk about market pressures and how this impacts a bank's ability to make money. The first pressure is on loan demands. The top chart is a study of C&amp;amp;I loan demand in the U.S. over the last decade, while the bottom is the percentage of financial institutions reporting an increase in the spreads they can charge on these loans. Now, as you can see, the curves moved towards each other most sharply during the last financial crisis, and since then loan demand has been sporadic, peaking and dipping on an annual basis in concert with election cycles, as uncertainty over tax, employment, and healthcare policies remain.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br style="color: #333333; font-family: arial, sans-serif; font-size: 13.333333969116211px; line-height: 17px;" /&gt;&lt;br style="color: #333333; font-family: arial, sans-serif; font-size: 13.333333969116211px; line-height: 17px;" /&gt;&lt;span style="color: #333333; font-family: arial, sans-serif; font-size: 13.333333969116211px; line-height: 17px;"&gt;Now, the challenge that this presents for banks specifically is that this pattern is really too new to be a long-term trend, so being able to rely upon revenues, being able to forecast these revenues from the loan portfolio, are becoming increasingly difficult, and we'll be, of course, monitoring these results to see if we see a similar dip as we approach the upcoming election cycle in November of this year.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br style="color: #333333; font-family: arial, sans-serif; font-size: 13.333333969116211px; line-height: 17px;" /&gt;&lt;br style="color: #333333; font-family: arial, sans-serif; font-size: 13.333333969116211px; line-height: 17px;" /&gt;&lt;span style="color: #333333; font-family: arial, sans-serif; font-size: 13.333333969116211px; line-height: 17px;"&gt;Now, from there, we look at the impact that regulation and competition are having on expenses. Now, expenses are outpacing bank revenues, given the challenges over interest income and a steep drop off in fee revenues, as well, so the dark blue line that you see at the bottom of the slide and dipping most sharply, or falling to its lowest level around Q4 2010, is related to prohibitions on overdraft fees and the overall push to limit interchange. Now, as you can see, this is placing financial institutions in an increasingly dire situation, given that the impact that fee revenue has and the ability for it to help offset operating expenses.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br style="color: #333333; font-family: arial, sans-serif; font-size: 13.333333969116211px; line-height: 17px;" /&gt;&lt;br style="color: #333333; font-family: arial, sans-serif; font-size: 13.333333969116211px; line-height: 17px;" /&gt;&lt;span style="color: #333333; font-family: arial, sans-serif; font-size: 13.333333969116211px; line-height: 17px;"&gt;Now, let's talk to the next set of pressures, and that is, of course, regulatory pressure. This slide reflects the results of CEB TowerGroup surveys of financial institutions around the world on the topic of regulation and the impact that regulation will have on their businesses. Based on these surveys, we see that nearly 40 percent of financial institutions believe that regulation will have a negative impact on their business, and the reason for that is very much reflective over the infrastructures they are working with, in that they're simply not built to provide the information that's being requested. A prime example is FATCA, which came into effect recently, where banks are wrestling with how to provide the required information and is one of the reasons why over 60 percent of banks believe that compliance spend is going to increase.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br style="color: #333333; font-family: arial, sans-serif; font-size: 13.333333969116211px; line-height: 17px;" /&gt;&lt;br style="color: #333333; font-family: arial, sans-serif; font-size: 13.333333969116211px; line-height: 17px;" /&gt;&lt;span style="color: #333333; font-family: arial, sans-serif; font-size: 13.333333969116211px; line-height: 17px;"&gt;Now, I mentioned that system limitations are the prime reason, but you also see that data integrity, resource limitation, and even data availability are main challenges, as well, as we have siloed systems fragmenting infrastructure that simply wasn't meant to share information across lines of business or across the organization. And, of course, as you have multiple systems that you may have acquired over time, there's always a challenge in terms of data integrity, whether the data is being ported over from a system that is being terminated, or if you have multiple customers that have accounts at the various institutions that were acquired. So, for example, in some account systems I could be A. Schmidt, others I could be Andy Schmidt, others Andrew Schmidt, and the challenge for institutions is being able to reconcile those various identities and be able to create that one view of the customer.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br style="color: #333333; font-family: arial, sans-serif; font-size: 13.333333969116211px; line-height: 17px;" /&gt;&lt;br style="color: #333333; font-family: arial, sans-serif; font-size: 13.333333969116211px; line-height: 17px;" /&gt;&lt;span style="color: #333333; font-family: arial, sans-serif; font-size: 13.333333969116211px; line-height: 17px;"&gt;Now, since we've gone over the pressures facing the market, let's look at some of the opportunities that payments, and specifically enterprise payments, can provide. Non-cash payment volumes in the form of check, card, and ACH are growing, and are becoming more electronic as buyers and sellers seek out faster, more efficient, more data-rich payment times. And one of the assets that we have to track this indicates that debit, for example, is the most commonly used payment type in the world, but that ACH is growing quickly, as well, as both consumers and corporates are looking to simplify their payment capabilities or payment needs.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="58600722" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/aciworldwide/Enterprise_Payments-_Thriving_in_a_Growing_and_Fragmented_Payments_Market.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:01:03</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Webinar co-hosted by TowerGroup. Visit: http://www.aciworldwide.com/UP</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Concepts to Harness Multiple Benefits with EMV Technology</title>
                    <pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2014 14:18:27 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">864a43362603c35e55a3ec11e7f93fc2</guid>
                    <link>www.aciworldwide.com</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/7100932"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;EMEA has implemented EMV as well, and we're going to talk you through the benefits that will be seen in the US, and also set the scene for how this is going to work in the US as we, ACI, see it. Finally, the third person on the call is Bill Hanifin, who's the managing director of Hanifin Loyalty in the USA. We believe that loyalty will have an increasing role to play in the payments business, as both NFC cards and indeed mobile roll out. The plan is for us to talk to you about this, and then look for questions and answers at the end. Could I move to the next slide, please? Thank you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The US is now the only G-20 country without EMV and has subsequently . . . for a long while, there's been a battle not to implement EMV in the US, mainly driven around the fact that the majority of card authorizations are done online. That now is the situation that's not sustainable and the schemes have moved to give the US an implementation, as well. Could I have the next slide, please?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This shows that Visa and MasterCard have put programs, mandates, and remote acceptance of chip cards in the USA. Visa's focused mostly at merchants acquirers and processors. MasterCard is focusing on ATM acquiring. This movement is a catalyst for EMV in the US. It will involve financial penalties and incentives, and it will get an infrastructure in place to support EMV to reduce fraud. That's one of the things we're going to cover today. We're also going to highlight some of the other things, the benefits of EMV will come to the United States.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It's not just about card issuance, it's also merchants and acquirers both point-of-serve and ATM who'll need to justify the investment in the EMV infrastructure. We're going to talk briefly about the changes and benefits that that will be. It will also include a view to future payment innovation, and here, we're going to talk about NFC. Next slide, please.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Visa mandate includes RFID and NFC, and we're going to talk about that in some detail. Contactless cards and EMV: The US did contactless cards before; they did it only as a mag stripe edition. They're now rolling out much more strongly in Europe, and in some markets much more than others. We did a trial in London a few years ago, and the roll out is now starting to take shape. Again, we'll talk about the elements that need to be included in that. Mobile and EMV is also a key point. The secure element is one of the issues involved there, and we'll talk briefly about that. Payment credentials, mobile payments, and script changes will be part of that. Next slide, please.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here we go. We're going to talk about the Magnificent Seven of EMV. I'm now going to hand over to my colleague, Dave Locke.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;Good morning. My name is Dave Locke. I'm going to talk a little bit about 7 different aspects of EMV; how we think it will affect the States. I think it's fair to say we don't pretend we've got all the answers; that's certainly something in this world that nobody has, but hopefully we'll give you a few pointers and give you some idea of where to look and some of the experiences that we've gained. We're going to cover 7 of these things as we go through. The first one I'd like to cover is fraud. Can we go to the next slide, please?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The thing about fraud is that the frauds that they're innovating as much as anyone else. If you look here, this is a 14-year comparison. There are always lots and lots of statistics with EMV. One of the things that the UK has shown is that counterfeit cards and lost/stolen frauds has been reduced dramatically. It's difficult, the US doesn't keep fraud statistics in the same way as the UK does, but there is some open statistic. The statistics at the moment are saying 34% of fraud in the US is counterfeit. I don't think that's 44% of the whole amount because it isn't registered; it's only complaints that are registered, but it still shows that the considerable amount is something that will be sorted by EMV.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The issue with fraud is it's like a balloon. You'll take what it is and you'll change it. In this case, it will be EMV. The bad guys will just move somewhere else. Now we're in a situation where the banks have to react again and again differently, making each twist and turn a new thing. The thing is the right-hand corner is allegedly an anteater. If anyone wants the link on the web to make a balloon anteater, at the end of it, we can also supply that as well.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="52531119" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/aciworldwide/Concepts_to_Harness_Multiple_Benefits_with_EMV_Technology.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>54:43</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>ACI Worldwide software powers electronic transactions for financial institutions, processors and retailers around the world - all the time, without fail. Learn more: http://www.aciworldwide.com/emv</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>What Does EMV Mean for Acquirers?</title>
                    <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2014 20:55:50 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">25a20c3acd8b6dada6aaaa53dbc04118</guid>
                    <link>http://aciworldwide.libsyn.com/what-does-emv-mean-for-acquirers</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/6889597"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;In this episode of the ACI Worldwide's interview series, we will be discussing the move in the US toward EMV and what that means for acquirers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Product Page:&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://www.aciworldwide.com/what-we-do/retail-payments/emv-solutions/emv-for-acquirers.aspx"&gt;EMV for Acquirers &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="28754586" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/aciworldwide/What_does_EMV_mean.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>59:55</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>In this episode of the ACI Worldwide's interview series, we will be discussing the move in the US toward EMV and what that means for acquirers.
Product Page:&amp;nbsp;EMV for Acquirers</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Enterprise Payments: Accelerating Payments Transformation</title>
                    <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2014 20:24:22 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">788cbf232ae334e6804b80e9a0a9dda7</guid>
                    <link>http://aciworldwide.libsyn.com/enterprise-payments-accelerating-payments-transformation</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/6889489"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #333333; font-family: arial, sans-serif; font-size: 13px; line-height: 17px;"&gt;ACI Worldwide software powers electronic transactions for financial institutions, processors and retailers around the world - all the time, without fail.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this episode of ACI Worldwide's interview series, we will be discussing how Distra improves our ability to enable&amp;nbsp;our customers to execute&amp;nbsp;their payment strategies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.aciworldwide.com/products-and-services/wholesale-payments/online-and-mobile-banking/enterprise-banker.aspx"&gt;ACI Enterprise Banker product page&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="31090552" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/aciworldwide/Enterprise.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:04:47</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>ACI Worldwide software powers electronic transactions for financial institutions, processors and retailers around the world - all the time, without fail.&amp;nbsp;
In this episode of ACI Worldwide's interview series, we will be discussing how Distra...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Deploying EMV for Fraud Prevention</title>
                    <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2014 20:15:37 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">1f649423551f320a1b4f55fc8b4b5826</guid>
                    <link>http://aciworldwide.libsyn.com/deploying-emv-for-fraud-prevention</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/6889486"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #333333; font-family: arial, sans-serif; font-size: 13px; line-height: 17px;"&gt;ACI Worldwide software powers electronic transactions for financial institutions, processors and retailers around the world - all the time, without fail.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #333333; font-family: arial, sans-serif; font-size: 13px; line-height: 17px;"&gt;Presenters include:&amp;nbsp;Andy Morris; Financial Client Lead Solution Consultant for the region and John Verkia; Senior Fraud Prevention Manager, Nationwide Building Society. They will share with you their&amp;nbsp;experiences and challenges in respect to migrating to EMV. The&amp;nbsp;objectives&amp;nbsp;of the webinar&amp;nbsp;include describing what EMV actually is, articulating the business drivers behind EMV adoption in the UK, where the industry perceive the fraudster will strike next, or in the rollout to EMV, checkpoint the success points of EMV adoption, what actually happen in reality in respect to trends, the lessons as an industry we've learnt, and Nationwide Film Society's customer experience in relation to EMV.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.aciworldwide.com/what-we-do/retail-payments/emv-solutions/emv-for-issuers.aspx"&gt;EMV for Issuers solution page&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="31090555" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/aciworldwide/Deploying_EMV.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:04:47</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>ACI Worldwide software powers electronic transactions for financial institutions, processors and retailers around the world - all the time, without fail.
Presenters include:&amp;nbsp;Andy Morris; Financial Client Lead Solution Consultant for the region...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>EMV for Issuers Webinar: EMV Implementation, Infrastructure &amp; Tools</title>
                    <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2014 20:12:29 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">e896f853d792cd4190442fc6e3a04cbb</guid>
                    <link>http://aciworldwide.libsyn.com/emv-for-issuers-webinar-emv-implementation-infrastructure-tools</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/6889468"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;This webinar has three major segments; the main focus of this is how EMV is going to affect you specifically as an issuer.&amp;nbsp;Any non-issuers listening&amp;nbsp;will&amp;nbsp;still obviously learn some things--on the ACI website, you will find in more generic EMV overview webinar that we did a few months ago that you can also download and listen to. After discussing some of the details of EMV issuance, the presentation will&amp;nbsp;move to discuss some tools that ACI can supply to assist you through this period. Then the last half of the hour, Nigel will be speaking about his experience and implementation of some EMV tools.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.aciworldwide.com/what-we-do/retail-payments/emv-solutions/emv-for-issuers.aspx"&gt;EMV for Issuers solution page&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="31090557" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/aciworldwide/EMV_for_Issuers.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:04:47</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>This webinar has three major segments; the main focus of this is how EMV is going to affect you specifically as an issuer.&amp;nbsp;Any non-issuers listening&amp;nbsp;will&amp;nbsp;still obviously learn some things--on the ACI website, you will find in more...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>BANK 3.0 - Building Strong Relationships with Customers via Digital Channels</title>
                    <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2014 20:09:06 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">b93bd98abac0bb3ae202fc74a974ee50</guid>
                    <link>http://aciworldwide.libsyn.com/bank-30-building-strong-relationships-with-customers-via-digital-channels</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/6889464"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #333333; font-family: arial, sans-serif; font-size: 13px; line-height: 17px;"&gt;This is a webinar&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color: #333333; font-family: arial, sans-serif; font-size: 13px; line-height: 17px;"&gt;about this concept of digital relationships and building strong relationships with customers on a digital platform. It challenges the concept that the branch builds great relationships with customers, and thus&amp;nbsp;in that respect digital channels are inferior. You'll also hear about the practicalities of having a strong relationship with a customer who doesn't visit a branch, which is a concern for many organizations who have been branch-led for most of their existence, and now shifting this, thinking about the uncertainties behind it.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #333333; font-family: arial, sans-serif; font-size: 13px; line-height: 17px;"&gt;The&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color: #333333; font-family: arial, sans-serif; font-size: 13px; line-height: 17px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;presentation structured i&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color: #333333; font-family: arial, sans-serif; font-size: 13px; line-height: 17px;"&gt;n two parts. The first &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color: #333333; font-family: arial, sans-serif; font-size: 13px; line-height: 17px;"&gt;part is &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color: #333333; font-family: arial, sans-serif; font-size: 13px; line-height: 17px;"&gt;to give you some introductory thoughts, followed by a framework of key issues that came out in the lead-up to the webinar; primarily questions that were submitted by the audience, concerns that they have, and the key hurdles to the next generation of banking, in terms of digital engagement.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.aciworldwide.com/what-we-do/retail-payments/payments-processing/device-and-channel-management.aspx"&gt;Device and Channel Management solutions&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="27890654" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/aciworldwide/Bank_3.0.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>58:07</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>This is a webinar&amp;nbsp;about this concept of digital relationships and building strong relationships with customers on a digital platform. It challenges the concept that the branch builds great relationships with customers, and thus&amp;nbsp;in that...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Concepts to Harness Multiple Benefits with EMV Technology</title>
                    <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2014 19:03:36 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">59cd1ee38358a95b769fc38e4b76e96b</guid>
                    <link>http://aciworldwide.libsyn.com/concepts-to-harness-multiple-benefits-with-emv-technology</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/6889078"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;In this episode of ACI Worldwide's interview series, we will eb discussing the benefits of EMV technology, and how you can harness them.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.aciworldwide.com/what-we-do/retail-payments/emv-solutions/emv-for-acquirers.aspx"&gt;EMV for Acquirers solution page&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="26306589" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/aciworldwide/Concepts.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>54:49</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>ACI Worldwide software powers electronic transactions for financial institutions, processors and retailers around the world - all the time, without fail.</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>An Overview of EMV for the US Market</title>
                    <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2014 18:55:28 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">d93ae48188c135ff4eb888e37bc3aac9</guid>
                    <link>http://aciworldwide.libsyn.com/an-overview-of-emv-for-the-us-market</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/6889032"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #333333; font-family: arial, sans-serif; font-size: 13px; line-height: 17px;"&gt;Today's topic is EMV: An Overview with Some US Considerations. We are going to cover 3 main topics today. First, about half of our time will be spent on what is EMV and chip. This is by no means a detailed technical overview. It'll be a high-level discussion of what EMV is, where it came from, and we'll finish up with a bit of a discussion about where is EMV in the world and around the globe. Then we'll spend a bit of time on some discussions of EMV in the United States; how it might move into the States, and what factors are pushing it that the US might want to consider. Then lastly, we'll finish up with some thoughts about what EMV means to me, and I come at this from 2 points of view: Whether I'm an acquirer or an issuer of card transactions.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.aciworldwide.com/what-we-do/retail-payments/emv-solutions/emv-for-acquirers.aspx"&gt;EMV for Acquirers solution page&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="31090560" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/aciworldwide/An_Overview_of_EMV.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:04:47</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>A webinar going over 3 main topics about EMV in the United States </itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>The Impact of Mobile on the Future of Retail Banking</title>
                    <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2014 18:49:09 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">c1b97b66b5f9386b19b33d607e4b773d</guid>
                    <link>http://aciworldwide.libsyn.com/the-impact-of-mobile-on-the-future-of-retail-banking-0</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/6888808"/>
                    <description>&lt;p class="p1"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Aite and ACI discuss the impact of mobile on the needs of consumers and the marketing of retail financial services&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="p1"&gt;The Future of Mobile Banking is a topic on everyone's radar, regardless of the size of your institution or where you're are with your global strategy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="p1"&gt;An interesting element of mobile is the changing and evolving needs of the consumer and the technological information that addresses those needs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="p1"&gt;ACI Worldwide software powers electronic transactions for financial institutions, processors and retailers around the world - all the time, without fail.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="p1"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.aciworldwide.com/what-we-do/retail-payments/online-mobile-branch-banking/mobile-banking-and-payments.aspx"&gt;Mobile Banking and Payments solutions&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="27890666" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/aciworldwide/The_Impact_of_Mobile.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>58:07</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Retail Banking and Mobile Banking</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>The Global Rise of Smartphonatics: Driving Mobile Payments in Banking Adoption in the Americas, EMEA, and Asia-Pacific</title>
                    <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2014 18:44:37 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">0f5941ed05318da892fe62edf30dd5e1</guid>
                    <link>http://aciworldwide.libsyn.com/the-global-rise-of-smartphonatics-driving-mobile-payments-in-banking-adoption-in-the-americas-emea-and-asia-pacific</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/6888782"/>
                    <description>&lt;p class="p1"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ACI and Aite discuss how current global and regional smartphone use is predicting the future shape of the mobile economy. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="p1"&gt;Mobile is one of the hottest areas in the payments and banking industry today. Despite the fact that we see mobility everywhere, we felt that there was not a lot of data on our mobile customers. Across the industry, there is an inconsistent understanding of these consumers; what they are doing, what they look like in different countries, how they prefer to shop or transact, and how they shape the future of banking and payments over the next 5 years. Within this podcast we discuss the results of our global study and what the implications are within the payments and banking industry.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="p1"&gt;ACI Worldwide software powers electronic transactions for financial institutions, processors and retailers around the world - all the time, without fail.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="p1"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.aciworldwide.com/what-we-do/retail-payments/online-mobile-branch-banking/mobile-banking-and-payments.aspx"&gt;Mobile Banking and Payments solution&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="27890656" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/aciworldwide/AP_Session.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>58:07</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Mobile: One of the Hottest Areas in the Payments and Banking Industry Today</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Replace your Card Issuing Platform for Higher Revenue Generation</title>
                    <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2014 18:40:17 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">461c559756371bbc0895b272042027a9</guid>
                    <link>http://aciworldwide.libsyn.com/replace-your-card-issuing-platform-for-higher-revenue-generation-0</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/6888763"/>
                    <description>&lt;p class="p1"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Aite and ACI discuss the basic requirements for a card issuing platform in the 21st century and discuss the the value added and revenue generation capabilities that are needed to grow an issuing business.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="p1"&gt;This episode consider some of the IT infrastructure dilemmas faced by payment insures and banks in general, the frustrations they have with the current payment hub systems, and the likelihood of them purchasing new software solutions rather than building systems in-house. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="p1"&gt;ACI Worldwide software powers electronic transactions for financial institutions, processors and retailers around the world - all the time, without fail.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="p1"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.aciworldwide.com/products-and-services/retail-payments/card-management-acquiring-and-settlement/issuer.aspx"&gt;ACI Issuer product page&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="27890663" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/aciworldwide/Replace_your_Card.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>58:07</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Understand Market Drivers for Moving to a Modern Card Issuing Platform</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Managing Cardholder Transactions: Disputes and Chargebacks</title>
                    <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2014 18:34:47 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">63d228f4ba28b8c04d8d570c24220371</guid>
                    <link>http://aciworldwide.libsyn.com/managing-cardholder-transactions-disputes-and-chargebacks-0</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/6888738"/>
                    <description>&lt;p class="p1"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ACI discuss how automating disputes and chargebacks can reduce handle time, strengthen your position and keep you compliant with critical date requirements.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="p1"&gt;It is easier than ever for customers to dispute transactions; issuers must be prepared to resolve transactions quickly before they miss critical turnaround parameters.&amp;nbsp;Changes in legislation and technology make it easier than ever to put a transaction into a dispute; if you fail to react quickly you can lose chargeback rights, face complaints with the Consumer Financial Protection Bureau and network penalties. Best practices handle these expensive transactions with well trained staff using engineered workflows and supporting tools.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Customers typically require real time resolution and final resolution within one billing cycle. In many cases, you will be interacting with merchants and processors that use automated tools that can outpace your current staff.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="p1"&gt;ACI Worldwide software powers electronic transactions for financial institutions, processors and retailers around the world - all the time, without fail.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="p1"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="p1"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.aciworldwide.com/products-and-services/payments-fraud/case-management/case-manager.aspx"&gt;ACI Case Manager product page&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="27890678" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/aciworldwide/Managing_Cardholder_Transactions.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>58:07</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Best Practices: Reducing Operating Timeframes, Internal Handling Expense and Account Workflows</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Global Consumers React to Rising Payment Fraud</title>
                    <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2014 18:31:49 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">2e8a775c5f836f51f6d2cbb12de8eb7f</guid>
                    <link>http://aciworldwide.libsyn.com/global-consumers-react-to-rising-payment-fraud-0</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/6888731"/>
                    <description>&lt;p class="p1"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ACI and Aite share results of a global study and convey consumer attitudes towards payment fraud, its affect on customer retention, and working with banks to fight fraud.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="p1"&gt;The survey was conducted to help our customers better understand how their consumers are impacted by fraud and how those consumers are responding to this ever-changing threat.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Speakers include Mike Braatz; Senior Vice President and Product Line Manager at ACI Worldwide. Mike is responsible for the product strategy roadmap and delivery of ACI Payments Fraud product line, which includes Proactive Risk Manager and ACI Case Manager. Shirley Insco is a senior analyst with IK Group, covering fraud, data security, anti-money laundering and compliance issues.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="p1"&gt;ACI Worldwide software powers electronic transactions for financial institutions, processors and retailers around the world - all the time, without fail.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="p1"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="p1"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.aciworldwide.com/products-and-services/payments-fraud/fraud-detection-and-aml/proactive-risk-manager.aspx"&gt;ACI Proactive Risk Manager product page&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="27890662" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/aciworldwide/Global_Consumers.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>58:07</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>ACI's 3rd Annual Global Card Fraud Study  </itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>ACI Worldwide Merchant Acquirer:  A Technology Refresh for Growth</title>
                    <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2014 18:28:44 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">a0e13211326d9bc7ba61aab884c7d145</guid>
                    <link>http://aciworldwide.libsyn.com/aci-worldwide-merchant-acquirer-a-technology-refresh-for-growth</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/6888727"/>
                    <description>&lt;p class="p1"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ACI and Aite Group discuss a recent survey of Merchant Acquirers in the US Market and consider the need for a merchant acquiring technology refresh.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="p1"&gt;Easing the Pain: Finding New Growth Opportunities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="p1"&gt;ACI Worldwide software powers electronic transactions for financial institutions, processors and retailers around the world - all the time, without fail.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="p1"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="p1"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.aciworldwide.com/what-we-do/retail-payments/card-management-acquiring-and-settlement/merchant-acquiring.aspx"&gt;ACI Merchant Acquiring solution page&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="24434566" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/aciworldwide/Merchant_Acquirer_Webinar.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>50:55</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Merchant Acquiring Technology Survey Discussion</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>ACI Mobile Billing and Payment: Maximizing Your Success</title>
                    <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2014 18:02:47 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">2484e0957757d133cdc117f51ca63c9f</guid>
                    <link>http://aciworldwide.libsyn.com/aci-mobile-billing-and-payment-maximizing-your-success</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/6888646"/>
                    <description>&lt;p class="p1"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ACI discusses how to effectively deploy a mobile billing system.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="p1"&gt;As mobile continues on the fast track, mobile bill presentment and payment across web, apps and text has transitioned from optional features to essential components of a successful billing and payment strategy, and organizations are quickly realizing the importance of providing optimal mobile services.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="p1"&gt;Implementing a mobile billing and payment system is an essential step toward meeting increasing customer demands. Ultimately though, the mobile capabilities and how effectively they are deployed are what will determine whether or not the mobile billing system is perceived as exceptional or inadequate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="p1"&gt;ACI Worldwide software powers electronic transactions for financial institutions, processors and retailers around the world - all the time, without fail.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="p1"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.aciworldwide.com/what-we-do/retail-payments/online-mobile-branch-banking/mobile-banking-and-payments.aspx"&gt;Mobile Billing and Payments solutions &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="25722288" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/aciworldwide/Mobile_Billing.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>53:36</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Essential Components of Mobile Bill Presentment and Payment </itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>ACI Anti-Fraud Solution Proactive Risk Manager for Postilion</title>
                    <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2014 17:59:06 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">8a807453336d7ee069a876b4a0886401</guid>
                    <link>http://aciworldwide.libsyn.com/aci-anti-fraud-solution-proactive-risk-manager-for-postilion-1</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/6889655"/>
                    <description>&lt;p class="p1"&gt;Getting financial crime wrong has implications, not just financial costs, but the potential loss of a valued customer or even reputation damage.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="p1"&gt;Are we doing a good job in the industry today? From my perspective, the answer is probably no. Recent card fraud losses reported $365 million in losses, a fall from $444 million in the previous year. We need to look further back to the 1990s to understand the extent of today's problems. Our industry losses then stood at less than $100 million. We have also dreamt up new names for emerging challenges. Back in the 1990s, we had phantom withdrawals, which is skimming today. Ghost Money was a common term used to describe what we today know as 419 scams or more elaborate boiler room frauds. Customer education is vital in fighting fraud, but customers are also gullible. If it sounds too good to be true, it probably is too good to be true, but still, customers remain vulnerable.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="p1"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.aciworldwide.com/products-and-services/payments-fraud/fraud-detection-and-aml/proactive-risk-manager.aspx"&gt;ACI Proactive Risk Manager product page&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="10963985" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/aciworldwide/ACI-Anti-Fraud-Solution-Proactive-Risk-Manager-for-Postilion.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>22:51</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>This podcast discusses how ACI's industry leading anti-fraud solution Proactive Risk Manager can be used in conjunction with Postilion.</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>2013 Trends in Online Banking &amp; Cash Management</title>
                    <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2014 17:53:40 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">57ad5ab5b0118ee180e612239f0623a6</guid>
                    <link>http://aciworldwide.libsyn.com/2013-trends-in-online-banking-cash-management-0</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/6889657"/>
                    <description>&lt;p class="p1"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Greenwich Associates and ACI Worldwide provide&amp;nbsp;insight into both the views of executives regarding their online banking and cash management practices and the latest market trends.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="p1"&gt;Business executives rely on banking providers to supply a continuous flow of information to inform the organization of its true cash position. In particular, client expectations for information delivered to mobile devices have continued to increase over the past 12 months, particularly among small businesses.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="p1"&gt;Marc Harrison, Principal Consultant with Greenwich Associates, discusses the firm's recent findings on the mindset of executives in mid-sized and small businesses with a focus on the role of online-banking in building and maintaining strong treasury/cash management relationships. Matt Ellis, SVP Channel Solutions with ACI Worldwide then presents the benefits of ACI Universal Online Banker and how it helps banks to keep pace in this fast moving market.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="p1"&gt;ACI Worldwide software powers electronic transactions for financial institutions, processors and retailers around the world - all the time, without fail.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="p1"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.aciworldwide.com/products-and-services/retail-payments/online-mobile-branch-banking/online-banking.aspx" target="_blank"&gt;Online Banking product page &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="27890657" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/aciworldwide/2013_Trends.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>58:07</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Keeping Pace in this Fast Moving Market</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
            </channel>
        </rss>
    </httpclient:body>
</httpclient:response>