<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<httpclient:response xmlns:httpclient="http://exist-db.org/xquery/httpclient" statusCode="200">
    <httpclient:headers>
        <httpclient:header name="Server" value="Apache/2.2.22 (Ubuntu)"/>
        <httpclient:header name="X-Libsyn-Host" value="web-engine3.libsyn.com"/>
        <httpclient:header name="Vary" value="Accept-Encoding"/>
        <httpclient:header name="Content-Type" value="application/rss+xml"/>
        <httpclient:header name="last-modified" value="Mon, 18 Aug 2014 07:00:02 GMT"/>
        <httpclient:header name="Content-Length" value="138380"/>
        <httpclient:header name="Accept-Ranges" value="bytes"/>
        <httpclient:header name="Date" value="Wed, 20 Aug 2014 09:57:12 GMT"/>
        <httpclient:header name="X-Varnish" value="3094185848 3074906402"/>
        <httpclient:header name="Age" value="182981"/>
        <httpclient:header name="Via" value="1.1 varnish"/>
        <httpclient:header name="Connection" value="close"/>
        <httpclient:header name="X-Cache" value="HIT"/>
    </httpclient:headers>
    <httpclient:body mimetype="application/rss+xml" type="xml">
        <rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:cc="http://web.resource.org/cc/" version="2.0">
            <channel>
                <atom:link href="http://ariynbf.libsyn.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
                <title>Alison Rosen Is Your New Best Friend</title>
                <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2014 06:58:56 +0000</pubDate>
                <lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2014 07:00:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
                <generator>Libsyn WebEngine 2.0</generator>
                <link>http://www.alisonrosen.com</link>
                <language>en</language>
                <copyright>Alison Rosen</copyright>
                <docs>http://www.alisonrosen.com</docs>
                <description>A twice weekly podcast hosted by veteran interviewer and everyone's new best friend Alison Rosen (The Adam Carolla Show) featuring surprisingly honest conversations that are equal parts silly, serious, revelatory and sometimes involving a sombrero. Plus an eternal quest to find out if that thing you think or do is normal in a segment called "Just Me or Everyone?" </description>
                <image>
                    <url>http://assets.libsyn.com/content/4192410.jpg</url>
                    <title>Alison Rosen Is Your New Best Friend</title>
                    <link>http://www.alisonrosen.com</link>
                </image>
                <itunes:author>Carolla Digital</itunes:author>
                <itunes:category text="Comedy"/>
                <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/4192410.jpg"/>
                <itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
                <itunes:summary>A twice weekly podcast hosted by veteran interviewer and everyone's new best friend Alison Rosen (The Adam Carolla Show) featuring surprisingly honest conversations that are equal parts silly, serious, revelatory and sometimes involving a sombrero. Plus an eternal quest to find out if that thing you think or do is normal in a segment called "Just Me or Everyone?"</itunes:summary>
                <itunes:subtitle/>
                <item>
                    <title>Lauren Sivan</title>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2014 06:58:56 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">620165d843e670688bfebe1739ac6c5a</guid>
                    <link>http://ariynbf.libsyn.com/lauren-sivan</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/7516662"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Lauren Sivan stops by this episode of Alison Rosen Is Your New Best Friend to talk about her start in broadcasting, working for Fox, working overnights, Courtney Friel's cookie party, sneakers vs. tennis shoes, pronunciations, dream jobs, losing her father at a young age, finding Libya on a map, crashing a news van, hair, twitter and so much more. We also did a round of Just Me Or Everyone&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="53018028" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/ariynbf/ARIYNBF_LaurenSivan.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:49:29</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Lauren Sivan stops by this episode of Alison Rosen Is Your New Best Friend to talk about her start in broadcasting, working for Fox, working overnights, Courtney Friel's cookie party, sneakers vs. tennis shoes, pronunciations, dream jobs, losing her...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Caelan's Carb Contribution, Hearing People's Thoughts, BoBo Barking</title>
                    <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2014 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">b0aa5bf703c4d3a39e529a3fd5f7919f</guid>
                    <link>http://ariynbf.libsyn.com/caelans-carb-contribution-hearing-peoples-thoughts-bobo-barking</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/7492112"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;The Thursday gang &amp;nbsp;(Alison, Chris Laxamana, Matt Fondiler, Gary Smith and Jenna Kim Jones) &amp;nbsp;discusses Caelan's Carb Contribution, driving to San Diego, vaccines and shots in general, whether the ability to hear everyone's thoughts would make you feel compassion or contempt, milk and so much more. We also did a round of Just Me Or Everyone&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="39905040" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/ariynbf/ARIYNBF_MBF73.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:22:10</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>The Thursday gang &amp;nbsp;(Alison, Chris Laxamana, Matt Fondiler, Gary Smith and Jenna Kim Jones) &amp;nbsp;discusses Caelan's Carb Contribution, driving to San Diego, vaccines and shots in general, whether the ability to hear everyone's thoughts would make...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Jeremy Konner</title>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2014 18:25:50 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">f6ca6d2818aabb1b1de91ab8ab9e0ff3</guid>
                    <link>http://ariynbf.libsyn.com/jeremy-konner</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/7492149"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Jeremy Konner (Drunk History) stops by this episode of Alison Rosen Is Your New Best Friend to talk about directing, producing and co-creating Comedy Central's Drunk History, being the brother of Girls show runner Jenni Konner, growing up in a screenwriting family, his mother's stroke and subsequent six month long coma when he was seven, TV shows, being Jack Black's assistant, relationships, architects and so much more. We also did a round of Just Me Or Everyone&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="44351226" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/ariynbf/ARIYNBF_JeremyKonner.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:31:26</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Jeremy Konner (Drunk History) stops by this episode of Alison Rosen Is Your New Best Friend to talk about directing, producing and co-creating Comedy Central's Drunk History, being the brother of Girls show runner Jenni Konner, growing up in a...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Alison's Website Is Making Her Crazy, Nicknames, Vacations</title>
                    <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2014 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">da6a0258fcfb294866c9cc3f4a3f1141</guid>
                    <link>http://ariynbf.libsyn.com/alisons-website-is-making-her-crazy-nicknames-vacations</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/7481967"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;The Thursday gang &amp;nbsp;(Alison, Chris Laxamana, Matt Fondiler, Gary Smith and Jenna Kim Jones) &amp;nbsp;discusses family nicknames, our upcoming vacations, how we feel about talking on the phone and so much more. Also we pulled your topics out of the hat! Also Alison's website is down right now and it's making her crazy! Also we also did a round of Just Me Or Everyone&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="33009549" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/ariynbf/ARIYNBF_MBF72.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:07:48</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>The Thursday gang &amp;nbsp;(Alison, Chris Laxamana, Matt Fondiler, Gary Smith and Jenna Kim Jones) &amp;nbsp;discusses family nicknames, our upcoming vacations, how we feel about talking on the phone and so much more. Also we pulled your topics out of the...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Matt Braunger</title>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2014 05:16:07 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">fdd6a4ad56f60a099ff542c874441321</guid>
                    <link>http://ariynbf.libsyn.com/matt-braunger</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/7470784"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Matt Braunger stops by this episode of Alison Rosen Is Your New Best Friend to talk about his podcast Ding-Donger with Matt Braunger, hitchhiking, love, being an only child, casting shows, therapy, relationships, commercials, stand up and so much more. We also did a round of Just Me Or Everyone&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="39607807" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/ariynbf/ARIYNBF_MattBraugner.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:21:33</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Matt Braunger stops by this episode of Alison Rosen Is Your New Best Friend to talk about his podcast Ding-Donger with Matt Braunger, hitchhiking, love, being an only child, casting shows, therapy, relationships, commercials, stand up and so much...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Jenna's Fry Sauce, BoBo Boys, Nut Rankings</title>
                    <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2014 05:18:14 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">a2c944e3ff1244279c768f97081fb435</guid>
                    <link>http://ariynbf.libsyn.com/jennas-fry-sauce-bobo-boys-nut-rankings</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/7456495"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;The Thursday gang &amp;nbsp;(Alison, Chris Laxamana, Matt Fondiler, Gary Smith and Jenna Kim Jones) &amp;nbsp;discusses being reunited after Jenna's adventures, fry sauce, Daniel's thoughts on nuts, nut rankings, baking, burping and so much more. We also did a round of Just Me Or Everyone&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="35280321" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/ariynbf/ARIYNBF_MBF71.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:12:32</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>The Thursday gang &amp;nbsp;(Alison, Chris Laxamana, Matt Fondiler, Gary Smith and Jenna Kim Jones) &amp;nbsp;discusses being reunited after Jenna's adventures, fry sauce, Daniel's thoughts on nuts, nut rankings, baking, burping and so much more. We also did...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Zhena Muzyka</title>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2014 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">d79b57bba1f3ee123325862fca34ef93</guid>
                    <link>http://ariynbf.libsyn.com/zhena-muzyka</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/7437822"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Zhena Muzyka, author of Life by the Cup, stops by this episode of Alison Rosen Is Your New Best Friend to talk about her journey from poor single mother to successful author, entrepreneur and activist. We discussed learning to ask for help, picking your battles, powerful women versus powerful men, her gypsy heritage, growing her Gypsy Tea company, yurts, Ojai, raising money, motherhood, book widows, tarot cards and so much more. We also did a round of Just Me Or Everyone&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="44065969" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/ariynbf/ARIYNBF_Zhena.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:30:50</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Zhena Muzyka, author of Life by the Cup, stops by this episode of Alison Rosen Is Your New Best Friend to talk about her journey from poor single mother to successful author, entrepreneur and activist. We discussed learning to ask for help, picking...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Alison Needs Surgery, Caelan Takes Tips, Return of Fan Phone Call</title>
                    <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2014 05:13:42 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">fab854ec8ca7ba69aea64d58acc50134</guid>
                    <link>http://ariynbf.libsyn.com/alison-needs-surgery-caelan-takes-tips-return-of-fan-phone-call</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/7424229"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;The Thursday gang &amp;nbsp;(Alison, Chris Laxamana, Matt Fondiler, Gary Smith and Jenna Kim Jones) &amp;nbsp;minus Jenna plus Mike Altier discusses Alison's frisbee/boomerang uterus, vaccines, tubas, more butter sandwich talk, Mike Altier's nutrition theory as it relates to sandwiches, the BoBo Boys, National Batman Day, tattoos and the return of fan phone call. We also did a round of Just Me Or Everyone&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="47145138" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/ariynbf/ARIYNBF_MBF70.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:37:15</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>The Thursday gang &amp;nbsp;(Alison, Chris Laxamana, Matt Fondiler, Gary Smith and Jenna Kim Jones) &amp;nbsp;minus Jenna plus Mike Altier discusses Alison's frisbee/boomerang uterus, vaccines, tubas, more butter sandwich talk, Mike Altier's nutrition theory...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Jonah Ray</title>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2014 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">b49a7e9f922e2755eaf0b099557e6397</guid>
                    <link>http://ariynbf.libsyn.com/jonah-ray</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/7407892"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Jonah Ray stops by this episode of Alison Rosen Is Your New Best Friend to talk about The Meltdown which premieres on Comedy Central July, 23, playing in bands, how he met Chris Hardwick and became part of Nerdist, growing up overweight, meeting his wife, comedy and stand up, guitar stores, the ladies, drinking, Vine and so much more. We also did a round of Just Me Or Everyone&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="57012673" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/ariynbf/ARIYNBF_JonahRay.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:57:48</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Jonah Ray stops by this episode of Alison Rosen Is Your New Best Friend to talk about The Meltdown which premieres on Comedy Central July, 23, playing in bands, how he met Chris Hardwick and became part of Nerdist, growing up overweight, meeting his...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Dawson Plays the Animal Name Game, Adam Hurls a Jump Rope, Chris and Alison Can't Sleep</title>
                    <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2014 04:06:53 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">ffcdf516294243a88cc7a21f16fac62c</guid>
                    <link>http://ariynbf.libsyn.com/dawson-plays-the-animal-name-game-adam-hurls-a-jump-rope-chris-and-alison-cant-sleep</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/7395094"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;The Thursday gang &amp;nbsp;(Alison, Chris Laxamana, Matt Fondiler, Gary Smith and Jenna Kim Jones) minus Jenna plus Mike Dawson revisits the pill discussion while Gary pre-reads. Also we discuss Adam's jump rope attempt on Matt and Mike's life, the air conditioning fiasco of last week, manscaping, Eva Peron, Ray Donovan, Real Housewives of Orange County, Keeping up with the Kardashians, Celebrity Rehab and we introduce the animal name game. We also did a round of Just Me Or Everyone&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="36001574" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/ariynbf/ARIYNBF_MBF69.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:14:02</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>The Thursday gang &amp;nbsp;(Alison, Chris Laxamana, Matt Fondiler, Gary Smith and Jenna Kim Jones) minus Jenna plus Mike Dawson revisits the pill discussion while Gary pre-reads. Also we discuss Adam's jump rope attempt on Matt and Mike's life, the air...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Courtney Robertson</title>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2014 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">fdccd7202541ab0f94b88d8af140b685</guid>
                    <link>http://ariynbf.libsyn.com/courtney-robertson-0</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/7381506"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Courtney Robertson stops by this episode of Alison Rosen Is Your New Best Friend to talk about her new book I Didn't Come Here To Make Friends: Confessions of a Reality Show Villain (about her experience winning the Ben Flajnik season of The Bachelor), the bachelor himself, dating, what it's like behind-the-scenes on a reality show, feeling betrayed by her friends, having sex on the show, the whole "skinny-dipping with a model" thing, her overprotective mother, buying dogs with her first modeling money, modeling in general, nudity, how to look good at a photo shoot and so much more. We also did a round of Just Me Or Everyone&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="36766375" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/ariynbf/ARIYNBF_CourtneyRobertson.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:15:38</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Courtney Robertson stops by this episode of Alison Rosen Is Your New Best Friend to talk about her new book I Didn't Come Here To Make Friends: Confessions of a Reality Show Villain (about her experience winning the Ben Flajnik season of The...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Alison's a Hero, Pink Starburst Are Best, Live Caelan's Corner Jingle</title>
                    <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2014 09:57:48 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">5820f9c73d440037a22a96b127fd2215</guid>
                    <link>http://ariynbf.libsyn.com/alisons-a-hero-pink-starburst-are-best-live-caelans-corner-jingle</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/7370809"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;The Thursday gang &amp;nbsp;(Alison, Chris Laxamana, Matt Fondiler, Gary Smith, Jenna Kim Jones, Caelan Biehn) &amp;nbsp;minus Matt plus Mike Altier discusses Alison's blood drawing and fertility clinic experiences and performs numerous live Caelan's Corner jingles, plus shower talk, pencil waving and more. We also did a round of Just Me Or Everyone&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="41342819" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/ariynbf/ARIYNBF_MBF68.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:25:10</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>The Thursday gang &amp;nbsp;(Alison, Chris Laxamana, Matt Fondiler, Gary Smith, Jenna Kim Jones, Caelan Biehn) &amp;nbsp;minus Matt plus Mike Altier discusses Alison's blood drawing and fertility clinic experiences and performs numerous live Caelan's Corner...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Mary Katharine Ham Returns</title>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2014 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">3d3f537678d9adf949e99646d4494f23</guid>
                    <link>http://ariynbf.libsyn.com/mary-katharine-ham-returns</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/7357566"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Mary Katharine Ham returns to &amp;nbsp;Alison Rosen Is Your New Best Friend to talk about her new hair, new baby, being referred to as a "conservative pundit," Bill O'Reilly, race on TV, Donald Sterling, birth control, childbirth, finances and name changes, makeup, pot, periods, braces, grocery stores and so much more. We also did a round of Just Me Or Everyone&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="41533827" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/ariynbf/ARIYNBF_MKHamReturns.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:25:33</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Mary Katharine Ham returns to &amp;nbsp;Alison Rosen Is Your New Best Friend to talk about her new hair, new baby, being referred to as a "conservative pundit," Bill O'Reilly, race on TV, Donald Sterling, birth control, childbirth, finances and name...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Alison Can't Whistle, Leaving Dumb Jokes to Matt, Getting Blood Drawn</title>
                    <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2014 04:07:43 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">889d8cc4404f9f4f80601e5ee2271e72</guid>
                    <link>http://ariynbf.libsyn.com/alison-cant-whistle-leaving-dumb-jokes-to-matt-getting-blood-drawn</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/7347172"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: Georgia, 'Times New Roman', 'Bitstream Charter', Times, serif; font-size: 13px; line-height: 19px;"&gt;The Thursday gang &amp;nbsp;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a style="font-family: Georgia, 'Times New Roman', 'Bitstream Charter', Times, serif; font-size: 13px; line-height: 19px;" href="http://twitter.com/alisonrosen"&gt;Alison&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: Georgia, 'Times New Roman', 'Bitstream Charter', Times, serif; font-size: 13px; line-height: 19px;"&gt;,&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a style="font-family: Georgia, 'Times New Roman', 'Bitstream Charter', Times, serif; font-size: 13px; line-height: 19px;" href="http://twitter.com/chrislaxamana"&gt;Chris Laxamana&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: Georgia, 'Times New Roman', 'Bitstream Charter', Times, serif; font-size: 13px; line-height: 19px;"&gt;,&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a style="font-family: Georgia, 'Times New Roman', 'Bitstream Charter', Times, serif; font-size: 13px; line-height: 19px;" href="http://therewillbespoilers.com/"&gt;Matt Fondiler&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: Georgia, 'Times New Roman', 'Bitstream Charter', Times, serif; font-size: 13px; line-height: 19px;"&gt;,&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a style="font-family: Georgia, 'Times New Roman', 'Bitstream Charter', Times, serif; font-size: 13px; line-height: 19px;" href="http://twitter.com/gpatricksmith"&gt;Gary Smith&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: Georgia, 'Times New Roman', 'Bitstream Charter', Times, serif; font-size: 13px; line-height: 19px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;and&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a style="font-family: Georgia, 'Times New Roman', 'Bitstream Charter', Times, serif; font-size: 13px; line-height: 19px;" href="http://twitter.com/jennakimjones"&gt;Jenna Kim Jones&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: Georgia, 'Times New Roman', 'Bitstream Charter', Times, serif; font-size: 13px; line-height: 19px;"&gt;) &amp;nbsp;discusses&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a style="font-family: Georgia, 'Times New Roman', 'Bitstream Charter', Times, serif; font-size: 13px; line-height: 19px;" href="http://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B00KST4WDY/ref=as_li_tl?ie=UTF8&amp;amp;camp=1789&amp;amp;creative=390957&amp;amp;creativeASIN=B00KST4WDY&amp;amp;linkCode=as2&amp;amp;tag=alisrose-20&amp;amp;linkId=O765NZURMJT2QR6E"&gt;Jenna's comedy special&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: Georgia, 'Times New Roman', 'Bitstream Charter', Times, serif; font-size: 13px; line-height: 19px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;which Alison and Matt watched, Chris's hot musical performance, Dawson's "fart with legs," Limp Bizkit, Alison's inability to whistle, waxing, Chris's fantasy baseball bets, the impending return of fan phone call and so much more. We also did a round of Just Me Or Everyone&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="41150976" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/ariynbf/ARIYNBF_MBF67.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:24:46</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>The Thursday gang &amp;nbsp;(Alison,&amp;nbsp;Chris Laxamana,&amp;nbsp;Matt Fondiler,&amp;nbsp;Gary Smith&amp;nbsp;and&amp;nbsp;Jenna Kim Jones) &amp;nbsp;discusses&amp;nbsp;Jenna's comedy special&amp;nbsp;which Alison and Matt watched, Chris's hot musical performance, Dawson's "fart...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Jason Nash</title>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2014 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">e1f31c630bc2008e9436807326557390</guid>
                    <link>http://ariynbf.libsyn.com/jason-nash</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/7331794"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Jason Nash stops by this episode of Alison Rosen Is Your New Best Friend to talk about his new movie, Jason Nash is Married along with how he got into comedy, how his real life differs from the one depicted in the film, growing up in Boston, his parents, the relative important of fancy things, growing up overweight, his parents, parenthood, dogs, infidelity, Busy Phillips and so much more. We also did a round of Just Me Or Everyone&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="41900104" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/ariynbf/ARIYNBF_JasonNash.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:26:19</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Jason Nash stops by this episode of Alison Rosen Is Your New Best Friend to talk about his new movie, Jason Nash is Married along with how he got into comedy, how his real life differs from the one depicted in the film, growing up in Boston, his...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Chris's Banana Holder, Basic Wooki, Mike Altier</title>
                    <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2014 08:20:18 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">8c5420be76a59b74a5baf1f4f8a05e22</guid>
                    <link>http://ariynbf.libsyn.com/chriss-banana-holder-basic-wooki-mike-altier</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/7321351"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;The Thursday gang &amp;nbsp;(Alison, Chris Laxamana, Matt Fondiler, Gary Smith and Jenna Kim Jones) minus Jenna but with the addition of Mike Altier discusses Alison's hot date with David Wild to see Matt Nathanson, Olive Garden, Chris's banana hook, Mike's positions on hot topics, Wooki, Star Wars and so much more. We also did a round of Just Me Or Everyone&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="29008008" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/ariynbf/ARIYNBF_MBF66.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>59:28</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>The Thursday gang &amp;nbsp;(Alison, Chris Laxamana, Matt Fondiler, Gary Smith and Jenna Kim Jones) minus Jenna but with the addition of Mike Altier discusses Alison's hot date with David Wild to see Matt Nathanson, Olive Garden, Chris's banana hook,...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Brody Stevens</title>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2014 04:35:25 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">3bee3ad4c2d1844c9df2d0444bf661d3</guid>
                    <link>http://ariynbf.libsyn.com/brody-stevens</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/7309997"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Brody Stevens stops by this episode of Alison Rosen Is Your New Best Friend to talk about mental health, comedy, twitter, television, Chelsea Handler, experiences being fired, bullying, niceness, doing warmup for TV audiences, Starbucks and so much more. We also did a round of Just Me Or Everyone&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="44785067" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/ariynbf/ARIYNBF_BrodyStevens.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:32:20</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Brody Stevens stops by this episode of Alison Rosen Is Your New Best Friend to talk about mental health, comedy, twitter, television, Chelsea Handler, experiences being fired, bullying, niceness, doing warmup for TV audiences, Starbucks and so much...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Presidential Fitness Awards, Backstreet Boys, Chris's Obsessions</title>
                    <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2014 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">cbe26687f2fcde1d5bb32a658d01193e</guid>
                    <link>http://ariynbf.libsyn.com/presidential-fitness-awards-backstreet-boys-chriss-obsessions</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/7297986"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;The Thursday gang &amp;nbsp;(Alison, Chris Laxamana, Matt Fondiler, Gary Smith and Jenna Kim Jones) &amp;nbsp;discusses the presidential fitness awards, Backstreet Boys vs. 'N Sync, Chris's obsession with Hanson, Game of Thrones, interviews and so much more. We also did a round of Just Me Or Everyone&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="42859094" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/ariynbf/ARIYNBF_MBF65.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:28:19</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>The Thursday gang &amp;nbsp;(Alison, Chris Laxamana, Matt Fondiler, Gary Smith and Jenna Kim Jones) &amp;nbsp;discusses the presidential fitness awards, Backstreet Boys vs. 'N Sync, Chris's obsession with Hanson, Game of Thrones, interviews and so much more....</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Sarah Colonna</title>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2014 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">207ef21160411a630b110b417b75f007</guid>
                    <link>http://ariynbf.libsyn.com/sarah-colonna</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/7286401"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Sarah Colonna stops by this episode of Alison Rosen Is Your New Best Friend to talk about growing up in Arkansas, drill team, attempts at having a balanced life, pets, the time John Stamos followed and unfollowed her, meeting Chelsea Handler, haircuts, improv, comedy, books, relationships and so much more. We also did a round of Just Me Or Everyone&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="45132182" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/ariynbf/ARIYNBF_SarahColonna.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:33:03</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Sarah Colonna stops by this episode of Alison Rosen Is Your New Best Friend to talk about growing up in Arkansas, drill team, attempts at having a balanced life, pets, the time John Stamos followed and unfollowed her, meeting Chelsea Handler,...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Surprise Parties, The Color of Blueberries, Do All Men Rank Women?</title>
                    <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2014 06:22:25 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">df248c438503f8f8d2815755c64719fc</guid>
                    <link>http://ariynbf.libsyn.com/surprise-parties-the-color-of-blueberries-do-all-men-rank-women</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/7274718"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;The Thursday gang &amp;nbsp;(Alison, Chris Laxamana, Matt Fondiler, Gary Smith, Jenna Kim Jones and Caelan Biehn) &amp;nbsp;discusses Jenna's birthday and pizookies, Jenna's comedy special, a comment the Hollywood Hillbillies made that rattled Alison, whether blueberries are blue, Gary's surprise bday party, the Spike TV Guys Choice Awards, pot pie, ranking women and so much more. We also did a round of Just Me Or Everyone&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="38350649" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/ariynbf/ARIYNBF_MBF64.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:18:56</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>The Thursday gang &amp;nbsp;(Alison, Chris Laxamana, Matt Fondiler, Gary Smith, Jenna Kim Jones and Caelan Biehn) &amp;nbsp;discusses Jenna's birthday and pizookies, Jenna's comedy special, a comment the Hollywood Hillbillies made that rattled Alison, whether...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Theo Von</title>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2014 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">f9cb77e595af0e68f299b4cce21b493b</guid>
                    <link>http://ariynbf.libsyn.com/theo-von</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/7262739"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Comedian Theo Von stops by this episode of Alison Rosen Is Your New Best Friend to talk about his experience on Road Rules at 19, growing up in Louisiana, having a father who was 70 when he was born, religion, dating, depression, his changing views on same sex marriage, Deal with It and so much more. We also did a round of Just Me Or Everyone&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="37082497" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/ariynbf/ARIYNBF_TheoVon.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:16:17</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Comedian Theo Von stops by this episode of Alison Rosen Is Your New Best Friend to talk about his experience on Road Rules at 19, growing up in Louisiana, having a father who was 70 when he was born, religion, dating, depression, his changing views on...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Cupcakes, Pepper, Jenna's Odyssey</title>
                    <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2014 04:57:38 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">f25b541d99c51d83dcebcad11623e22f</guid>
                    <link>http://ariynbf.libsyn.com/cupcakes-pepper-jennas-odyssey</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/7250972"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;The Thursday gang &amp;nbsp;(Alison, Chris Laxamana, Matt Fondiler, Gary Smith and Jenna Kim Jones) &amp;nbsp;discusses Jenna's race against the clock to get to the studio, whether cupcakes are overly frosted, frosting in general, pepper and its merits, anemia, sweatshirts, endometriosis, abbreviations and so much more including an awesome video by the one and only Jason Dix. We also did a round of Just Me Or Everyone&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="41984596" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/ariynbf/ARIYNBF_MBF63.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:26:30</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>The Thursday gang &amp;nbsp;(Alison, Chris Laxamana, Matt Fondiler, Gary Smith and Jenna Kim Jones) &amp;nbsp;discusses Jenna's race against the clock to get to the studio, whether cupcakes are overly frosted, frosting in general, pepper and its merits,...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Mike Catherwood</title>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2014 04:15:11 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">7bb44f9b99599a775fa2927a080358ca</guid>
                    <link>http://ariynbf.libsyn.com/mike-catherwood</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/7239782"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Mike Catherwood (Loveline) stops by this episode of Alison Rosen Is Your New Best Friend to talk about sexual tension, social anxiety, overcoming various addictions, working with Dr. Drew, how he feels around Adam Carolla, soiling his pants around Adam Carolla, soiling his pants in Paris, his wife and daughter and so much more. We also did a round of Just Me Or Everyone&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="48802491" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/ariynbf/ARIYNBF_MikeCatherwood.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:40:42</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Mike Catherwood (Loveline) stops by this episode of Alison Rosen Is Your New Best Friend to talk about sexual tension, social anxiety, overcoming various addictions, working with Dr. Drew, how he feels around Adam Carolla, soiling his pants around...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>High School Reunions, Matt's Travels, Sushi Burps</title>
                    <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2014 02:26:46 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">07487e787829b000c3f4489bc4bd8ae3</guid>
                    <link>http://ariynbf.libsyn.com/high-school-reunions-matts-travels-sushi-burps</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/7226073"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;The Thursday gang &amp;nbsp;(Alison, Chris Laxamana, Matt Fondiler, Gary Smith and Jenna Kim Jones) &amp;nbsp;discusses whether Jenna should attend her high school reunion, cotillion, sushi burps, Matt's travels and so much more. We also did a round of Just Me Or Everyone&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="42321471" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/ariynbf/ARIYNBF_MBF62.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:27:12</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>The Thursday gang &amp;nbsp;(Alison, Chris Laxamana, Matt Fondiler, Gary Smith and Jenna Kim Jones) &amp;nbsp;discusses whether Jenna should attend her high school reunion, cotillion, sushi burps, Matt's travels and so much more. We also did a round of Just...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Alicia Witt (and a Chris Laxamana cameo)</title>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2014 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">556558f6ce4e56731efd8d8faac51f29</guid>
                    <link>http://ariynbf.libsyn.com/alicia-witt-and-a-chris-laxamana-cameo</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/7204818"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Alicia Witt stops by this episode of Alison Rosen Is Your New Best Friend to talk about doing everything at a young age, being home schooled, her attraction to older and then younger guys, toxic relationships, healthy relationships, Ben Folds, auditioning, dogs, coconut oil and so much more. We also did a round of Just Me Or Everyone&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="39328883" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/ariynbf/ARIYNBF_AliciaWitt.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:20:58</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Alicia Witt stops by this episode of Alison Rosen Is Your New Best Friend to talk about doing everything at a young age, being home schooled, her attraction to older and then younger guys, toxic relationships, healthy relationships, Ben Folds,...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Potatoes, Caelan Being Caelan-y, Chris's Pole Vaulting</title>
                    <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2014 04:48:54 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">ec59abd8deed5dd29e34d292163602c5</guid>
                    <link>http://ariynbf.libsyn.com/potatoes-caelan-being-caelan-y-chriss-pole-vaulting</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/7204783"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;The Thursday gang &amp;nbsp;(Alison, Chris Laxamana, Matt Fondiler, Gary Smith and Jenna Kim Jones) &amp;nbsp;discusses Caelan being Caelan-y, sneezing, pole vaulting, office supplies, nudity, whether heartrending is a word and so much more. We also did a round of Just Me Or Everyone&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="37461023" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/ariynbf/ARIYNBF_MBF61.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:17:04</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>The Thursday gang &amp;nbsp;(Alison, Chris Laxamana, Matt Fondiler, Gary Smith and Jenna Kim Jones) &amp;nbsp;discusses Caelan being Caelan-y, sneezing, pole vaulting, office supplies, nudity, whether heartrending is a word and so much more. We also did a...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Jesse Thorn and Maria Menounos</title>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2014 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">57f5e461c64cedb93289360ec6947ce1</guid>
                    <link>http://ariynbf.libsyn.com/jesse-thorn-and-maria-menounos</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/7191879"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Jesse Thorn (Bullseye, Jordan, Jesse Go!) returns to &amp;nbsp;Alison Rosen Is Your New Best Friend to talk about BoatParty.biz and cruises in general, pocket squares, his parents, love, fatherhood, sea sickness, balls, pools and so much more. We also talked to Maria Menounos about the finale of Chasing Maria Menounos. Plus a round of Just Me Or Everyone&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="55928968" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/ariynbf/ARIYNBF_JesseThornReturns.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:55:33</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Jesse Thorn (Bullseye, Jordan, Jesse Go!) returns to &amp;nbsp;Alison Rosen Is Your New Best Friend to talk about BoatParty.biz and cruises in general, pocket squares, his parents, love, fatherhood, sea sickness, balls, pools and so much more. We also...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Doppelgangers, Chris's Medical Practice, Stray Curly Fries</title>
                    <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2014 04:56:44 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">67080d6fef0f30647b8bcb7f674f27a8</guid>
                    <link>http://ariynbf.libsyn.com/doppelgangers-chriss-medical-practice-stray-curly-fries</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/7180667"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;The Thursday gang &amp;nbsp;(Alison, Chris Laxamana, Matt Fondiler, Gary Smith and Jenna Kim Jones) &amp;nbsp;discusses birthdays, traveling with Adam, doppelgangers, whether Chris is a doctor or not and so much more. We also did a round of Just Me Or Everyone&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="28032282" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/ariynbf/ARIYNBF_MBF60.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>57:26</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>The Thursday gang &amp;nbsp;(Alison, Chris Laxamana, Matt Fondiler, Gary Smith and Jenna Kim Jones) &amp;nbsp;discusses birthdays, traveling with Adam, doppelgangers, whether Chris is a doctor or not and so much more. We also did a round of Just Me Or Everyone</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Matt Atchity (and a dash of Bald Bryan)</title>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2014 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">d495994179dfb10b2cf0bb7f893d7070</guid>
                    <link>http://ariynbf.libsyn.com/matt-atchity-and-a-dash-of-bald-bryan</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/7167924"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Matt Atchity (Rotten Tomatoes) stops by this episode of Alison Rosen Is Your New Best Friend to talk about soup, his relationship with his father, Major Dad, net neutrality, paranoia, kids and the internet, having a heart condition in his late thirties, getting into online arguments, revenge porn, love and so much more. We also did a round of Just Me Or Everyone&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="50046112" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/ariynbf/ARIYNBF_Atchity.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:43:18</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Matt Atchity (Rotten Tomatoes) stops by this episode of Alison Rosen Is Your New Best Friend to talk about soup, his relationship with his father, Major Dad, net neutrality, paranoia, kids and the internet, having a heart condition in his late...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Hot Wallet Talk, Kevin Nealon's Interruption, Things Matt Finds Delicious</title>
                    <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2014 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">83262a4fd102b05d5853b5097a9bc8a0</guid>
                    <link>http://ariynbf.libsyn.com/hot-wallet-talk-kevin-nealons-interruption-things-matt-finds-delicious</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/7156714"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;The Thursday gang &amp;nbsp;(Alison, Chris Laxamana, Matt Fondiler, Gary Smith and Jenna Kim Jones) &amp;nbsp;engages in some hot wallet and key talk before being interrupted by Kevin Nealon. Also, what happens when dogs take over, Matt's use of "delicious," Jenna's neighbors, Caelan's lack of twitter and so much more. We also did a round of Just Me Or Everyone&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="43095531" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/ariynbf/ARIYNBF_MBF59.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:28:49</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>The Thursday gang &amp;nbsp;(Alison, Chris Laxamana, Matt Fondiler, Gary Smith and Jenna Kim Jones) &amp;nbsp;engages in some hot wallet and key talk before being interrupted by Kevin Nealon. Also, what happens when dogs take over, Matt's use of "delicious,"...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Dave Dameshek Returns, Again!</title>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2014 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">834c8322a63e1b654c91a31d128cc142</guid>
                    <link>http://ariynbf.libsyn.com/dave-dameshek-returns-again</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/7144290"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Dave Dameshek stops by this episode of Alison Rosen Is Your New Best Friend to talk about the three of clubs, Pete Holmes, being an introvert, Bald Bryan, TV, produce, Gary's wang and so much more. We also did a round of Just Me Or Everyone&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="49116443" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/ariynbf/ARIYNBF_Shek3.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:41:21</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Dave Dameshek stops by this episode of Alison Rosen Is Your New Best Friend to talk about the three of clubs, Pete Holmes, being an introvert, Bald Bryan, TV, produce, Gary's wang and so much more. We also did a round of Just Me Or Everyone</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Speaking of Speaking, FOMO, Fit with a Kissable Face</title>
                    <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2014 05:22:37 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">f769f1c764598e9be7efe2c11f66d206</guid>
                    <link>http://ariynbf.libsyn.com/speaking-of-speaking-fomo-fit-with-a-kissable-face</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/7132738"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;The Thursday gang &amp;nbsp;(Alison, Chris Laxamana, Matt Fondiler, Gary Smith and Jenna Kim Jones) &amp;nbsp;discusses the meaning of #FOMO, working out, Caelan as a kid, Skittles, Hugh Grant, coincidences, sneezing, hair drying and so much more. We also did a round of Just Me Or Everyone&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="40536785" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/ariynbf/ARIYNBF_MBF58.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:23:29</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>The Thursday gang &amp;nbsp;(Alison, Chris Laxamana, Matt Fondiler, Gary Smith and Jenna Kim Jones) &amp;nbsp;discusses the meaning of #FOMO, working out, Caelan as a kid, Skittles, Hugh Grant, coincidences, sneezing, hair drying and so much more. We also did...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Bert Kreischer Returns</title>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2014 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">464e6f9051bf174441a0f69b71dce80f</guid>
                    <link>http://ariynbf.libsyn.com/bert-kreischer-returns</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/7119810"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Bert Kreischer returns to Alison Rosen Is Your New Best Friend to talk about the trepidation he feels regarding the upcoming release of his book Life of the Party, Will Smith, social anxiety, testing people, the Call In Sick to Work tour, the time his dad may or may not have soiled his pants in Banana Republic, fatherhood and so much more. Plus, his wife and dad make cameos. We also did a round of Just Me Or Everyone&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="73823265" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/ariynbf/ARIYNBF_BertKreischerReturns.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>02:32:50</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Bert Kreischer returns to Alison Rosen Is Your New Best Friend to talk about the trepidation he feels regarding the upcoming release of his book Life of the Party, Will Smith, social anxiety, testing people, the Call In Sick to Work tour, the time his...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>The Ego No Es Matt's Amigo, Chris Has Otter Hair, 'Sup with Pumpernickel</title>
                    <pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2014 04:08:07 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">c96576c6a80139d843c2b27f5da58332</guid>
                    <link>http://ariynbf.libsyn.com/the-ego-no-es-matts-amigo-chris-has-otter-hair-sup-with-pumpernickel</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/7106724"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;The Thursday gang &amp;nbsp;(Alison, Chris Laxamana, Matt Fondiler, Gary Smith and Jenna Kim Jones) &amp;nbsp;discusses Alison's Road Hard shoot, Chris's otter hair, nicknames, letting comments get to you, when people project on you, Matt's philosophy, bread, workouts and so much more. &amp;nbsp;We also did a round of Just Me Or Everyone&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="40348285" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/ariynbf/ARIYNBF_MBF57.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:23:05</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>The Thursday gang &amp;nbsp;(Alison, Chris Laxamana, Matt Fondiler, Gary Smith and Jenna Kim Jones) &amp;nbsp;discusses Alison's Road Hard shoot, Chris's otter hair, nicknames, letting comments get to you, when people project on you, Matt's philosophy, bread,...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Alison Agosti</title>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2014 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">6db0d63ddb28dad3598cdf6029851902</guid>
                    <link>http://ariynbf.libsyn.com/alison-agosti</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/7095616"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Alison Agosti stops by this episode of Alison Rosen Is Your New Best Friend to talk about writing for Late Night with Seth Meyers, doing punch up, hiking, Felicity, sketch comedy, her relationship with her parents, dogs and so much more. We also did a round of Just Me Or Everyone&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="44624780" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/ariynbf/ARIYNBF_AlisonAgosti.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:32:00</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Alison Agosti stops by this episode of Alison Rosen Is Your New Best Friend to talk about writing for Late Night with Seth Meyers, doing punch up, hiking, Felicity, sketch comedy, her relationship with her parents, dogs and so much more. We also did a...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Thursday Anniversary, Road Hard Wardrobe, Chris Gets a New Fridge Friend</title>
                    <pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2014 03:58:45 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">f8c6b88b710311d12fc2f24f88d05ab4</guid>
                    <link>http://ariynbf.libsyn.com/thursday-anniversary-road-hard-wardrobe-chris-gets-a-new-fridge-friend</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/7085004"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;The Thursday gang &amp;nbsp;(Alison, Chris Laxamana, Matt Fondiler, Gary Smith and Jenna Kim Jones) &amp;nbsp;celebrates what possibly might be the anniversary of the Thursday show and discusses an array of topics including waking up early and people who have a problem with people who don't wake up early, Alison's dealings with Road Hard's wardrobe department, clothes in general, Chris wanting to be friends with his refrigerator delivery man, how to rinse your hair in the shower, thongs, HSPs and so much more. We also did a round of Just Me Or Everyone&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="33516533" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/ariynbf/ARIYNBF_MBF56.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:08:51</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>The Thursday gang &amp;nbsp;(Alison, Chris Laxamana, Matt Fondiler, Gary Smith and Jenna Kim Jones) &amp;nbsp;celebrates what possibly might be the anniversary of the Thursday show and discusses an array of topics including waking up early and people who have...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Jack Burditt</title>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2014 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">f888312e3990471401aa6bed02f132c0</guid>
                    <link>http://ariynbf.libsyn.com/jack-burditt</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/7072090"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Jack Burditt (TV producer/writer extraordinaire; The Mindy Project, 30 Rock) stopped by this episode of Alison Rosen Is Your New Best Friend to talk about working on Tina Fey's new series, sobriety, how he met his wife, fatherhood, his days as a music critic, Six Flags, Lockheed, writing rooms onFrasier, Just Shoot Me and 30 Rock and so much more. We also spoke about grief, mourning, therapy and the family tragedy he experienced two and a half years. And we did a round of Just Me Or Everyone&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="54896545" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/ariynbf/ARIYNBF_JackBurditt.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:53:24</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Jack Burditt (TV producer/writer extraordinaire; The Mindy Project, 30 Rock) stopped by this episode of Alison Rosen Is Your New Best Friend to talk about working on Tina Fey's new series, sobriety, how he met his wife, fatherhood, his days as a music...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Matt's Flip Flop Budget, Dry Shampoo and Annoying Yogurt Guy</title>
                    <pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2014 05:35:27 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">8531aebb9fa63ccb740fcdda4f2a92aa</guid>
                    <link>http://ariynbf.libsyn.com/matts-flip-flop-budget-dry-shampoo-and-annoying-yogurt-guy</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/7061528"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;The Thursday gang &amp;nbsp;(Alison, Chris Laxamana, Matt Fondiler, Gary Smith and Jenna Kim Jones) &amp;nbsp;discusses churros, hand peeling, ointment, shopping. Matt's flip flop budget, eggplant rollatini, tupperware, food items to avoid at various eateries, Cross Fit and so much more. We also did a round of Just Me Or Everyone&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="38454512" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/ariynbf/ARIYNBF_MBF55.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:19:09</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>The Thursday gang &amp;nbsp;(Alison, Chris Laxamana, Matt Fondiler, Gary Smith and Jenna Kim Jones) &amp;nbsp;discusses churros, hand peeling, ointment, shopping. Matt's flip flop budget, eggplant rollatini, tupperware, food items to avoid at various...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Bald Bryan and Christie Bishop</title>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2014 05:07:36 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">dec8a7ee9b209bc088ea441e8e699935</guid>
                    <link>http://ariynbf.libsyn.com/bald-bryan-and-christie-bishop</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/7050143"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Bryan Bishop and Christie Bishop stop by this episode of Alison Rosen Is Your New Best Friend to talk about Bryan's upcoming cancer memoir Shrinkage, how cancer affects family relationships, being in the caretaker role, fear, openness, being of service, poo and so much more. We also did a round of Just Me Or Everyone&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="44131861" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/ariynbf/ARIYNBF_TheBishops.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:30:58</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Bryan Bishop and Christie Bishop stop by this episode of Alison Rosen Is Your New Best Friend to talk about Bryan's upcoming cancer memoir Shrinkage, how cancer affects family relationships, being in the caretaker role, fear, openness, being of...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>The Boom Off, Jenna's Special, How We All Lost Our Virginity</title>
                    <pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2014 06:09:43 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">2f111de78c6cee8aa10c7ba12546e8d1</guid>
                    <link>http://ariynbf.libsyn.com/the-boom-off-jennas-special-how-we-all-lost-our-virginity</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/7038218"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;The Thursday gang &amp;nbsp;(Alison, Chris Laxamana, Matt Fondiler, Gary Smith and Jenna Kim Jones) &amp;nbsp;discusses Jenna's upcoming comedy special, Jack Mormons, Matt's "Boom Off," various TV shows and musicals, bobos and how everyone lost his or her virginity. We also did a round of Just Me Or Everyone&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="46887466" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/ariynbf/ARIYNBF_MBF54.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:36:43</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>The Thursday gang &amp;nbsp;(Alison, Chris Laxamana, Matt Fondiler, Gary Smith and Jenna Kim Jones) &amp;nbsp;discusses Jenna's upcoming comedy special, Jack Mormons, Matt's "Boom Off," various TV shows and musicals, bobos and how everyone lost his or her...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Hampton Yount</title>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2014 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">66a856103ffde615e453f16f1f37b3f6</guid>
                    <link>http://ariynbf.libsyn.com/hampton-yount</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/7025032"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Hampton Yount stops by this episode of Alison Rosen Is Your New Best Friend to talk about his name, growing up the son of a gem dealer, his dad's stories, working on Ridiculousness, how he got into comedy, lies, showering, email rants, breaking teachers and so much more. We also did a round of Just Me Or Everyone&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="40243732" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/ariynbf/ARIYNBF_HamptonYount.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:22:52</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Hampton Yount stops by this episode of Alison Rosen Is Your New Best Friend to talk about his name, growing up the son of a gem dealer, his dad's stories, working on Ridiculousness, how he got into comedy, lies, showering, email rants, breaking...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Alison Attempts Yoga, Chris Resets a Stare, Gary Unpacks</title>
                    <pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2014 04:10:21 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">0dd32deb09c4b83f6f4115d6daeb8c2c</guid>
                    <link>http://ariynbf.libsyn.com/alison-attempts-yoga-chris-resets-a-stare-gary-unpacks</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/7012730"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;The Thursday gang (Alison, Chris Laxamana, Matt Fondiler, Gary Smith and Jenna Kim Jones) discusses Alison's first attempt at yoga, Chris's knowledge of fancy foodstuffs, nodding to "reset" a stare, crazy people in the neighborhood, shopping carts, moving and unpacking, tennis and so much more. We also did a round of Just Me Or Everyone&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="41502271" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/ariynbf/ARIYNBF_MBF53.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:25:30</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>The Thursday gang (Alison, Chris Laxamana, Matt Fondiler, Gary Smith and Jenna Kim Jones) discusses Alison's first attempt at yoga, Chris's knowledge of fancy foodstuffs, nodding to "reset" a stare, crazy people in the neighborhood, shopping carts,...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Grace Helbig, Hannah Hart and Mamrie Hart</title>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2014 03:34:07 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">e01137d3a77733801e6271984bc744a1</guid>
                    <link>http://ariynbf.libsyn.com/grace-helbig-hannah-hart-and-mamrie-hart</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/7000165"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Grace Helbig, Hannah Hart and Mamrie Hart of Camp Takota stop by this episode of Alison Rosen Is Your New Best Friend to talk about how they met, summer camp movies, relinquishing control, drunken uploads, how you'd introduce someone with no arms or legs, moving to Los Angeles, burning chinas and more. We also did a round of Just Me Or Everyone&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="30098463" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/ariynbf/ARIYNBF_CampTakota.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:01:44</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Grace Helbig, Hannah Hart and Mamrie Hart of Camp Takota stop by this episode of Alison Rosen Is Your New Best Friend to talk about how they met, summer camp movies, relinquishing control, drunken uploads, how you'd introduce someone with no arms or...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Alison's Wedding, Matt's Bathroom Politics, A Chance to Be Aggressively Freaked</title>
                    <pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2014 03:58:14 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">f12ad26146ad3866ac5133878e2e3d3d</guid>
                    <link>http://ariynbf.libsyn.com/alisons-wedding-matts-bathroom-politics-a-chance-to-be-aggressively-freaked</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/6985613"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;The Thursday gang &amp;nbsp;(Alison, Chris Laxamana, Matt Fondiler, Gary Smith and Jenna Kim Jones) &amp;nbsp;discuss Alison's wedding, the way Chris and Daniel (Alison's husband) have similar voices, frustration with parents, Matt moving in with his girlfriend, bathroom politics, missing Yosicles, Jenna's upcoming special and so much more. We also did a round of Just Me Or Everyone&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="39227319" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/ariynbf/ARIYNBF_MBF52.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:20:45</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>The Thursday gang &amp;nbsp;(Alison, Chris Laxamana, Matt Fondiler, Gary Smith and Jenna Kim Jones) &amp;nbsp;discuss Alison's wedding, the way Chris and Daniel (Alison's husband) have similar voices, frustration with parents, Matt moving in with his...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Nikki Glaser</title>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2014 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">8296c90726d3eb6c28333936994b1d94</guid>
                    <link>http://ariynbf.libsyn.com/nikki-glaser</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/6968308"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Nikki Glaser stops by this episode of Alison Rosen Is Your New Best Friend to talk about working on MTV, hecklers, high school, sex, relationships, anorexia, rapidly going from 155 lbs to 98 lbs, feeling like a fraud, discovering comedy, therapy and so much more. We also did a round of Just Me Or Everyone&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="48298432" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/ariynbf/ARIYNBF_NikkiGlaser.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:39:39</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Nikki Glaser stops by this episode of Alison Rosen Is Your New Best Friend to talk about working on MTV, hecklers, high school, sex, relationships, anorexia, rapidly going from 155 lbs to 98 lbs, feeling like a fraud, discovering comedy, therapy and...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>My Fiance Daniel Week Continues! Plus Speaker Scams and Fires</title>
                    <pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2014 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">d757934b06b7a09858d5677e5a036cea</guid>
                    <link>http://ariynbf.libsyn.com/my-fiance-daniel-week-continues-plus-speaker-scams-and-fires</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/6952134"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;The Thursday gang &amp;nbsp;(Alison, Chris Laxamana, Matt Fondiler, Gary Smith and Jenna Kim Jones) &amp;nbsp;plus Daniel Quantz (Alison's new husband) talks about makeup, moms, first dates, fires, speaker scams, pants and so much more. We also did a round of Just Me Or Everyone&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="33538476" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/ariynbf/ARIYNBF_MBF51.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:08:54</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>The Thursday gang &amp;nbsp;(Alison, Chris Laxamana, Matt Fondiler, Gary Smith and Jenna Kim Jones) &amp;nbsp;plus Daniel Quantz (Alison's new husband) talks about makeup, moms, first dates, fires, speaker scams, pants and so much more. We also did a round of...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Daniel Quantz</title>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2014 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">9074a316e6ad5ee693a9b25f95f96db5</guid>
                    <link>http://ariynbf.libsyn.com/daniel-quantz</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/6923876"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Daniel Quantz (Alison's brand &amp;nbsp;new husband) stops by this episode of Alison Rosen Is Your New Best Friend to set the record straight on a few things and talk about how he and Alison met. We also did a round of Just Me Or Everyone&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="44154785" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/ariynbf/ARIYNBF_MyFianceDaniel.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:31:01</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Daniel Quantz (Alison's brand &amp;nbsp;new husband) stops by this episode of Alison Rosen Is Your New Best Friend to set the record straight on a few things and talk about how he and Alison met. We also did a round of Just Me Or Everyone</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>The Almost Seduction of Matt, Plus Linens and Bisque</title>
                    <pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2014 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">cc6f1483482c85bef95af1338aea67c6</guid>
                    <link>http://ariynbf.libsyn.com/the-almost-seduction-of-matt-plus-linens-and-bisque</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/6918250"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;The Thursday gang &amp;nbsp;(Alison, Chris Laxamana, Matt Fondiler, Gary Smith and Jenna Kim Jones) &amp;nbsp;talks about bisque versus soup, Chris's cooking, sharks, linens, name changes, not having the appropriate number of friends, hot older women and pee boners. We also did a round of Just Me Or Everyone&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="37955260" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/ariynbf/ARIYNBF_MBF50.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:18:06</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>The Thursday gang &amp;nbsp;(Alison, Chris Laxamana, Matt Fondiler, Gary Smith and Jenna Kim Jones) &amp;nbsp;talks about bisque versus soup, Chris's cooking, sharks, linens, name changes, not having the appropriate number of friends, hot older women and pee...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Lynette Carolla Returns</title>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2014 05:52:37 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">962daade802c579b946a228b33033da3</guid>
                    <link>http://ariynbf.libsyn.com/lynette-carolla-returns</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/6906427"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Lynette Carolla makes a return appearance on Alison Rosen Is Your New Best Friend to talk about making a marriage work, drums, the 10th Avenue Podcast featuring conversations with fellow Bruce Springsteen fans, the new house, TV show trends, Natalia and Adam, Natalia and Olga, the Josh Gardner episode, For Crying Out Loud and so much more. We also did a round of Just Me Or Everyone&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="41547201" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/ariynbf/ARIYNBF_LynetteReturns.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:25:35</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Lynette Carolla makes a return appearance on Alison Rosen Is Your New Best Friend to talk about making a marriage work, drums, the 10th Avenue Podcast featuring conversations with fellow Bruce Springsteen fans, the new house, TV show trends, Natalia...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Spiders, Pizza, Assistant Jay</title>
                    <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2014 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">42f6fc88d47984ef9d3c7c560a48dfb3</guid>
                    <link>http://ariynbf.libsyn.com/spiders-pizza-assistant-jay</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/6890942"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;The Thursday gang &amp;nbsp;(Alison, Chris Laxamana, Matt Fondiler, Gary Smith and Jenna Kim Jones) minus Matt but plus Jay, talks about the barcycle, guitar lessons, dude manicures and pedicures, wedding rings, sore throats, retainers, regional dialects, spiders, pizza and so much more. We also did a round of Just Me Or Everyone&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="33760622" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/ariynbf/ARIYNBF_MBF49.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:09:22</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>The Thursday gang &amp;nbsp;(Alison, Chris Laxamana, Matt Fondiler, Gary Smith and Jenna Kim Jones) minus Matt but plus Jay, talks about the barcycle, guitar lessons, dude manicures and pedicures, wedding rings, sore throats, retainers, regional dialects,...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Mark Geragos</title>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2014 05:08:30 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">2c6b53f3a98c72d9337824d98dd2b5fb</guid>
                    <link>http://ariynbf.libsyn.com/mark-geragos</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/6877998"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Defense attorney Mark Geragos (Mistrial: An Inside Look at How the Criminal Justice System Works... and Sometimes Doesn't) stops by this episode of Alison Rosen Is Your New Best Friend to talk the little known Robin Hood aspect of his practice, choosing law over religion, getting arrested at his bachelor party, Alison's wedding, why the legal system is rigged, the death penalty, anarchy, how he met his wife, music, his approach to conflict and so much more. We also did a round of Just Me Or Everyone&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="38988809" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/ariynbf/ARIYNBF_Mark_Geragos.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:20:15</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Defense attorney Mark Geragos (Mistrial: An Inside Look at How the Criminal Justice System Works... and Sometimes Doesn't) stops by this episode of Alison Rosen Is Your New Best Friend to talk the little known Robin Hood aspect of his practice,...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Wedding Cake Flavor Poll, Gary's Favorite Emoji, Sleep Positions</title>
                    <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2014 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">c95006251d86f9c67881ad38976df3a4</guid>
                    <link>http://ariynbf.libsyn.com/wedding-cake-flavor-poll-garys-favorite-emoji-sleep-positions</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/6862782"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: Georgia, 'Times New Roman', 'Bitstream Charter', Times, serif; font-size: small;"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height: 19px;"&gt;The Thursday gang (Alison, Chris Laxamana, Matt Fondiler, Gary Smith and Jenna Kim Jones) talks about wedding cake flavors, wedding registries, marathon lovemaking, Mark Geragos, The Lego Movie, Her, Chris's former weight, beds, pillows and more. &amp;nbsp;We also did a round of Just Me Or Everyone&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="36076951" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/ariynbf/ARIYNBF_MBF48.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:14:11</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>The Thursday gang (Alison, Chris Laxamana, Matt Fondiler, Gary Smith and Jenna Kim Jones) talks about wedding cake flavors, wedding registries, marathon lovemaking, Mark Geragos, The Lego Movie, Her, Chris's former weight, beds, pillows and more....</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>David Wild</title>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2014 04:30:35 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">b29617df5e747b35d552a68e665e7d6a</guid>
                    <link>http://ariynbf.libsyn.com/david-wild</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/6848811"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Writer David Wild, hot on the heels of his Beatles Tribute and Grammy's successes, stops by this episode of Alison Rosen Is Your New Best Friend to talk about how he got into journalism, Rolling Stone, writing for TV, Friends, respecting music to a fault, celebrity and so much more. We also did a round of Just Me Or Everyone&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="46669645" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/ariynbf/ARIYNBF_DavidWild.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:36:15</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Writer David Wild, hot on the heels of his Beatles Tribute and Grammy's successes, stops by this episode of Alison Rosen Is Your New Best Friend to talk about how he got into journalism, Rolling Stone, writing for TV, Friends, respecting music to a...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Matt's Hot Pottery Date, Gary's Facial and an Epiphany</title>
                    <pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2014 05:25:08 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">83f3a124b89467b69fffa5aefa53fba8</guid>
                    <link>http://ariynbf.libsyn.com/matts-hot-pottery-date-garys-facial-and-an-epiphany</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/6827519"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;The Thursday gang (Alison, Chris Laxamana, Matt Fondiler, Gary Smith and Jenna Kim Jones) talks about facials, Adam changing the schedule, Woody Allen and Alison's epiphany, Matt's non-apology, Fondilering, Color Me Mine, when to text after meeting someone or going on a first date, Valentine's Day, caffeine and Mormons and so much more. &amp;nbsp;We also did a round of Just Me Or Everyone&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="40998421" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/ariynbf/ARIYNBF_MBF47.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:24:27</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>The Thursday gang (Alison, Chris Laxamana, Matt Fondiler, Gary Smith and Jenna Kim Jones) talks about facials, Adam changing the schedule, Woody Allen and Alison's epiphany, Matt's non-apology, Fondilering, Color Me Mine, when to text after meeting...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Josh Gardner</title>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2014 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">1eb9d56a842a6cf20609ace8065c1621</guid>
                    <link>http://ariynbf.libsyn.com/josh-gardner</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/6808914"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Josh Gardner (AKA Deaf Frat Guy) stopped by this episode of Alison Rosen Is Your New Best Friend to talk about escaping to Maine, his recent travels, frostbite, fatherhood, pimps, Gerhard Reinke's Wanderlust, meeting his wife, stardom and so much more. We also did a round of Just Me Or Everyone&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="36326409" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/ariynbf/ARIYNBF_JoshGardner.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:14:43</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Josh Gardner (AKA Deaf Frat Guy) stopped by this episode of Alison Rosen Is Your New Best Friend to talk about escaping to Maine, his recent travels, frostbite, fatherhood, pimps, Gerhard Reinke's Wanderlust, meeting his wife, stardom and so much...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Pancake Hands, Peeing On Stage, Woody Allen</title>
                    <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2014 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">8014a3ed442883e4cbae7e8d302bf5d7</guid>
                    <link>http://ariynbf.libsyn.com/pancake-hands-peeing-on-stage-woody-allen</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/6790380"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;The Thursday gang (Alison, Chris Laxamana, Matt Fondiler, Gary Smith and Jenna Kim Jones) talks about short term carb memory, words Chris can no longer use, Puff the Magic Dragon, Woody Allen and Dylan Farrow, working retail, peeing on stage, pancake hands and so much more. &amp;nbsp;We also did a round of Just Me Or Everyone&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="33922581" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/ariynbf/ARIYNBF_MBF46.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:09:42</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>The Thursday gang (Alison, Chris Laxamana, Matt Fondiler, Gary Smith and Jenna Kim Jones) talks about short term carb memory, words Chris can no longer use, Puff the Magic Dragon, Woody Allen and Dylan Farrow, working retail, peeing on stage, pancake...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Paul Scheer</title>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2014 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">2dffff7e8a69e689a0da9721d3b152d3</guid>
                    <link>http://ariynbf.libsyn.com/paul-scheer</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/6773059"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Paul Scheer stopped by this episode of Alison Rosen Is Your New Best Friend to talk about the shame he feels admitting he's from Long Island, working at Blockbuster, his cool comedy dad, his relationship with his parents, NYU, Chicago, falling in love, voiceover work, imminent fatherhood, his podcast How Did This Get Made and so much more. &amp;nbsp;We also did a round of Just Me Or Everyone&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="38076822" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/ariynbf/ARIYNBF_PaulScheer.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:18:21</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Paul Scheer stopped by this episode of Alison Rosen Is Your New Best Friend to talk about the shame he feels admitting he's from Long Island, working at Blockbuster, his cool comedy dad, his relationship with his parents, NYU, Chicago, falling in...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>A Doodle Array, The Other Chris Laxamana, Celebs with Soft Handshakes</title>
                    <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2014 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">7572c5972f9e7c969e22ddb9d5c133fb</guid>
                    <link>http://ariynbf.libsyn.com/a-doodle-array-the-other-chris-laxamana-celebs-with-soft-handshakes</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/6755672"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;The Thursday gang (Alison, Chris Laxamana, Matt Fondiler, Gary Smith and Jenna Kim Jones) talks about varieties of doodles, wedding planning stress, why Chris would be an awful bride, misunderstandings, whether Russell Brand or Leonardo Dicaprio has slept with more women, the other Chris Laxamana, Matt Crack, Quesaritos and so much more. We also did a round of Just Me Or Everyone&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="37135015" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/ariynbf/ARIYNBF_MBF45.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:16:24</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>The Thursday gang (Alison, Chris Laxamana, Matt Fondiler, Gary Smith and Jenna Kim Jones) talks about varieties of doodles, wedding planning stress, why Chris would be an awful bride, misunderstandings, whether Russell Brand or Leonardo Dicaprio has...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Jake and Amir</title>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2014 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">e5c0eee4fa0bfa2f044f07793d789338</guid>
                    <link>http://ariynbf.libsyn.com/jake-and-amir</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/6736928"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Jake Hurwitz and Amir Blumenfeld (CollegeHumor, JakeandAmir.com, If I Were You) stop by this episode of Alison Rosen Is Your New Best Friend to talk about doling out advice on their new podcast If I Were You, how they met, working for College Humor, web videos, relationships, being disconnected from your feelings, their new TBS pilot produced by Ed Helms, relocating to Los Angeles and so much more. &amp;nbsp;We also did a round of Just Me Or Everyone and HGFY.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="47882145" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/ariynbf/ARIYNBF_JakeAndAmir.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:38:47</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Jake Hurwitz and Amir Blumenfeld (CollegeHumor, JakeandAmir.com, If I Were You) stop by this episode of Alison Rosen Is Your New Best Friend to talk about doling out advice on their new podcast If I Were You, how they met, working for College Humor,...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Popsicle Update, Punchability, Microwaves</title>
                    <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2014 06:26:49 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">ec18ab502ac06441c01fde01b40413f6</guid>
                    <link>http://ariynbf.libsyn.com/popsicle-update-punchability-microwaves</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/6718011"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;The Thursday gang (Alison, Chris Laxamana, Matt Fondiler, Gary Smith and Jenna Kim Jones) discuss an exciting popsicle update, smoothies, positive reinforcement, cheating, cold feet, ratchet microwaves and so much more. We also did a round of Just Me Or Everyone&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="35767871" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/ariynbf/ARIYNBF_MBF44.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:13:33</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>The Thursday gang (Alison, Chris Laxamana, Matt Fondiler, Gary Smith and Jenna Kim Jones) discuss an exciting popsicle update, smoothies, positive reinforcement, cheating, cold feet, ratchet microwaves and so much more. We also did a round of Just Me...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Pete Holmes Returns</title>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2014 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">375ad4ae8739280b5c0c7ce2a2aca81f</guid>
                    <link>http://ariynbf.libsyn.com/pete-holmes-returns</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/6699515"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Pete Holmes, who was the first guest ever on Alison Rosen Is Your New Best Friend returns to talk about getting the news The Pete Holmes Show will be renewed, corporate gigs in Arizona, swearing on TV, rejecting certain jackets, fashion, orange pants, Conan, flirting, old man jobs, "wash my damn towels," surfing, relationships, STDs, sex, monogamy, You Made It Weird and so much more. We also did a round of Just Me Or Everyone&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="47662780" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/ariynbf/ARIYNBF_PeteHolmes3.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:38:20</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Pete Holmes, who was the first guest ever on Alison Rosen Is Your New Best Friend returns to talk about getting the news The Pete Holmes Show will be renewed, corporate gigs in Arizona, swearing on TV, rejecting certain jackets, fashion, orange pants,...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Cold Feet, Popsicles, The Mighty Ducks</title>
                    <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2014 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">e99401b88fd6084c0f0c0e1bb662096c</guid>
                    <link>http://ariynbf.libsyn.com/cold-feet-popsicles-the-mighty-ducks</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/6680341"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;The Thursday gang (Alison, Chris Laxamana, Matt Fondiler, Gary Smith and Jenna Kim Jones) discuss Alison's wedding freakout, Jenna's super long trek, Gary's holiday, head scabs, popsicles, The Mighty Ducks and so much more. We also did a round of Just Me Or Everyone&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="37337098" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/ariynbf/ARIYNBF_MBF_043.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:16:49</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>The Thursday gang (Alison, Chris Laxamana, Matt Fondiler, Gary Smith and Jenna Kim Jones) discuss Alison's wedding freakout, Jenna's super long trek, Gary's holiday, head scabs, popsicles, The Mighty Ducks and so much more. We also did a round of Just...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Mike Dawson</title>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2014 06:16:28 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">7725c7025d3d40fac8bfd0e7621559a7</guid>
                    <link>http://ariynbf.libsyn.com/mike-dawson</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/6664542"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Mike Dawson (Adam Carolla Show announcer and engineer) stops by this episode of Alison Rosen Is Your New Best Friend to talk about his childhood, his early fascination with radio, sickness, his new years resolution to not be a dick, how he started working with Adam Carolla, negotiating, web sites, weddings, his new podcast (Front of House Pod), farting and so much more. We also did a round of Just Me Or Everyone&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="38977106" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/ariynbf/ARIYNBF_Dawson.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:20:14</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Mike Dawson (Adam Carolla Show announcer and engineer) stops by this episode of Alison Rosen Is Your New Best Friend to talk about his childhood, his early fascination with radio, sickness, his new years resolution to not be a dick, how he started...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Hillicopters, Badass Chris, Cheerio Breath</title>
                    <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2014 06:56:58 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">daca2b34ba1868372b8a2250129b8e39</guid>
                    <link>http://ariynbf.libsyn.com/hillicopters-badass-chris-cheerio-breath</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/6645710"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;The Thursday gang (Alison, Chris Laxamana, Matt Fondiler, Gary Smith and Jenna Kim Jones) discuss Alison's ice skating confession/betrayal, Matt's helicopter disaster, Chris's surreal street fight, motion sickness, grocery stores, Cheerio breath and a &amp;nbsp;sweet video sent in by the father of a fan. We also did a round of Just Me Or Everyone&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="29324194" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/ariynbf/ARIYNBF_MBF_042.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:00:07</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>The Thursday gang (Alison, Chris Laxamana, Matt Fondiler, Gary Smith and Jenna Kim Jones) discuss Alison's ice skating confession/betrayal, Matt's helicopter disaster, Chris's surreal street fight, motion sickness, grocery stores, Cheerio breath and a...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Jen Kirkman</title>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2014 04:42:04 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">f155da787b78ed40e7ff22711ba0fda9</guid>
                    <link>http://ariynbf.libsyn.com/jen-kirkman</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/6629048"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Jen Kirkman (Chelsea Lately) stops by this episode of Alison Rosen Is Your New Best Friend to talk about her book, I Can Barely Take Care of Myself (Tales from a Happy Life Without Kids), dentists, veneers, hiatus, her marriage and divorce, Chelsea Handler, twitter, roller coasters,The Day After, her podcast I Seem Fun, style, wills, her parents and so much more. We also did a round of Just Me Or Everyone&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="43150638" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/ariynbf/ARIYNBF_JenKirkman.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:28:56</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Jen Kirkman (Chelsea Lately) stops by this episode of Alison Rosen Is Your New Best Friend to talk about her book, I Can Barely Take Care of Myself (Tales from a Happy Life Without Kids), dentists, veneers, hiatus, her marriage and divorce, Chelsea...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>New Year's Resolutions, Fruit Cake, Welcome to 2014</title>
                    <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2014 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">f31a87a1e3c22221f5b5d08621d5996e</guid>
                    <link>http://ariynbf.libsyn.com/new-year-s-resolutions-fruit-cake-welcome-to-2014</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/6562794"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Last show of the year! The Thursday gang (Alison, Chris Laxamana, Matt Fondiler,Gary Smith and Jenna Kim Jones) discuss their New Year's resolutions and Alison puts her foot in her mouth. See you in 2014!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="15149107" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/ariynbf/ARIYNBF_MBF_041.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>30:35</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Last show of the year! The Thursday gang (Alison, Chris Laxamana, Matt Fondiler,Gary Smith and Jenna Kim Jones) discuss their New Year's resolutions and Alison puts her foot in her mouth. See you in 2014!</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Special Thursday on Monday episode!</title>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2013 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">f96bc3834737cbf649d63d4411a021d9</guid>
                    <link>http://ariynbf.libsyn.com/special-thursday-on-monday-episode</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/6562783"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Special Thursday on Monday group episode! The Thursday gang (Alison, Chris Laxamana, Matt Fondiler, Gary Smith and Jenna Kim Jones) discuss their New Year's plans, vacations, Chris's roommate and more. It was delightful and this description isn't doing it justice. Hi!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="13550414" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/ariynbf/ARIYNBF_MBF_040.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>27:16</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Special Thursday on Monday group episode! The Thursday gang (Alison, Chris Laxamana, Matt Fondiler, Gary Smith and Jenna Kim Jones) discuss their New Year's plans, vacations, Chris's roommate and more. It was delightful and this description isn't...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Chris's Gambling, Christmas Plans, Weird Stuff in Your Cart</title>
                    <pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2013 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">82fab0c26c24ecb0d82ced707117f936</guid>
                    <link>http://ariynbf.libsyn.com/chris-s-gambling-christmas-plans-weird-stuff-in-your-cart</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/6562759"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;The Thursday gang (Alison, Chris Laxamana, Matt Fondiler, Gary Smith and Jenna Kim Jones) discuss discovering items in your Amazon cart THAT YOU DIDN'T PUT THERE, snooping, Christmas plans, Chris's gambling, &amp;nbsp;Beyonce and more. We also did a round of Just Me Or Everyone&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="28646473" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/ariynbf/ARIYNBF_MBF_039.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>58:43</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>The Thursday gang (Alison, Chris Laxamana, Matt Fondiler, Gary Smith and Jenna Kim Jones) discuss discovering items in your Amazon cart THAT YOU DIDN'T PUT THERE, snooping, Christmas plans, Chris's gambling, &amp;nbsp;Beyonce and more. We also did a round...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Adam Ray</title>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2013 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">aaf4def9199c8b16023935cfdfce9477</guid>
                    <link>http://ariynbf.libsyn.com/adam-ray</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/6560934"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Adam Ray (About Last Night podcast) stops by this episode of Alison Rosen Is Your New Best Friend to talk about his recent awful haircut, bummer couples, growing up in Seattle, working at Universal Studios, his parents getting divorced, dragons and so much more. &amp;nbsp; We also did a round of HGFY and Just Me Or Everyone&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="47010282" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/ariynbf/ARIYNBF_AdamRay.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:36:58</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Adam Ray (About Last Night podcast) stops by this episode of Alison Rosen Is Your New Best Friend to talk about his recent awful haircut, bummer couples, growing up in Seattle, working at Universal Studios, his parents getting divorced, dragons and so...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Ice Skating, Field Trips and Adam's Pep Talk</title>
                    <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2013 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">49eb59ea9224dc608eb6d900be64aea1</guid>
                    <link>http://ariynbf.libsyn.com/ice-skating-field-trips-and-adam-s-pep-talk</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/6556696"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;The Thursday gang (Alison, Chris Laxamana, Matt Fondiler, Gary Smith and Jenna Kim Jones) discuss carbs, ice skating, Gary's hockey revelation, potential field trips, &amp;nbsp;Adam's pep talk, working a room and more. We also did a round of Just Me Or Everyone&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="27614532" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/ariynbf/ARIYNBF_MBF_038.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>56:34</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>The Thursday gang (Alison, Chris Laxamana, Matt Fondiler, Gary Smith and Jenna Kim Jones) discuss carbs, ice skating, Gary's hockey revelation, potential field trips, &amp;nbsp;Adam's pep talk, working a room and more. We also did a round of Just Me Or...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Kurt Braunohler</title>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2013 05:48:24 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">bb3617726aaadaf27f4565471a9cf15c</guid>
                    <link>http://ariynbf.libsyn.com/kurt-braunohler</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/6544464"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="p1"&gt;Kurt Braunohler stops by this episode of Alison Rosen Is Your New Best Friend to talk about SPF, comedy, pitching shows, relationships, Kristin Schaal, the three month fuck-a-thon, Lauren Cook, mopeds, family, his podcast The K Ohle and so much more.&amp;nbsp; We also did a round of Just Me Or Everyone&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="39851895" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/ariynbf/ARIYNBF_2XX_KurtBraunohler.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:22:03</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Kurt Braunohler stops by this episode of Alison Rosen Is Your New Best Friend to talk about SPF, comedy, pitching shows, relationships, Kristin Schaal, the three month fuck-a-thon, Lauren Cook, mopeds, family, his podcast The K Ohle and so much...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Update on Chris's Awful Neighbor, Plastic Spoon Mouth, Human Spam</title>
                    <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2013 07:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">9acefaf452457d78b018a064fa18897b</guid>
                    <link>http://ariynbf.libsyn.com/update-on-chris-s-awful-neighbor-plastic-spoon-mouth-human-spam</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/6529774"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;The Thursday gang (Alison, Chris Laxamana, Matt Fondiler, Gary Smith and Jenna Kim Jones) discuss an update regarding Chris's awful neighbor then talk about Chris's "thing," how to be assertive, more shower talk, plastic spoon mouth and more. We also did a round of Just Me Or Everyone&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="29377130" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/ariynbf/ARIYNBF_MBF_037.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:00:14</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>The Thursday gang (Alison, Chris Laxamana, Matt Fondiler, Gary Smith and Jenna Kim Jones) discuss an update regarding Chris's awful neighbor then talk about Chris's "thing," how to be assertive, more shower talk, plastic spoon mouth and more. We also...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Jim O'Heir</title>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2013 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">ba5ab69e4671d06b3103dcb4a39cdb3f</guid>
                    <link>http://ariynbf.libsyn.com/jim-o-heir</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/6509662"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Jim O'Heir (Parks and Recreation) stops by this episode of Alison Rosen Is Your New Best Friend to talk about butt-dialing his sister, growing up in Lansing, his father's family secret, turning 50, being Irish Catholic, the White Noise comedy group, his magic fingers, Stumpy's Gang, depression, panic attacks, Parks and Recreation and so much more. We also did a round of Just Me Or Everyone&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="43150638" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/ariynbf/ARIYNBF_JimOHeir.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:28:56</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Jim O'Heir (Parks and Recreation) stops by this episode of Alison Rosen Is Your New Best Friend to talk about butt-dialing his sister, growing up in Lansing, his father's family secret, turning 50, being Irish Catholic, the White Noise comedy group,...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Hot Girls Who Need to Use Your Printer, Chris's Horrible Neighbor, Karaoke</title>
                    <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2013 06:04:07 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">d06e77f14038385e72ff2a57318dbe51</guid>
                    <link>http://ariynbf.libsyn.com/hot-girls-who-need-to-use-your-printer-chris-s-horrible-neighbor-karaoke</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/6498694"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;The Thursday gang (Alison, Chris Laxamana, Matt Fondiler, Gary Smith and Jenna Kim Jones) reminisces about Thanksgiving, discusses whether to answer the door when someone unexpected rings the bell, talks about Chris's horrible new neighbor and Matt's "thing" being rollerblading and debates the merits of karaoke. &amp;nbsp;We also did a round of Just Me Or Everyone&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="30644109" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/ariynbf/ARIYNBF_MBF_036.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:02:52</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>The Thursday gang (Alison, Chris Laxamana, Matt Fondiler, Gary Smith and Jenna Kim Jones) reminisces about Thanksgiving, discusses whether to answer the door when someone unexpected rings the bell, talks about Chris's horrible new neighbor and Matt's...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Ray Oldhafer</title>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2013 06:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">8bf32d9655930a1cbbe54362dafe1834</guid>
                    <link>http://ariynbf.libsyn.com/ray-oldhafer</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/6482817"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Ray Oldhafer &amp;nbsp;(Ace of the House, Ray and Lorenzo) stops by this episode of Alison Rosen Is Your New Best Friend to talk about the other Ray Oldhafer, golf personalities, being deported in 1969, roughhousing versus fighting, bullying, Adam Carolla, relationships, his childhood, therapy and trying to grow up, pigs and so much more. We also did a round of HGFY and Just Me Or Everyone&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="43836509" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/ariynbf/ARIYNBF_RayOldhafer.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:30:21</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Ray Oldhafer &amp;nbsp;(Ace of the House, Ray and Lorenzo) stops by this episode of Alison Rosen Is Your New Best Friend to talk about the other Ray Oldhafer, golf personalities, being deported in 1969, roughhousing versus fighting, bullying, Adam...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Matt Crack, Shower Squeegees and Underwear Thoughts</title>
                    <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2013 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">f31b06be08fc81cd219e87e14877aac7</guid>
                    <link>http://ariynbf.libsyn.com/matt-crack-shower-squeegees-and-underwear-thoughts</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/6469598"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;The Thursday gang (Alison, Chris Laxamana, Matt Fondiler, Gary Smith and Jenna Kim Jones) talks pouffy dresses, showering, underwear, drying methods, Matt Crack, fancy soap and so much more. &amp;nbsp;We also did a round of Just Me Or Everyone&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="23035162" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/ariynbf/ARIYNBF_MBF_035.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>47:01</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>The Thursday gang (Alison, Chris Laxamana, Matt Fondiler, Gary Smith and Jenna Kim Jones) talks pouffy dresses, showering, underwear, drying methods, Matt Crack, fancy soap and so much more. &amp;nbsp;We also did a round of Just Me Or Everyone</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Brian Redban</title>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2013 06:06:27 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">8e55fa56c437ea6eaab3ffefe58333a2</guid>
                    <link>http://ariynbf.libsyn.com/brian-redban</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/6454253"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Brian Redban stopped by this episode of Alison Rosen Is Your New Best Friend to talk about Deathsquad, working with Joe Rogan, growing up in Columbus, Ohio, being a touring comic, friendship, tampons, simulation theory, Carlos Mencia, Molly, relationships and so much more. We also did a round of Just Me Or Everyone&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="45124032" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/ariynbf/ARIYNBF_2XX_BrianRedban.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:33:02</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Brian Redban stopped by this episode of Alison Rosen Is Your New Best Friend to talk about Deathsquad, working with Joe Rogan, growing up in Columbus, Ohio, being a touring comic, friendship, tampons, simulation theory, Carlos Mencia, Molly,...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>The Truth About Chris, Puffy Dresses, Fondilering</title>
                    <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2013 06:00:28 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">65982d91fa6a00a151daf5c2cf825a7d</guid>
                    <link>http://ariynbf.libsyn.com/the-truth-about-chris-puffy-dresses-fondilering</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/6437149"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;The Thursday gang (Alison, Chris Laxamana, Matt Fondiler, Gary Smith and Jenna Kim Jones) minus Chris discuss Chris, stigmas, cheese, the thick skin you develop working with Adam, what podcasts we all listen to, Fondilering and so much more. &amp;nbsp;We also did a round of Just Me Or Everyone&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="31066457" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/ariynbf/ARIYNBF_MBF_034.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:03:45</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>The Thursday gang (Alison, Chris Laxamana, Matt Fondiler, Gary Smith and Jenna Kim Jones) minus Chris discuss Chris, stigmas, cheese, the thick skin you develop working with Adam, what podcasts we all listen to, Fondilering and so much more. &amp;nbsp;We...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Dave Anthony</title>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2013 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">ff2ce41a0b34fe92e7d066311c1aa481</guid>
                    <link>http://ariynbf.libsyn.com/dave-anthony</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/6421166"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Dave Anthony stopped by this episode of Alison Rosen Is Your New Best Friend to talk about being one of the founders of the LA Podcast Festival, writing on Maron, stand up comedy, Scare Tactics, selling mushrooms, the mob, his relationship with his parents, fatherhood, UC Santa Barbara, McSorley's, anger and so much more. We also did a round of Just Me Or Everyone&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="49344584" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/ariynbf/ARIYNBF_2XX_DaveAnthony.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:41:50</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Dave Anthony stopped by this episode of Alison Rosen Is Your New Best Friend to talk about being one of the founders of the LA Podcast Festival, writing on Maron, stand up comedy, Scare Tactics, selling mushrooms, the mob, his relationship with his...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Adam Carolla's Stress Factory, Matt Fondiler's Tummy Towel, The Other Alison</title>
                    <pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2013 05:59:08 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">1dea771aa2fd96d662bf2e3d46061471</guid>
                    <link>http://ariynbf.libsyn.com/adam-carolla-s-stress-factory-matt-fondiler-s-tummy-towel-the-other-alison</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/6408063"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;The Thursday gang (Alison, Chris Laxamana, Matt Fondiler, Gary Smith and Jenna Kim Jones) discuss Alison's crazy and surreal attempt to make a new friend, the "other" Alison, Matt's showering and towel habits, bath robes, shoes, sleeping and making out with dogs and so much more. Also: Evitamigos and stress factories that spit you out with your shoes on. We also did a round of Just Me Or Everyone&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="36528556" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/ariynbf/ARIYNBF_MBF_033.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:15:08</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>The Thursday gang (Alison, Chris Laxamana, Matt Fondiler, Gary Smith and Jenna Kim Jones) discuss Alison's crazy and surreal attempt to make a new friend, the "other" Alison, Matt's showering and towel habits, bath robes, shoes, sleeping and making...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Jo Koy</title>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2013 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">42f12333aaf8f3aa0bd51dd357a73375</guid>
                    <link>http://ariynbf.libsyn.com/jo-koy</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/6393176"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Jo Koy stopped by this episode of Alison Rosen Is Your New Best Friend to talk about all sorts of things including fatherhood, saggy pants, growing up with a schizophrenic brother, his relationship with his father, stand up, VHS tapes, chid support, Las Vegas, Chelsea Handler, negative energy and so much more. We also did a round of Just Me Or Everyone&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="41902194" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/ariynbf/ARIYNBF_2XX_JoKoy.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:26:20</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Jo Koy stopped by this episode of Alison Rosen Is Your New Best Friend to talk about all sorts of things including fatherhood, saggy pants, growing up with a schizophrenic brother, his relationship with his father, stand up, VHS tapes, chid support,...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Boners, Showers, Sandwiches</title>
                    <pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2013 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">2af2661212ea5a1ae15ebe237f8cab13</guid>
                    <link>http://ariynbf.libsyn.com/boners-showers-sandwiches</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/6377042"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;The Thursday gang (Alison, Chris Laxamana, Matt Fondiler, Gary Smith and Jenna Kim Jones) discuss bad moods, being on your boner, toilet seats, sandwiches, Miv Schaaf, shower protocol, shower sex, shampooing and so much more. We also did a round of Just Me Or Everyone.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="33916520" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/ariynbf/ARIYNBF_MBF_032.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:09:41</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>The Thursday gang (Alison, Chris Laxamana, Matt Fondiler, Gary Smith and Jenna Kim Jones) discuss bad moods, being on your boner, toilet seats, sandwiches, Miv Schaaf, shower protocol, shower sex, shampooing and so much more. We also did a round of...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Emily Gordon</title>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2013 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">0f6b6a9715b36fd1ed6f41783e67caaf</guid>
                    <link>http://ariynbf.libsyn.com/emily-gordon</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/6363665"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Emily Gordon (The Indoor Kids, The Meltdown Show) stopped by this episode of Alison Rosen Is Your New Best Friend to talk about all sorts of things including growing up in North Carolina, meeting her husband Kumail Nanjiani, relationships, their secret wedding, being in a coma, working with schizophrenics, working with comics, leaving her therapy practice, writing, body image, Tavi Gevinson and so much more. We also did a round of Just Me Or Everyone&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="41236385" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/ariynbf/ARIYNBF_2XX_EmilyGordon.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:24:56</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Emily Gordon (The Indoor Kids, The Meltdown Show) stopped by this episode of Alison Rosen Is Your New Best Friend to talk about all sorts of things including growing up in North Carolina, meeting her husband Kumail Nanjiani, relationships, their...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Matt's Drug Use, Halloween and Butter Sandwiches</title>
                    <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2013 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">3b0d35190737143763bbb714474ae6a4</guid>
                    <link>http://ariynbf.libsyn.com/matt-s-drug-use-halloween-and-butter-sandwiches</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/6347434"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;The Thursday gang (Alison, Chris Laxamana, Matt Fondiler, Gary Smith and Jenna Kim Jones) discuss Halloween, being indirect, butter sandwiches (again!), other sandwiches, pinatas and drugs, Les Claypool and so much more. We also did a round of Just Me Or Everyone&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="37146927" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/ariynbf/ARIYNBF_MBF_031.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:16:25</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>The Thursday gang (Alison, Chris Laxamana, Matt Fondiler, Gary Smith and Jenna Kim Jones) discuss Halloween, being indirect, butter sandwiches (again!), other sandwiches, pinatas and drugs, Les Claypool and so much more. We also did a round of Just Me...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Michael Showalter</title>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2013 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">a20b18c412f4c9390b13bec791a274cb</guid>
                    <link>http://ariynbf.libsyn.com/michael-showalter</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/6331376"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Michael Showalter stopped by this episode of Alison Rosen Is Your New Best Friend to talk about all sorts of things including his rich and varied history with Alison, Lou Reed, being too attached to his cell phone, moving to LA from New York, his feelings about the East Coast, things Alison was wrong about, The State, cats, his book Guys Can Be Cat Ladies Too, meeting his wife, being a certified cat trapper, They Came Together, semiotics and so much more. We also did a round of Just Me Or Everyone&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="37087304" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/ariynbf/ARIYNBF_2XX_MichaelShowalter.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:16:18</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Michael Showalter stopped by this episode of Alison Rosen Is Your New Best Friend to talk about all sorts of things including his rich and varied history with Alison, Lou Reed, being too attached to his cell phone, moving to LA from New York, his...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Jenna's Return, Chris's Tortilla Soup and Gusto</title>
                    <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2013 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">9af9c37280941d3dfe89003a22001f24</guid>
                    <link>http://ariynbf.libsyn.com/jenna-s-return-chris-s-tortilla-soup-and-gusto</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/6316201"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;The Thursday gang (Alison, Chris Laxamana, Matt Fondiler, Gary Smith and Jenna Kim Jones) discuss where Jenna's been, her history dancing and singing at Lagoon, whether Chris is the male Alison, hair cutting and coloring, butter sandwiches, more things we regret, the number one worst thing Chris has ever done, the whole Dingo Boy situation and the pronunciation of "gusto." We also did a round of Just Me Or Everyone and announced the winner of the Citrix contest.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="41712086" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/ariynbf/ARIYNBF_MBF_030.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:25:56</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>The Thursday gang (Alison, Chris Laxamana, Matt Fondiler, Gary Smith and Jenna Kim Jones) discuss where Jenna's been, her history dancing and singing at Lagoon, whether Chris is the male Alison, hair cutting and coloring, butter sandwiches, more...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Greg Proops Returns</title>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2013 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">b534dbbc112481015c629d45182866f5</guid>
                    <link>http://ariynbf.libsyn.com/greg-proops-returns</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/6299370"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Greg Proops stopped by this episode of Alison Rosen Is Your New Best Friend to talk about all sorts of things including being the first guest ever to appear thrice on the show, Nu Shooz and Andie MacDowell, football and sports in general, owning a Filofax, his capacity to love, his latest special filmed at Musso &amp;amp; Frank and what happened with Chill.com, poetry, fiction, pizza and more. We also did a round of Just Me Or Everyone&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="49057092" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/ariynbf/ARIYNBF_2XX_GregProops.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:41:14</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Greg Proops stopped by this episode of Alison Rosen Is Your New Best Friend to talk about all sorts of things including being the first guest ever to appear thrice on the show, Nu Shooz and Andie MacDowell, football and sports in general, owning a...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>A Startling Revelation, an Airing of Grievances and a Sandwich Debate</title>
                    <pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2013 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">82624a20cbb15b40e171828609a1a1c5</guid>
                    <link>http://ariynbf.libsyn.com/a-startling-revelation-an-airing-of-grievances-and-a-sandwich-debate</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/6279809"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;In what Alison is already regarding as a Very Special Episode of Alison Rosen Is Your New Best Friend, The Thursday gang (Alison, Chris Laxamana, Matt Fondiler, Gary Smith) along with fellow Carolla Digital producer extraordinaire Jeff Fox go around the room airing grievances in a round of Hey Go F*ck Yourself. Then Chris makes a brave and upsetting confession. Plus more heated discussion about whether a butter sandwich actually exists or whether, as Gary maintains, it's just two pieces of toast slapped together. Plus talk of Gravity, energy and baseball. We also did a round of Just Me Or Everyone&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="24782649" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/ariynbf/ARIYNBF_MBF_029.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>50:40</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>In what Alison is already regarding as a Very Special Episode of Alison Rosen Is Your New Best Friend, The Thursday gang (Alison, Chris Laxamana, Matt Fondiler, Gary Smith) along with fellow Carolla Digital producer extraordinaire Jeff Fox go around...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Paul Gilmartin Returns</title>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2013 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">be6ca152ed62df9234bf0368b48ae7b6</guid>
                    <link>http://ariynbf.libsyn.com/paul-gilmartin-returns</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/6266318"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Paul Gilmartin stops by this episode of Alison Rosen Is Your New Best Friend to talk about weird sex music, his excellent podcast The Mental Illness Happy Hour and what inspired him to start it, boundary issues, relationships, his relationship with his mom, getting sober, anger, depression, support groups and so much more. We also did a round of Just Me Or Everyone&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="38868437" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/ariynbf/ARIYNBF_2XX_PaulGilmartin2.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:20:00</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Paul Gilmartin stops by this episode of Alison Rosen Is Your New Best Friend to talk about weird sex music, his excellent podcast The Mental Illness Happy Hour and what inspired him to start it, boundary issues, relationships, his relationship with...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Jeff Fox, Podfest Chatter and Chris's Car Double</title>
                    <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2013 04:57:13 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">af85a1462e0e842a166841d228cde421</guid>
                    <link>http://ariynbf.libsyn.com/jeff-fox-podfest-chatter-and-chris-s-car-double</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/6253018"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;The Thursday gang (Alison, Chris Laxamana, Matt Fondiler and Gary Smith) welcome fellow Carolla Digital producer extraordinaire Jeff Fox to the show to talk about his early days in magazines, video editing, how to pronounce "aunt" and spell "gray," Chris's car double and so much more. We also did a round of Just Me Or Everyone&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="26678721" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/ariynbf/ARIYNBF_MBF_028.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>54:37</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>The Thursday gang (Alison, Chris Laxamana, Matt Fondiler and Gary Smith) welcome fellow Carolla Digital producer extraordinaire Jeff Fox to the show to talk about his early days in magazines, video editing, how to pronounce "aunt" and spell "gray,"...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Larry Miller</title>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2013 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">8c0a0d551595817c29260019099254b8</guid>
                    <link>http://ariynbf.libsyn.com/larry-miller</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/6237944"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Larry Miller stops by this episode of Alison Rosen Is Your New Best Friend to talk about Chicken Larry, suffering head trauma earlier this year, his alter ego Fred Stone, his one-man show, cleaning habits, drinking, parents' night and so much more. We also did a round of Just Me Or Everyone.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="32761008" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/ariynbf/ARIYNBF_2XX_LarryMiller.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:07:17</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Larry Miller stops by this episode of Alison Rosen Is Your New Best Friend to talk about Chicken Larry, suffering head trauma earlier this year, his alter ego Fred Stone, his one-man show, cleaning habits, drinking, parents' night and so much more. We...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Caelan Biehn, Chris's High Heels and The Weekend Conundrum</title>
                    <pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2013 05:51:59 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">d5494d5070f976535b4e04f397d8b691</guid>
                    <link>http://ariynbf.libsyn.com/caelan-biehn-chris-s-high-heels-and-the-weekend-conundrum</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/6223329"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;The Thursday gang (Alison, Chris Laxamana, Matt Fondiler and Gary Smith) welcome newish Carolla Digital employee Caelan Biehn -- son of actor Michael Biehn-- to the podcast while Jenna is out with a cold. We talk about Chris's weekend conundrum, who will get the honor of being Alison's Face Czar, Matt Costa and the upcoming live show at the LA Podfest, video games, the way Jo Koy says "drawers" vs. the way Chris says "drawers," dancing, super embarrassing moments, Matt's running around in flip flops and so much more.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="30230956" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/ariynbf/ARIYNBF_MBF_027.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:02:01</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>The Thursday gang (Alison, Chris Laxamana, Matt Fondiler and Gary Smith) welcome newish Carolla Digital employee Caelan Biehn -- son of actor Michael Biehn-- to the podcast while Jenna is out with a cold. We talk about Chris's weekend conundrum, who...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Tom Segura</title>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2013 04:16:12 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">639f52c16e8c3b0e88c73afb8caac659</guid>
                    <link>http://ariynbf.libsyn.com/tom-segura</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/6208116"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Comedian Tom Segura (Your Mom's House) stops by this episode of Alison Rosen Is Your New Best Friend to talk about spiders and ants, wiping technique, sneezing and whether light triggers the sneeze response, a brief stint in Boston real estate, America's Most Wanted, the Groundlings, comedy in general, how he met his lovely wife Christina Pazsitsky, cars, Theo Huxtable Segura and so much more. We also did a round of Just Me Or Everyone&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="49736839" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/ariynbf/ARIYNBF_2XX_TomSegura.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:42:39</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Comedian Tom Segura (Your Mom's House) stops by this episode of Alison Rosen Is Your New Best Friend to talk about spiders and ants, wiping technique, sneezing and whether light triggers the sneeze response, a brief stint in Boston real estate,...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>The Sexy Gary Voice and The Cheese Game</title>
                    <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2013 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">e5535e6488f840cd3a127f9385cca273</guid>
                    <link>http://ariynbf.libsyn.com/the-sexy-gary-voice-and-the-cheese-game</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/6192190"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;The Thursday gang (Alison, Jenna Kim Jones, Chris Laxamana, Matt Fondiler and Gary Smith) plays a short round of The Cheese Game and then after much prodding Gary unleashes a little something he's had tucked away for far too long: The Sexy Gary Voice. Plus so much more. We also did a round of Just Me Or Everyone&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="26425229" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/ariynbf/ARIYNBF_MBF_026.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>54:05</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>The Thursday gang (Alison, Jenna Kim Jones, Chris Laxamana, Matt Fondiler and Gary Smith) plays a short round of The Cheese Game and then after much prodding Gary unleashes a little something he's had tucked away for far too long: The Sexy Gary Voice....</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Fred Stoller</title>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2013 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">e90b3d1f7c05a4d7e9cb5aa40618877d</guid>
                    <link>http://ariynbf.libsyn.com/fred-stoller</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/6176503"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Fred Stoller (Seinfeld, Friends, Everybody Loves Raymond) stops by this episode of Alison Rosen Is Your New Best Friend to talk about being a perennial guest star, writing for Seinfeld (My Seinfeld Year), his book Maybe We'll Have You Back, hating go getters, Billy Crystal, self-doubt, relationships and so much more. We also did a round of Just Me Or Everyone&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="35636985" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/ariynbf/ARIYNBF_2XX_FredStoller.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:13:16</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Fred Stoller (Seinfeld, Friends, Everybody Loves Raymond) stops by this episode of Alison Rosen Is Your New Best Friend to talk about being a perennial guest star, writing for Seinfeld (My Seinfeld Year), his book Maybe We'll Have You Back, hating go...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Scary Bunnies, School Supplies, Hot Dogs and Matt's Other Nickname</title>
                    <pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2013 04:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">82d913920acc2b4c1eb928bbff0d28b4</guid>
                    <link>http://ariynbf.libsyn.com/scary-bunnies-school-supplies-hot-dogs-and-matt-s-other-nickname</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/6160564"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;The Thursday gang (Alison, Jenna Kim Jones, Chris Laxamana, Matt Fondiler and Gary Smith) talks about the clock watch (the new watch watch), Gary calling Matt "Matty," school supplies, Laura Leu choking on a hot dog, roller coasters, "scaracters," haunted houses, dolls, deleted tweets, getting burned by a subject line and so much more. We also did a round of Just Me Or Everyone&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="31113686" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/ariynbf/ARIYNBF_MBF_025.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:03:51</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>The Thursday gang (Alison, Jenna Kim Jones, Chris Laxamana, Matt Fondiler and Gary Smith) talks about the clock watch (the new watch watch), Gary calling Matt "Matty," school supplies, Laura Leu choking on a hot dog, roller coasters, "scaracters,"...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>David Wain</title>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2013 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">b2593a22e476a401dddb4771e8b49a0a</guid>
                    <link>http://ariynbf.libsyn.com/david-wain</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/6143943"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;David Wain (Wet Hot American Summer, The State, Stella, Children's Hospital) stops by this episode of Alison Rosen Is Your New Best Friend to talk about being a director/producer/actor/writer, his passion for magic, moving to Los Angeles, making videos in the 80s, Aaron Sorkin, a missing therapist, Wainy Days, fear and anxiety, meeting his wife, how typing may have been the glue that held Stella together and so much more. We also did a round of Just Me Or Everyone&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="39810517" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/ariynbf/ARIYNBF_2XX_DavidWain.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:21:58</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>David Wain (Wet Hot American Summer, The State, Stella, Children's Hospital) stops by this episode of Alison Rosen Is Your New Best Friend to talk about being a director/producer/actor/writer, his passion for magic, moving to Los Angeles, making...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Calling Out Dr. Drew, Bad Screen Names and Chris's Eating Habits</title>
                    <pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2013 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">2e668b588b762dbb46b0edadb4e79b78</guid>
                    <link>http://ariynbf.libsyn.com/calling-out-dr-drew-bad-screen-names-and-chris-s-eating-habits</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/6125640"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;The Thursday group (Alison, Jenna Kim Jones, Chris Laxamana, Matt Fondiler and Gary Smith) talks about a new development in watch watch, Dr. Drew's interview style versus Alison's, eye crud, whether email subject lines are necessary, etiquette, awful screen names, veganism and so much more. We also did a round of Just Me Or Everyone&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="30834698" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/ariynbf/ARIYNBF_MBF_024.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:03:16</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>The Thursday group (Alison, Jenna Kim Jones, Chris Laxamana, Matt Fondiler and Gary Smith) talks about a new development in watch watch, Dr. Drew's interview style versus Alison's, eye crud, whether email subject lines are necessary, etiquette, awful...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Kelly Carlin</title>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2013 03:57:35 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">612390d688ef41254805fc30b883499d</guid>
                    <link>http://ariynbf.libsyn.com/kelly-carlin</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/6111209"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Kelly Carlin, monologist, host, writer and daughter of George Carlin, stops by this episode of Alison Rosen Is Your New Best Friend to talk about her unusual childhood, growing up around addiction, her coke dealer mechanic ex, psychology, losing her parents, her one woman show (A Carlin Home Companion), guns, her podcast Waking from the American Dream and so much more. We also did a round for Just Me Or Everyone&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="44629169" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/ariynbf/ARIYNBF_1XX_KellyCarlin.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:32:00</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Kelly Carlin, monologist, host, writer and daughter of George Carlin, stops by this episode of Alison Rosen Is Your New Best Friend to talk about her unusual childhood, growing up around addiction, her coke dealer mechanic ex, psychology, losing her...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Bald Bryan, The Cornhole Tournament and Watch Watch</title>
                    <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2013 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">d562dbce2c228038a42298373edebccc</guid>
                    <link>http://ariynbf.libsyn.com/bald-bryan-the-cornhole-tournament-and-watch-watch</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/6094067"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Bald Bryan joined the the Thursday group (Alison, Chris Laxamana, Matt Fondiler and Gary Smith) this week as Jenna was out and we discussed Alison's continued critical timepiece situation, Chris's cornhole debacle, beards, dog parks, breakfast, bugs and so much more. We also did Topic Sombrero, a round of Just Me Or Everyone and new segment, HGFYD.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="30187906" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/ariynbf/ARIYNBF_MBF_023.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:01:55</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Bald Bryan joined the the Thursday group (Alison, Chris Laxamana, Matt Fondiler and Gary Smith) this week as Jenna was out and we discussed Alison's continued critical timepiece situation, Chris's cornhole debacle, beards, dog parks, breakfast, bugs...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
            </channel>
        </rss>
    </httpclient:body>
</httpclient:response>