<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<httpclient:response xmlns:httpclient="http://exist-db.org/xquery/httpclient" statusCode="200">
    <httpclient:headers>
        <httpclient:header name="Server" value="Apache/2.2"/>
        <httpclient:header name="Cache-Control" value="no-store, no-cache, must-revalidate, post-check=0, pre-check=0"/>
        <httpclient:header name="Content-Type" value="text/xml; charset=UTF-8"/>
        <httpclient:header name="Date" value="Wed, 20 Aug 2014 09:26:40 GMT"/>
        <httpclient:header name="X-Pingback" value="http://abraham.com/xmlrpc.php"/>
        <httpclient:header name="Expires" value="Thu, 19 Nov 1981 08:52:00 GMT"/>
        <httpclient:header name="Pragma" value="no-cache"/>
        <httpclient:header name="Transfer-Encoding" value="chunked"/>
        <httpclient:header name="ETag" value="&#34;a9199ebd254fe33544a2084e812ab4db&#34;"/>
        <httpclient:header name="Connection" value="Keep-Alive"/>
        <httpclient:header name="Set-Cookie" value="X-Mapping-akaopmho=4C1776C1EE9B9E14ED2336AD82EA340A; path=/"/>
        <httpclient:header name="Set-Cookie" value="PHPSESSID=btkojk6gc9nloppno8kgu12i26; path=/"/>
        <httpclient:header name="Set-Cookie" value="wfvt_1298750786=53f469d2529f3; expires=Wed, 20-Aug-2014 09:56:42 GMT; path=/"/>
        <httpclient:header name="Last-Modified" value="Wed, 13 Aug 2014 16:51:06 GMT"/>
    </httpclient:headers>
    <httpclient:body mimetype="text/xml; charset=UTF-8" type="xml">
        <rss xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:rawvoice="http://www.rawvoice.com/rawvoiceRssModule/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" version="2.0">
            <channel>
                <title>The Ultimate Entrepreneur with Jay Abraham</title>
                <atom:link href="http://abraham.com/feed/podcast/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
                <link>http://abraham.com</link>
                <description>The Preeminent Global Resource for Entrepreneurs</description>
                <lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2014 16:51:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
                <language>en-US</language>
                <sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
                <sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	
<!-- podcast_generator="Blubrry PowerPress/5.0.2" mode="advanced" -->
                <itunes:summary>The Ultimate Entrepreneur with Jay Abraham 

Jay Abraham is widely considered the world's preeminent business growth expert – a mammoth force in original thinking. Certainly, he’s legendary in entrepreneurship circles. Advisor/mentor/masterful thinking partner to a wide spectrum of famous/iconic entrepreneurs. Referred to by many as the consultant’s consultant, he has personally advised/counseled over 300 prominent business experts. Jay is a leading authority on global entrepreneurship, with published works in China, Japan, United Kingdom and the former USSR. He is the creator of “The Strategy of Preeminence”, empowering some of the highest value-based companies in the world. Jay has authored best-selling books on a variety of topics that inspire business growth and development. He charges a daily consulting fee of $50,000. He currently has five new books in-process, ranging from one with Shark Tank star, Daymond John, another with the former CEO of Adidas and Speedo, and another with the CEO-Coach to the Department of Defense/Co-Founder of the Harvard Leadership Study.
Jay's body of work spans more than three decades and has generated an estimated $9 billion dollars of capital increases - within hundreds of industries. These podcasts contain provocative conversations with many of the world's most successful, inventive and respected entrepreneurs who share fresh facets of their knowledge on How to Achieve Greater Personal/Business/Emotional Wealth Creation.
Some of the interviews and conversations are migrated from Jay's national radio program and others are exclusive to iTunes. Inspirational, yet highly actionable, educational and thought-provoking, yet super-logical, these free downloads are co-hosted by Manhattan entrepreneur and veteran broadcaster, Paul Durante.</itunes:summary>
                <itunes:author>Jay Abraham and Paul Durante</itunes:author>
                <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
                <itunes:image href="http://abraham.com/wp-content/uploads/powerpress/Jay_Paul_logo.jpg"/>
                <itunes:owner>
                    <itunes:name>Jay Abraham and Paul Durante</itunes:name>
                    <itunes:email>teddy@cybermediamarketing.com</itunes:email>
                </itunes:owner>
                <managingEditor>teddy@cybermediamarketing.com (Jay Abraham and Paul Durante)</managingEditor>
                <itunes:subtitle>Jay Abraham’s Radio Show. Mastermind Interviews. For Global Entrepreneurial Preeminence, visit Abraham.com</itunes:subtitle>
                <itunes:keywords>entrepreneurship, marketing strategy, business strategy, joint ventures, scaleability, jay abraham, marketing, sales strategy, sales, marketing</itunes:keywords>
                <image>
                    <title>The Ultimate Entrepreneur with Jay Abraham</title>
                    <url>http://abraham.com/wp-content/uploads/powerpress/Jay_Paul_logo.jpg</url>
                    <link>http://abraham.com</link>
                </image>
                <itunes:category text="Business">
                    <itunes:category text="Management &amp; Marketing"/>
                    <itunes:category text="Business News"/>
                </itunes:category>
                <rawvoice:frequency>Weekly</rawvoice:frequency>
                <item>
                    <title>Daymond John &amp; Jay Abraham The Ultimate Entrepreneur</title>
                    <link>http://abraham.com/daymond-john-jay-abraham-the-ultimate-entrepreneur/</link>
                    <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2013 23:51:38 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://abraham.com/?p=2238</guid>
                    <comments>http://abraham.com/daymond-john-jay-abraham-the-ultimate-entrepreneur/#comments</comments>
                    <dc:creator>Teddy</dc:creator>
                    <category>Podcast</category>
                    <description>Daymond John is the founder of FUBU, is a global branding expert and a Shark Tank Shark. Jay Abraham and Paul Durante speak with Daymond about what makes an ultimate entrepreneur, how we were born with the ability to never give up, his humble beginnings as a child entrepreneur, how he started FUBU in his […]</description>
                    <wfw:commentRss>http://abraham.com/daymond-john-jay-abraham-the-ultimate-entrepreneur/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
                    <slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
                    <enclosure url="http://media.blubrry.com/ultimateentrepreneur/content.blubrry.com/ultimateentrepreneur/Ultimate_Entrepreneur_Jay_Abraham_and_Daymond_John.mp3" length="63587036" type="audio/mpeg"/>
                    <itunes:keywords>Jay Abraham,Daymond John,Entrepreneur,entrepreneurial,Success,Business,Income,Marketing,preeminent,Leadership,Strategy,Sales</itunes:keywords>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Jay Abraham’s Radio Show. Mastermind Interviews. For Global Entrepreneurial Preeminence, visit Abraham.com</itunes:subtitle>
                    <itunes:summary>Daymond John is the founder of FUBU, is a global branding expert and a Shark Tank Shark. Jay Abraham and Paul Durante speak with Daymond about what makes an ultimate entrepreneur, how we were born with the ability to never give up, his humble beginnings as a child entrepreneur, how he started FUBU in his house while still working at Red Lobster, how he failed many times and got turned down by 27 banks, how he almost lost everything including his house, how he lost $6 Million in the record industry, how you can drown in opportunity, what is and who is your brand, how he became a Shark on Shark Tank, and how compounding his passion made him successful. Fans of this podcast may register for FREE for The Abraham Ultimate Entrepreneur Success Force. Call 1-800-88-12345 or visit Abraham.com to receive FREE resources from Jay Abraham: Downloads, Special Offerings, Private Communiques, Invitations to Exclusive Events, and possibly Participate in Specialized Mastermind Discussions. All FREE and with no obligation.</itunes:summary>
                    <itunes:author>Jay Abraham and Paul Durante</itunes:author>
                    <itunes:image href="http://abraham.com/wp-content/uploads/powerpress/Jay_Paul_logo.jpg"/>
                    <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:duration>26:30</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:order>2</itunes:order>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Mark Cuban &amp; Jay Abraham The Ultimate Entrepreneur</title>
                    <link>http://abraham.com/mark-cuban-jay-abraham-the-ultimate-entrepreneur/</link>
                    <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2013 23:33:59 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://abraham.com/?p=2232</guid>
                    <comments>http://abraham.com/mark-cuban-jay-abraham-the-ultimate-entrepreneur/#comments</comments>
                    <dc:creator>Teddy</dc:creator>
                    <category>Podcast</category>
                    <description>Mark Cuban is the billionaire owner of the Dallas Mavericks, a world-class entrepreneur and a Shark on Shark Tank. Jay Abraham and Paul Durante speak with Mark about how his success comes from being extremely competitive, how effort is everything, why he doesn’t wear suits, how it’s a never ending quest to get better, the […]</description>
                    <wfw:commentRss>http://abraham.com/mark-cuban-jay-abraham-the-ultimate-entrepreneur/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
                    <slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
                    <enclosure url="http://media.blubrry.com/ultimateentrepreneur/content.blubrry.com/ultimateentrepreneur/Ultimate_Entrepreneur_Jay_Abraham_and_Mark_Cuban.mp3" length="56734220" type="audio/mpeg"/>
                    <itunes:keywords>Jay Abraham,Mark Cuban,Entrepreneur,entrepreneurial,Success,Business,Income,Marketing,preeminent,Leadership,Strategy,Sales</itunes:keywords>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Jay Abraham’s Radio Show. Mastermind Interviews. For Global Entrepreneurial Preeminence, visit Abraham.com</itunes:subtitle>
                    <itunes:summary>Mark Cuban is the billionaire owner of the Dallas Mavericks, a world-class entrepreneur and a Shark on Shark Tank. Jay Abraham and Paul Durante speak with Mark about how his success comes from being extremely competitive, how effort is everything, why he doesn't wear suits, how it’s a never ending quest to get better, the “sport of business”, the power of Shark Tank and how he decides who to make offers to, thinking “critically", helping young entrepreneurs, the importance of always trying to improve, why you shouldn't always listen to your customer, how to better communicate with your customer, his success with broadcast.com and the infancy of streaming, what motivates him today, and how he helps entrepreneurs who meet him in the street. Fans of this podcast may register for FREE for The Abraham Ultimate Entrepreneur Success Force. Call 1-800-88-12345 or visit Abraham.com to receive FREE resources from Jay Abraham: Downloads, Special Offerings, Private Communiques, Invitations to Exclusive Events, and possibly Participate in Specialized Mastermind Discussions. All FREE and with no obligation.</itunes:summary>
                    <itunes:author>Jay Abraham and Paul Durante</itunes:author>
                    <itunes:image href="http://abraham.com/wp-content/uploads/powerpress/Jay_Paul_logo.jpg"/>
                    <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:duration>23:38</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:order>3</itunes:order>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Kevin Harrington &amp; Jay Abraham The Ultimate Entrepreneur</title>
                    <link>http://abraham.com/kevin-harrington-jay-abraham-the-ultimate-entrepreneur/</link>
                    <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2013 23:28:38 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://abraham.com/?p=2227</guid>
                    <comments>http://abraham.com/kevin-harrington-jay-abraham-the-ultimate-entrepreneur/#comments</comments>
                    <dc:creator>Teddy</dc:creator>
                    <category>Podcast</category>
                    <description>Kevin Harrington is a Shark Tank Shark, King of the Infomercial and Chairman of “As Seen on TV”. Jay Abraham and Paul Durante speak with Kevin about leveraging local and international Celebrities, how he got 50 Cent to work with him for no money up front, the biggest challenges people face when starting a business, […]</description>
                    <wfw:commentRss>http://abraham.com/kevin-harrington-jay-abraham-the-ultimate-entrepreneur/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
                    <slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
                    <enclosure url="http://media.blubrry.com/ultimateentrepreneur/content.blubrry.com/ultimateentrepreneur/Ultimate_Entrepreneur_Jay_Abraham_and_KHarrington.mp3" length="48526292" type="audio/mpeg"/>
                    <itunes:keywords>Jay Abraham,Kevin Harrington,Entrepreneur,entrepreneurial,Success,Business,Income,Marketing,preeminent,Leadership,Strategy,Sales</itunes:keywords>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Jay Abraham’s Radio Show. Mastermind Interviews. For Global Entrepreneurial Preeminence, visit Abraham.com</itunes:subtitle>
                    <itunes:summary>Kevin Harrington is a Shark Tank Shark, King of the Infomercial and Chairman of “As Seen on TV”. Jay Abraham and Paul Durante speak with Kevin about leveraging local and international Celebrities, how he got 50 Cent to work with him for no money up front, the biggest challenges people face when starting a business, how people succeed and fail when appearing on ABC TV’s Shark Tank, how funding/money doesn’t necessarily create success, bringing in experts to help you succeed, the most important elements about marketing, customer acquisition costs, Kevin’s website: asseenontv.com, Kevin’s most successful infomercials, how Kevin puts “a shark in your tank”, Kevin’s success with ediets.com, and Kevin’s passion for the world of mobile. Fans of this podcast may register for FREE for The Abraham Ultimate Entrepreneur Success Force. Call 1-800-88-12345 or visit Abraham.com to receive FREE resources from Jay Abraham: Downloads, Special Offerings, Private Communiques, Invitations to Exclusive Events, and possibly Participate in Specialized Mastermind Discussions. All FREE and with no obligation.</itunes:summary>
                    <itunes:author>Jay Abraham and Paul Durante</itunes:author>
                    <itunes:image href="http://abraham.com/wp-content/uploads/powerpress/Jay_Paul_logo.jpg"/>
                    <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:duration>20:13</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:order>4</itunes:order>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Ramit Sethi &amp; Jay Abraham The Ultimate Entrepreneur</title>
                    <link>http://abraham.com/ramit-sethi-jay-abraham-the-ultimate-entrepreneur/</link>
                    <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2013 23:24:46 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://abraham.com/?p=2223</guid>
                    <comments>http://abraham.com/ramit-sethi-jay-abraham-the-ultimate-entrepreneur/#comments</comments>
                    <dc:creator>Teddy</dc:creator>
                    <category>Podcast</category>
                    <description>Ramit Seth is the definitive representative for Gen Y and Millennials. Jay Abraham and Paul Durante speak with Ramit about what ultimate entrepreneurship means to them. How to take many interests and integrate them, the importance of flexibility and free time, having the option to quit your job in order to travel and do other […]</description>
                    <wfw:commentRss>http://abraham.com/ramit-sethi-jay-abraham-the-ultimate-entrepreneur/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
                    <slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
                    <enclosure url="http://media.blubrry.com/ultimateentrepreneur/content.blubrry.com/ultimateentrepreneur/Ultimate_Entrepreneur_Jay_Abraham_and_Ramit_Sethi.mp3" length="36930584" type="audio/mpeg"/>
                    <itunes:keywords>Jay Abraham,Ramit Sethi,Entrepreneur,entrepreneurial,Success,Business,Income,Marketing,preeminent,Leadership,Strategy,Sales</itunes:keywords>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Jay Abraham’s Radio Show. Mastermind Interviews. For Global Entrepreneurial Preeminence, visit Abraham.com</itunes:subtitle>
                    <itunes:summary>Ramit Seth is the definitive representative for Gen Y and Millennials. Jay Abraham and Paul Durante speak with Ramit about what ultimate entrepreneurship means to them. How to take many interests and integrate them, the importance of flexibility and free time, having the option to quit your job in order to travel and do other things you really want to do in your 20's and 30’s, fiscal prudence, the dream of income generation while sleeping, the #1 reason for wanting to earn money “on the side”, the importance of options for a generation that knows they could have more than 10 jobs in their career, how to generate an extra $1K per month right away, how to take your skills and turn them into income, how to help parents of young adults, the biggest insights about how to “figure it out”, how getting really good at something leads to passion for it, and how 10 conversations can change your life. Ramit’s website: iwillteachyoutoberich.com. Fans of this podcast may register for FREE for The Abraham Ultimate Entrepreneur Success Force. Call 1-800-88-12345 or visit Abraham.com to receive FREE resources from Jay Abraham: Downloads, Special Offerings, Private Communiques, Invitations to Exclusive Events, and possibly Participate in Specialized Mastermind Discussions. All FREE and with no obligation.</itunes:summary>
                    <itunes:author>Jay Abraham and Paul Durante</itunes:author>
                    <itunes:image href="http://abraham.com/wp-content/uploads/powerpress/Jay_Paul_logo.jpg"/>
                    <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:duration>15:23</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:order>5</itunes:order>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Tony Robbins &amp; Jay Abraham The Ultimate Entrepreneur</title>
                    <link>http://abraham.com/the-ultimate-entrepreneur-with-jay-abraham-tony-robbins-3/</link>
                    <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2013 23:15:09 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://abraham.com/?p=2221</guid>
                    <comments>http://abraham.com/the-ultimate-entrepreneur-with-jay-abraham-tony-robbins-3/#comments</comments>
                    <dc:creator>Teddy</dc:creator>
                    <category>Podcast</category>
                    <description>Tony Robbins is a global icon and one of the top business intellectuals in the world. Jay Abraham and Paul Durante speak with Tony about why everyone needs to be an entrepreneur and/or entrepreneurial, what it means to be an ultimate entrepreneur, how entrepreneurship means finding ways to add massive value, examples of Steve Jobs […]</description>
                    <wfw:commentRss>http://abraham.com/the-ultimate-entrepreneur-with-jay-abraham-tony-robbins-3/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
                    <slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
                    <enclosure url="http://media.blubrry.com/ultimateentrepreneur/content.blubrry.com/ultimateentrepreneur/Ultimate_Entrepreneur_Jay_Abraham_and_Tony_Robbins.mp3" length="70483700" type="audio/mpeg"/>
                    <itunes:keywords>Jay Abraham,Tony Robins,Entrepreneur,entrepreneurial,Success,Business,Income,Marketing,preeminent,Leadership,Strategy,Sales</itunes:keywords>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Jay Abraham’s Radio Show. Mastermind Interviews. For Global Entrepreneurial Preeminence, visit Abraham.com</itunes:subtitle>
                    <itunes:summary>Tony Robbins is a global icon and one of the top business intellectuals in the world. Jay Abraham and Paul Durante speak with Tony about why everyone needs to be an entrepreneur and/or entrepreneurial, what it means to be an ultimate entrepreneur, how entrepreneurship means finding ways to add massive value, examples of Steve Jobs and Bill Gates, what customers really want/need and how you can provide it for them, the difference between customers and clients, creating a culture of raving fans, how to figure out what business you’re really in, how to stand out from all the rest, who is your client now and who they need to be for your growth, what people really need psychologically/emotionally and how you can provide it, 5 Ways To Innovate, how asking different questions provides your answers, what social media really is/what it really does and how you should utilize it, and the biggest steps you can take to move forward. Fans of this podcast may register, for FREE, for The Abraham Ultimate Entrepreneur Success Force. Call 1-800-88-12345 or visit Abraham.com to receive FREE resources from Jay Abraham: Downloads, Special Offerings, Private Communiques, Invitations to Exclusive Events, and possibly Participate in Specialized Mastermind Discussions. All FREE and with no obligation.</itunes:summary>
                    <itunes:author>Jay Abraham and Paul Durante</itunes:author>
                    <itunes:image href="http://abraham.com/wp-content/uploads/powerpress/Jay_Paul_logo.jpg"/>
                    <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:duration>29:22</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:order>1</itunes:order>
                </item>
            </channel>
        </rss>
    </httpclient:body>
</httpclient:response>