<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<httpclient:response xmlns:httpclient="http://exist-db.org/xquery/httpclient" statusCode="200">
    <httpclient:headers>
        <httpclient:header name="Content-Type" value="text/xml"/>
        <httpclient:header name="Pragma" value="public"/>
        <httpclient:header name="Server" value="nginx/1.6.0"/>
        <httpclient:header name="X-Powered-By" value="PHP/5.3.10-1ubuntu3.11"/>
        <httpclient:header name="Cache-Control" value="max-age=519"/>
        <httpclient:header name="Expires" value="Wed, 20 Aug 2014 09:55:21 GMT"/>
        <httpclient:header name="Date" value="Wed, 20 Aug 2014 09:46:42 GMT"/>
        <httpclient:header name="Content-Length" value="19529"/>
        <httpclient:header name="Connection" value="keep-alive"/>
    </httpclient:headers>
    <httpclient:body mimetype="text/xml" type="xml">
        <rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
            <channel>
                <atom:link href="http://api.videos.ndtv.com/apis/podcast/index/client_key/ndtv-podcast-5d35e3e34a92df17d11d54e0ff241e8b?shows=188&amp;showfull=1&amp;media_type=audio&amp;extra_params=keywords,description" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
                <title>The Big Fight</title>
                <link>http://www.ndtv.com</link>
                <language>en-GB</language>
                <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                <copyright>© Copyright NDTV Convergence Limited 2014. All rights reserved.</copyright>
                <itunes:subtitle>The Big Fight</itunes:subtitle>
                <itunes:author>NDTV</itunes:author>
                <itunes:summary>Tempers fly as the newsmakers of the week face-off in this award-winning show. Anchored by Vikram Chandra, this weekly program has politicians battling wits as a live audience.</itunes:summary>
                <description>Tempers fly as the newsmakers of the week face-off in this award-winning show. Anchored by Vikram Chandra, this weekly program has politicians battling wits as a live audience.</description>
                <itunes:owner>
                    <itunes:name>NDTV</itunes:name>
                    <itunes:email>podcast@ndtv.com</itunes:email>
                </itunes:owner>
                <itunes:image href="http://drop.ndtv.com/tvshows/show_188_1363591987.jpg"/>
                <itunes:category text="News &amp; Politics"/>
                <item>
                    <title>India's Forgotten Soldiers of World War I and II</title>
                    <itunes:author>Vikram Chandra</itunes:author>
                    <itunes:subtitle>They were brave, they were bold and they laid down their lives to stop the marauding German and Japanese forces. More than a million Indian soldiers in World War I and more than two million in World War II fought for the empire.</itunes:subtitle>
                    <itunes:summary>They were brave, they were bold and they laid down their lives to stop the marauding German and Japanese forces. But they did so for the British Empire and that was the reason they have been relegated to the footnotes of history. Men of honour, but no one to commemorate their bravery and sacrifices - neither the Indians nor the British. More than a million Indian soldiers in World War I and more than two million in World War II fought for the empire. The question is whether the time has come to look back upon history and commemorate these Indians, if not for anything else then at least for their bravery, as they were caught on the wrong side of India's freedom movement. To know the answer, join us for a debate on The Big Fight.</itunes:summary>
                    <itunes:image href="http://i.ndtvimg.com/video/images/vod/thumb/2014-08/thumb_334458_1408207906.jpg"/>
                    <enclosure url="http://voddownload.ndtv.com.edgesuite.net/mp3/2014-08/16082014_n_TheBigFight_15953_290161_117683.mp3" length="196736" type="audio/mpeg"/>
                    <guid>http://voddownload.ndtv.com.edgesuite.net/mp3/2014-08/16082014_n_TheBigFight_15953_290161_117683.mp3</guid>
                    <pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2014 22:14:30 +0530</pubDate>
                    <itunes:duration>51:14</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords>India's Forgotten Soldiers,World War I,World War II,soldiers,British Empire,Indian Soldiers,The Big Fight</itunes:keywords>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>'Modi'-fying India's Foreign Policy</title>
                    <itunes:author>NDTV</itunes:author>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Breaking away from the tradition, Narendra Modi chose Bhutan as his first overseas stop. The next stop for him was Nepal. Is there a message in these visits? Is the Modi government focusing on India's immediate neighbourhood?</itunes:subtitle>
                    <itunes:summary>Breaking away from the tradition, Narendra Modi chose Bhutan as his first overseas stop. The next stop for him was Nepal. Is there a message in these visits? Is the Modi government focusing on India's immediate neighbourhood? Are these steps necessary to tackle China's growing influence? Should India embrace a military pact with Japan? What about India's relationship with USA? Has Modi given a new direction to India's foreign policy? To know the answers, join us for a debate on The Big Fight.</itunes:summary>
                    <itunes:image href="http://i.ndtvimg.com/video/images/vod/thumb/2014-08/thumb_333472_1407603200.jpg"/>
                    <enclosure url="http://voddownload.ndtv.com.edgesuite.net/mp3/2014-08/08092014_n_PrimeShowBigFight_15753_288998_117070.mp3" length="194944" type="audio/mpeg"/>
                    <guid>http://voddownload.ndtv.com.edgesuite.net/mp3/2014-08/08092014_n_PrimeShowBigFight_15753_288998_117070.mp3</guid>
                    <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2014 23:10:02 +0530</pubDate>
                    <itunes:duration>50:46</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords>Narendra Modi,India's Foreign Policy,The Big Fight,Nepal,Japan</itunes:keywords>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Is the School Curriculum Going to Take a Right Turn?</title>
                    <itunes:author>Vikram Chandra</itunes:author>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Will the government try to push its agenda? We debate</itunes:subtitle>
                    <itunes:summary>Last time when the BJP-led NDA government was in power there were widespread allegations against NCERT director and historians of trying to 'saffronise' school textbooks. With Narendra Modi coming to power, scholars and educationists perceived to be close to the RSS are trying to make a case of revising our textbooks and school curriculum. There is a need for an overhaul of our education system but the question is that in the name of overhauling the education system will the government try to push its agenda? Will history be now written to appease and further the agenda of the Right wing? Is that a genuine concern? Join us for a special debate of The Big Fight.</itunes:summary>
                    <itunes:image href="http://i.ndtvimg.com/video/images/vod/thumb/2014-08/thumb_332536_1406997942.jpg"/>
                    <enclosure url="http://voddownload.ndtv.com.edgesuite.net/mp3/2014-08/02082014_n_TheBigFight_15624_287918_116614.mp3" length="189568" type="audio/mpeg"/>
                    <guid>http://voddownload.ndtv.com.edgesuite.net/mp3/2014-08/02082014_n_TheBigFight_15624_287918_116614.mp3</guid>
                    <pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2014 22:49:48 +0530</pubDate>
                    <itunes:duration>49:22</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords>NCERT,School Curriculum,Education,The Big Fight,Narendra Modi,Narendra Modi Government,RSS,school textbooks</itunes:keywords>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Force Feed, Communal Remarks, Sania Controversy - Are We Overhyping the Issues?</title>
                    <itunes:author>Vikram Chandra</itunes:author>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Force Feed, Communal Remarks, Sania Controversy - Are We Overhyping the Issues?</itunes:subtitle>
                    <itunes:summary>First was the force feed of a canteen staff by a Shiv Sena MP, then there was a series of remarks by politicians - mainly by BJP leaders - calling India a Hindu state to questioning Sania Mirza's appointment as the ambassador of Telangana for being the 'daughter-in-law' of Pakistan. Were these stray remarks or there is a pattern to it? Is the media overhyping these remarks? And does PM Modi needs to speak more often? Join us for a special edition of The Big Fight.</itunes:summary>
                    <itunes:image href="http://i.ndtvimg.com/video/images/vod/thumb/2014-07/thumb_331664_1406393606.jpg"/>
                    <enclosure url="http://voddownload.ndtv.com.edgesuite.net/mp3/2014-07/26072014_n_PrimeShowBigFight_15501_286912_116145.mp3" length="196480" type="audio/mpeg"/>
                    <guid>http://voddownload.ndtv.com.edgesuite.net/mp3/2014-07/26072014_n_PrimeShowBigFight_15501_286912_116145.mp3</guid>
                    <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2014 23:51:02 +0530</pubDate>
                    <itunes:duration>51:10</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords>Shiv Sena MPs,Hindu Nation,Sania Mirza,K Laxman,The Big Fight</itunes:keywords>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Should India Have a Uniform Civil Code?</title>
                    <itunes:author>Vikram Chandra</itunes:author>
                    <itunes:subtitle>The Supreme Court had asked for a Uniform Civil Code almost three decades ago, but the government has remained silent on the observation. Is India prepared to have a uniform civil law? Should all the personal laws be done away with?</itunes:subtitle>
                    <itunes:summary>The Supreme Court, in its observation in the Shah Bano case, had asked for a Uniform Civil Code in India. Almost three decades have passed but in spite of repeated observation and earnest instruction by the Top Court in other cases, the government of the day has chosen to remain a mute spectator in framing or at least having a discussion with various stakeholders in building up a consensus on the need for a uniform civil code. Recently, after the court declared fatwas and Sharia courts as illegal, Union Minister of Law had expressed the government's desire to have a uniform civil law in the country. The moot point is whether India is prepared to have a uniform civil law. Should all the personal laws be done away with? Instead of being imposed is consultation and consensus the only way to get the law through? To know all about this contentious issue join us for a special edition of The Big Fight.</itunes:summary>
                    <itunes:image href="http://i.ndtvimg.com/video/images/vod/thumb/2014-07/thumb_330683_1405789727.jpg"/>
                    <enclosure url="http://voddownload.ndtv.com.edgesuite.net/mp3/2014-07/19072014_n_PrimeShowTheBigFight_323842_15329_285782_115583.mp3" length="195200" type="audio/mpeg"/>
                    <guid>http://voddownload.ndtv.com.edgesuite.net/mp3/2014-07/19072014_n_PrimeShowTheBigFight_323842_15329_285782_115583.mp3</guid>
                    <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jul 2014 23:59:17 +0530</pubDate>
                    <itunes:duration>50:50</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords>Uniform Civil Code,The Big Fight,Shah Bano case,Muslim Personao Law Board,Supreme Court,Union Minister of Law</itunes:keywords>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Rebooting India's Economy - The Road Ahead</title>
                    <itunes:author>Vikram Chandra</itunes:author>
                    <itunes:subtitle>After the election results, this was the most awaited event for the Modi government - what will be there in the Budget? Will the government take some bold steps? Will it do away with subsidies?</itunes:subtitle>
                    <itunes:summary>After the election results, this was the most awaited event for the Modi government - what will be there in the Budget? Will the government take some bold steps? Will it do away with subsidies? Though Arun Jaitley, the Finance Minister, did not offer any big bang reform yet, the Budget laid down India's map for the future - infrastructure has to improve, prices of essential food items has to be controlled, tax officials hounding entrepreneurs needs to stop, that social sector lending and schemes will continue for the benefit of those who cannot help themselves; renewed fillip will be on Small &amp; Medium Scale Enterprises, entrepreneurship is to be encouraged and last but not the least bureaucratic complexities have to be simplified. If this is what the Finance Minister has said then what is there to worry about? Apparently and in theory, nothing, except for the fact that without implementation none of these schemes or plans are going to bear any fruit. For 'acche din' implementing all these schemes and plans in letter and theory is going to be the real challenge. Join us for a special edition of The Big Fight.</itunes:summary>
                    <itunes:image href="http://i.ndtvimg.com/video/images/vod/thumb/2014-07/thumb_329777_1405183607.jpg"/>
                    <enclosure url="http://voddownload.ndtv.com.edgesuite.net/mp3/2014-07/12072014_n_BigFight_Merge_322266_15211_284757_115205.mp3" length="200512" type="audio/mpeg"/>
                    <guid>http://voddownload.ndtv.com.edgesuite.net/mp3/2014-07/12072014_n_BigFight_Merge_322266_15211_284757_115205.mp3</guid>
                    <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2014 23:11:08 +0530</pubDate>
                    <itunes:duration>52:13</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords>After the election results,this was the most awaited event for the Modi government - what will be there in the Budget? Will the government take some bold steps? Will it do away with subsidies? Though Arun Jaitley,the Finance Minister,did not offer any big</itunes:keywords>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Insensitive rape remarks - Should stringent action be taken against politicians?</title>
                    <itunes:author>Vikram Chandra</itunes:author>
                    <itunes:subtitle>The outrageous comment by Trinamool Congress MP Tapas Pal has brought to light how politicians are getting away with making crass comments against women.</itunes:subtitle>
                    <itunes:summary>The outrageous comment by Trinamool Congress MP Tapas Pal has brought to light how politicians are getting away with making crass comments against women. In a video, the TMC MP was seen issuing threats of sending his men to rape women if anyone harmed his party workers. The incident also brought into the fore a disturbing fact that police or law enforcement agencies are unwilling to take action against leaders from ruling parties. But Tapas Pal is not alone. In the past, Mulayam Singh Yadav, Rita Bahuguna Joshi, CPIM's Anisur Rehman have all passed such insensitive comments. So how do we prevent our netas from making such insensitive comments or issuing threats? Should filing of FIRs be made mandatory? Or should the change come from within the political establishment? We debate on The Big Fight.</itunes:summary>
                    <itunes:image href="http://i.ndtvimg.com/video/images/vod/thumb/2014-07/thumb_328736_1404578296.jpg"/>
                    <enclosure url="http://voddownload.ndtv.com.edgesuite.net/mp3/2014-07/05072014_n_PrimeShowTheBigFight_Merge_320564_15113_283749_114841.mp3" length="171136" type="audio/mpeg"/>
                    <guid>http://voddownload.ndtv.com.edgesuite.net/mp3/2014-07/05072014_n_PrimeShowTheBigFight_Merge_320564_15113_283749_114841.mp3</guid>
                    <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jul 2014 23:19:55 +0530</pubDate>
                    <itunes:duration>44:34</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords>Trinamool Congress MPs,Trinamool Congress MP rape remark,Tapas Pal,Bengali actor,TMC leader's comment,Mulayam Singh Yadav,Rita Bahuguna Joshi,Remarks Against women,Rape remarks</itunes:keywords>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>The Big Fight: How to Prevent Illegal Immigration?</title>
                    <itunes:author>NDTV</itunes:author>
                    <itunes:subtitle>The debate was started in the run up to Lok Sabha polls by PM Narendra Modi. Addressing a gathering in West Bengal he had issued threats that if BJP comes to power Bangladeshi illegal immigrants will have to pack their bags and leave the country.</itunes:subtitle>
                    <itunes:summary>The debate was started in the run up to Lok Sabha polls by PM Narendra Modi. Addressing a gathering in West Bengal he had issued threats that if BJP comes to power Bangladeshi illegal immigrants will have to pack their bags and leave the country. But is it practically possible to identify illegal immigrants and deport them? Is the issue of illegal immigration a political hot potato? Are illegal immigrants a threat to country's security? Or should India issue work permit for illegal immigrants? We debate on The Big Fight.</itunes:summary>
                    <itunes:image href="http://i.ndtvimg.com/video/images/vod/thumb/2014-06/thumb_326771_1403369225.jpg"/>
                    <enclosure url="http://voddownload.ndtv.com.edgesuite.net/mp3/2014-06/21062014_n_PrimeShowTheBigFight_Merge_317221_14780_281546_113956.mp3" length="188288" type="audio/mpeg"/>
                    <guid>http://voddownload.ndtv.com.edgesuite.net/mp3/2014-06/21062014_n_PrimeShowTheBigFight_Merge_317221_14780_281546_113956.mp3</guid>
                    <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2014 23:02:51 +0530</pubDate>
                    <itunes:duration>49:02</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords>Illegal Immigration,The Big Fight,Narendra Modi,Lok Sabha polls,BJP,illegal immigrants,Bangladesh</itunes:keywords>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>The Big Fight over language</title>
                    <itunes:author>NDTV</itunes:author>
                    <itunes:subtitle>The fight over supremacy of language in India started before independence and is still continuing. With the newly elected Prime Minister speaking in Hindi the question is will Hindi make a comeback?</itunes:subtitle>
                    <itunes:summary>The fight over supremacy of language in India started before independence and is still continuing. With the newly elected Prime Minister speaking in Hindi the question is will Hindi make a comeback? Should Hindi be the only national language or should English be the language for all official purposes? Is it wrong to forcibly impose Hindi over the rest of the country? And the most important question of all - are we neglecting our mother tongue vis-a-vis English? Join us on The Big Fight to know what suits India, a multilingual country.</itunes:summary>
                    <itunes:image href="http://i.ndtvimg.com/video/images/vod/thumb/2014-06/thumb_325785_1402763177.jpg"/>
                    <enclosure url="http://voddownload.ndtv.com.edgesuite.net/mp3/2014-06/14062014_n_PrimeShowTheBigFight_Merge_315656_14613_280438_113550.mp3" length="189120" type="audio/mpeg"/>
                    <guid>http://voddownload.ndtv.com.edgesuite.net/mp3/2014-06/14062014_n_PrimeShowTheBigFight_Merge_315656_14613_280438_113550.mp3</guid>
                    <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2014 21:27:29 +0530</pubDate>
                    <itunes:duration>49:15</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords>Hindi,Reional Languages,Prime Minister,Modi Govt,English,The Big Fight</itunes:keywords>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>FIFA 2014: Who Will Win The Football World Cup?</title>
                    <itunes:author>Vikram Chandra</itunes:author>
                    <itunes:subtitle>The Football World Cup will kickstart in Brazil on June 12. So which are the favourite teams to win the World Cup and is there any realistic chance for India to reach the World Cup?</itunes:subtitle>
                    <itunes:summary>Come June 12 and the greatest show on earth - The Football World Cup - will kickstart in Brazil. This one-month will be a treat for all football aficionados. The world will be mesmerised by Messi's dribble, Ronaldo's header, Iniesta's magic and Neymar's outrageous Left Foot. So which are the favourite teams to win the World Cup? Will Messi dazzle this time? Will Brazil triumph at Marcana? Can CR7 win the Golden Ball? Will Spain make it two in a row? Is there any realistic chance for India to reach the World Cup?</itunes:summary>
                    <itunes:image href="http://i.ndtvimg.com/video/images/vod/thumb/2014-06/thumb_324821_1402158396.jpg"/>
                    <enclosure url="http://voddownload.ndtv.com.edgesuite.net/mp3/2014-06/07062014_n_TheBigFight_14401_279188_112847.mp3" length="182848" type="audio/mpeg"/>
                    <guid>http://voddownload.ndtv.com.edgesuite.net/mp3/2014-06/07062014_n_TheBigFight_14401_279188_112847.mp3</guid>
                    <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2014 21:35:44 +0530</pubDate>
                    <itunes:duration>47:37</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords>FIFA World Cup 2014,football,The Big Fight,Football World Cup 2014,Ronaldo,Messi</itunes:keywords>
                </item>
            </channel>
        </rss>
    </httpclient:body>
</httpclient:response>