<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<httpclient:response xmlns:httpclient="http://exist-db.org/xquery/httpclient" statusCode="200">
    <httpclient:headers>
        <httpclient:header name="Server" value="Apache/2.2.22 (Ubuntu)"/>
        <httpclient:header name="X-Libsyn-Host" value="web-engine4.libsyn.com"/>
        <httpclient:header name="Vary" value="Accept-Encoding"/>
        <httpclient:header name="Content-Type" value="application/rss+xml"/>
        <httpclient:header name="last-modified" value="Sat, 16 Aug 2014 15:57:11 GMT"/>
        <httpclient:header name="Content-Length" value="259957"/>
        <httpclient:header name="Accept-Ranges" value="bytes"/>
        <httpclient:header name="Date" value="Wed, 20 Aug 2014 09:17:47 GMT"/>
        <httpclient:header name="X-Varnish" value="2177970819 2145389607"/>
        <httpclient:header name="Age" value="322166"/>
        <httpclient:header name="Via" value="1.1 varnish"/>
        <httpclient:header name="Connection" value="close"/>
        <httpclient:header name="X-Cache" value="HIT"/>
    </httpclient:headers>
    <httpclient:body mimetype="application/rss+xml" type="xml">
        <rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:cc="http://web.resource.org/cc/" version="2.0">
            <channel>
                <atom:link href="http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
                <title>A Buddhist Podcast</title>
                <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2014 05:39:45 +0000</pubDate>
                <lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2014 15:57:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
                <generator>Libsyn WebEngine 2.0</generator>
                <link>http://www.abuddhistpodcast.com</link>
                <language>en</language>
                <copyright>©2008-2011 Jason Jarrett</copyright>
                <docs>http://www.abuddhistpodcast.com</docs>
                <managingEditor>jason@thejarretts.com (jason@thejarretts.com)</managingEditor>
                <description>Another great podcast hosted by LibSyn.com</description>
                <image>
                    <url>http://assets.libsyn.com/content/5915030.jpg</url>
                    <title>A Buddhist Podcast</title>
                    <link>http://www.abuddhistpodcast.com</link>
                </image>
                <itunes:author>Jason Jarrett</itunes:author>
                <itunes:category text="Religion &amp; Spirituality"/>
                <itunes:category text="Religion &amp; Spirituality">
                    <itunes:category text="Buddhism"/>
                </itunes:category>
                <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/5915030.jpg"/>
                <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
                <itunes:owner>
                    <itunes:name>Jason Jarrett</itunes:name>
                    <itunes:email>jason@thejarretts.com</itunes:email>
                </itunes:owner>
                <itunes:summary>This Podcast is a free show about the Buddhism of Nichiren Daishonin. Jason and Karen are members of the Soka Gakkai. Every two weeks they take a Buddhist study point and do their best to make it easy to understand and of use to anyone who listens.
Practical Buddhism for living in the 21st Century, not beside a remote lake or mountainside but in the midst of daily life, with a job to do, a house to run and children to raise.</itunes:summary>
                <itunes:subtitle>A Buddhist Podcast</itunes:subtitle>
                <item>
                    <title>On Practicing the Buddha's Teachings - February 2nd 2014</title>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2014 05:39:45 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">004b74a42f7bb861f97d78b0e1e83d94</guid>
                    <link>http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/on-practicing-the-buddha-s-teachings-february-2nd-2014</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/2660855"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to the first show of the year! Tonights Jason lectures on the writing, On Practicing The Buddha's Teachings. His lecture is based on President Ikeda's lectures series from The Teaching for Victory.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some of the theme for tonight include:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From provisional to true&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;How did Buddhism get so confused&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Former, middle and latter day of the law&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An accursed time&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Changing our minds&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The banner of our behaviour&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Archers of the mystic law&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Three carts and the burning house&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Shakabuku, compassion and reason&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Using struggles to become happy&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We have an great and inspiring experience that covers 40 year of faith from Roxanne Rae in Oregan. We also have music from Nic Saunders who kindly allowed us to play a piece from his Weald and Downland Suite, its called The Water Mill. From the pod safe music network we have Geoff Smith playing Gravity and Death Cab for Cutie with Title and Registration.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you so much for continuing to listen and support the show. Have an amazing week!&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="90244702" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/On_practicing_the_buddhas_teachings_Feb_2014.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:32:54</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Welcome to the first show of the year! Tonights Jason lectures on the writing, On Practicing The Buddha's Teachings. His lecture is based on President Ikeda's lectures series from The Teaching for Victory.
Some of the theme for tonight include:
From...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Death and dying part 1</title>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2013 03:28:58 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">fe393fd69050e829c5aabe5e73716202</guid>
                    <link>http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/death-and-dying-part-1</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/2386960"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to a podcast that took a long time to write! Tonights show is about death and dying from a Buddhist perspective. My lecture is based on President Ikeda's lecture in Unlocking the Mysteries of Life and Death. I am also very grateful to Donna and Dash for sharing their experience!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Subjects include:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nobody believes they are going to die&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;How do you want to feel when you die?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Near death experiences&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;5 stages of dying&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;3 paths into 3 virtues&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And then there was one&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nam myoho renge kyo is not constrained by death&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Eagle peak and mystical rendezvous&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are responsible for how we die&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Of course we have some music on the show. First up we have the Canadian, Christie Grace, courtesy of the Podsafe Music Network, playing her version of Joni Mitchells track, Both Sides Now. Beautiful voice! We also have the one and only Howard Jones, singing Building our own future. Thank you so much for all your support and encouragement. Have an amazing week!&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="67355232" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/Death_and_dying_part_1.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:09:55</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Welcome to a podcast that took a long time to write! Tonights show is about death and dying from a Buddhist perspective. My lecture is based on President Ikeda's lecture in Unlocking the Mysteries of Life and Death. I am also very grateful to Donna...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>The Three Kinds of Treasure</title>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2013 23:49:55 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">f4bf73b09664fd069558149945d2b81c</guid>
                    <link>http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/the-three-kinds-of-treasure</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/5612579"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Thank you so much for waiting. Welcome to the first show from our new home in Vancouver, Canada. Tonights lecture is based on some passages from a famous letter written by Nichiren Daishonin to his loyal disciple Shijo Kingo. My lecture is based on the first half of President Ikeda&amp;rsquo;s lecture on The Three Kinds of Treasure which can be found in SGI Newsletter No 7908.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Shijo Kingo is in the middle of a huge struggle and has written to Nichiren for guidance in faith on how he should go forward. Some of the points we cover include:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Practicing as Nichiren taught&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Encouraging each other revitalises the SGI&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Treasuring others&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The honest friendship of Nichiren and Shijo Kingo&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Backgammon&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Breakthroughs and victories&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Huge targets and how we achieve them&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The tragedy of jealousy&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We have a lot of shout outs and almost as many questions! We play two tracks from the Podsafe Music Network on tonights show. First we play Falling by Grace Kelly and later we have Gravity by Geoff Smith (who does the intro music to the show!).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you so much for listening and for your encouragement, support and patience while we have been moving! Have the best week of your lives and take great care of each other.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="65491790" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/The_three_kinds_of_treasure.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:08:00</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Thank you so much for waiting. Welcome to the first show from our new home in Vancouver, Canada. Tonights lecture is based on some passages from a famous letter written by Nichiren Daishonin to his loyal disciple Shijo Kingo. My lecture is based on...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>The four of us at the kitchen table</title>
                    <pubDate>Sat, 24 Nov 2012 20:25:36 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">fe87a148592cf0fb9fc3503b289708d8</guid>
                    <link>http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/the-four-of-us-at-the-kitchen-table</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/2136799"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;A few weeks ago we had the good fortune of having William Woollard, Matt MacMillan and Karen and myself sat around our kitchen table. We read two lovely experiences about relationships with mothers, one from two sisters in India, Bipasha van der Zijde &amp;amp; Bishaka Dalvi. The other experience was from Kelvin Lam.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We swapped stories and experiences and played music from the Podsafe music including, Levi Blues by the Lala Girls, Mine Again by Black Lab and Yael Naim with New Soul.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The editing took some time and I was able to get the file ready to the digital work on the plane to Brisbane, where when we land I hope to post online!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you very much everyone for the many birthday wishes you were kind enough to send and for all your good wishes about our forthcoming move to Vancouver. We are continuing to study hard and have started writing the lecture for the next show, so bear with us as we embark on the next crazy adventure. I think its about time we shared an experience of how we have done this, what do you think?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="77746356" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/abp_the_four_of_us.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:20:34</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>A few weeks ago we had the good fortune of having William Woollard, Matt MacMillan and Karen and myself sat around our kitchen table. We read two lovely experiences about relationships with mothers, one from two sisters in India, Bipasha van der Zijde...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>A Ship to Cross the Sea of Suffering – Part 2</title>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 08 Oct 2012 21:29:55 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">aba2f58086dd014410984881e620e358</guid>
                    <link>http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/a-ship-to-cross-the-sea-of-suffering-part-2</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/2090128"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Longer than we expected but none the less, here we are again with the second of a two part lecture on a letter written by Nichiren Daishonin to Shiiji Shiro in 1261. The letter is called A Ship to Cross the Sea of Suffering. This lecture is based on SGI President Ikedas lecture in SGI Newsletter 8518. It was a challenge to get this done and I suspect you may need to listen a couple of times to pick up all the points. Subjects include:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;a ship to cross the water,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;five flavours,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;discarding earlier teachings,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;unfurling the sail, 3000 realms,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;middle way,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;leaving the dock of our karma,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;tickets of faith,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;the good ship SGI.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We have shoutouts and a question about chanting for stuff! We play Howard Jones singing Building Our Own Future and courtesy of the Podsafe Music Network we play Let me know by the Fire Apes. Thank you for your constant encouragement, it means so much to us. Click on the link on the left hand side of the website if you want a shout out on the show. Take great care and have a fantastic week. Thank you for listening.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="52203639" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/A_ship_to_cross_the_sea_of_suffering_part_2.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>53:42</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Longer than we expected but none the less, here we are again with the second of a two part lecture on a letter written by Nichiren Daishonin to Shiiji Shiro in 1261. The letter is called A Ship to Cross the Sea of Suffering. This lecture is based on...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>A Ship to Cross the Sea of Suffering - Part 1</title>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 09 Sep 2012 15:56:24 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">e6b3c896e940825404416b968c95a03f</guid>
                    <link>http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/a-ship-to-cross-the-sea-of-suffering-part-1</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/2059823"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;We are back with the first of a two part lecture on a letter written by Nichiren Daishonin called A Ship to Cross the Sea of Suffering. The lecture is based on SGI President Ikeda&amp;rsquo;s guidance in SGI Newsletter 8518 which was giving in May this year.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Subjects we cover include:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Connecting our hearts to those around us&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Who was Shiiji Shiro?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;See like Li Lou, hear like Shih K&amp;rsquo;uang&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Faith rooted in action&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Teaching others about Buddhism&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The voice does the Buddha&amp;rsquo;s work&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A single sentence or phrase&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Karen reads a wonderful experience by Sue Davis from Essex in the UK. We also have some great music starting off with Smile by Robin Lukas (written by Barbara Pool). We also play Lucky Day by Stavia and $12.99 by Dave Potts from the Podsafe Music Network.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We have lots of shouts outs as well! Thank you all so much for supporting and encouraging us! If you want a shout out on the show, write and let us know or click the link on the left hand side of our website &amp;ldquo;Shoutouts&amp;rdquo;. If you have a great experience of practicing this Buddhism that you would be happy for us to read on the show, you can click the link for Experiences on the site! Thank you so much for listening, take care and have a wonderful week.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="80812717" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/A_ship_to_cross_the_sea_of_suffering_part_1.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:23:30</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>We are back with the first of a two part lecture on a letter written by Nichiren Daishonin called A Ship to Cross the Sea of Suffering. The lecture is based on SGI President Ikeda&amp;rsquo;s guidance in SGI Newsletter 8518 which was giving in May this...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Letter to the Lay Priest Nakaoki</title>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jun 2012 11:22:17 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">88062b729e03cc652abfef03f008ba50</guid>
                    <link>http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/letter-to-the-lay-priest-nakaoki</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/1979603"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Well finally we are back with another episode of A Buddhist Podcast! Its been a long gap since the last show, so thank you for your patience.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On tonights show Jason and Karen give a lecture on a letter written by Nichiren Daishonin called Letter to Nakaoki. The lectures is based on the lecture given by SGI President Ikeda in SGI Newsletter 8294. Subjects we cover include:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Buddhism before Nichiren&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Individuals create change&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Buddhism in daily life&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Protection from within invites protection from without&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Compassionate correction&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hoisting the banner of Buddhism&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;120&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Eagle Peak&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;How do you want to die?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Karens talk&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lives that contribute&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We have shout outs that criss cross the globe. We have a great experience from Anuraag Khanna We play a great track, Happy, by Adrianne Richards from the Podsafe Music Network. We also play an independent track that we fell in love with called Right Here by Annette Beja.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you want a shout out on the show, write and let us know or click the link on the left hand side of our website "Shoutouts". If you have a great experience of practicing this Buddhism that you would be happy for us to read on the show, you can click the link for Experiences on the site!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you so much for listening, take care and have a wonderful week.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="73050066" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/ABP_Letter_to_the_Lay_Priest_Nakaoki.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:16:04</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Well finally we are back with another episode of A Buddhist Podcast! Its been a long gap since the last show, so thank you for your patience.
On tonights show Jason and Karen give a lecture on a letter written by Nichiren Daishonin called Letter to...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Buddhism and the science of happiness - Appendix B</title>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 15 Apr 2012 09:12:27 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">dadf6b246143f7fd08735b05aa93de65</guid>
                    <link>http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/buddhism-and-the-science-of-happiness-appendix-b</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/1917797"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to another episode of A Buddhist Podcast! On tonights show we have William Woollard reading the last part of Buddhism and the science of happiness, Appendix B. This is the show that is for every beginner you have ever wanted to have something to say, "Here, listen to this, this is the basics of Buddhism!"&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By popular demand we have some more questions that we do our best to answer as well as the traditional shootouts!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In addition, we have music from the Podsafe Music Network. We play England by the great band, Great Big Sea and When We Are Old by Molly Magdalain.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is the first show that we use the new octa capture interface from Roland, so let us know what you make of the sound, we want to improve!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Have a fabulous week and thank you so much for listening.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="74917488" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/Buddhism_and_the_science_of_happiness_-_Appendix_B.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:17:47</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Welcome to another episode of A Buddhist Podcast! On tonights show we have William Woollard reading the last part of Buddhism and the science of happiness, Appendix B. This is the show that is for every beginner you have ever wanted to have something...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>The Offering of the Mud Pie</title>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Apr 2012 12:19:18 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">0ced8e1283bbf90f854e826fcaa40e78</guid>
                    <link>http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/the-offering-of-the-mud-pie</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/1904018"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Wow! This show was a challenge to bring you! In the first part of the show which we recorded last week we have William Woollard giving a lecture on Nichiren Daishonin's writing called, The Offering of the Mud Pie. Its a terrific lecture and we hope you enjoy listening to it as much as we enjoyed recording it!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A good friend of the show sent us an email and Karen and Jason talk about their reactions and thoughts to it. During the editing, Jason wished he had said more about gratitude in his answer, but then that will be coming up in a lecture soon! Let us know what you think of this section, if its popular we might do some more!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We have music from the podsafe music network tonight. Firstly, we play David Ushers track, The Music, from his successful album Strange Birds. We close with a wonderful track from Adrina Thorpes album, Halflight and Shadows called Everything Changes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you for taking the time to download the show and listen. Have a fantastic week and take great care of yourselves.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="71233668" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/The_Offering_of_the_Mud_Pie.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:14:06</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Wow! This show was a challenge to bring you! In the first part of the show which we recorded last week we have William Woollard giving a lecture on Nichiren Daishonin's writing called, The Offering of the Mud Pie. Its a terrific lecture and we hope...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Buddhism and the science of happiness - Chapter 16 and Appendix A</title>
                    <pubDate>Tue, 13 Mar 2012 21:09:36 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">b69a0f9d10c272613e89e9ca5a75ec3c</guid>
                    <link>http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/buddhism-and-the-science-of-happiness-chapter-16-and-appendix-a</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/1886314"/>
                    <description>&lt;p style="margin: 0.0px 0.0px 0.0px 0.0px; font: 12.0px Osaka;"&gt;And we are back with A Buddhist Podcast! Thank you for downloading the show! Tonight we have William Woollard reading Chapter 16 and Appendix A from Buddhism and the science of happiness. We also have an experience from Uri Rosenrauch in New York City, which was so much fun to read and record.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0.0px 0.0px 0.0px 0.0px; font: 12.0px Osaka;"&gt;As usual we have shoutouts from all over the world and music from the Podsafe Music Network. We play Reach Out by Beatrice Ericsson, Not on the radio by Geoff Smith and 143 by the Australian band, Stingray!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0.0px 0.0px 0.0px 0.0px; font: 12.0px Osaka;"&gt;Take great care and have a fabulous week!&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="49884566" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/Buddhism_and_the_science_of_happiness_-_Chapter_16_and_Appendix_A.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>51:53</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>And we are back with A Buddhist Podcast! Thank you for downloading the show! Tonight we have William Woollard reading Chapter 16 and Appendix A from Buddhism and the science of happiness. We also have an experience from Uri Rosenrauch in New York...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Buddhism and the science of happiness - Chapter 15</title>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2012 14:05:06 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">fada93f034a5ee68856d05ab054f507f</guid>
                    <link>http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/buddhism-and-the-science-of-happiness-chapter-15</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/1857895"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to another episode of A Buddhist Podcast. Thank you for taking the time to download and listen to this show. On tonights show we have William Woollard back in the kitchen to read Chapter 15 from his amazing book, Buddhism and the science of happiness.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jason talks about his brief trip to SGI headquarters and we have shout outs and of course music. Music from tonights show comes from the Podsafe Music Network a part of the Mevio group. Chris Ayer sings Awake and the Dala Girls are back with Anywhere under the moon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Take care and have a wonderful week.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="42078245" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/Buddhism_and_the_science_of_happiness_-_Chapter_15.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>43:45</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Welcome to another episode of A Buddhist Podcast. Thank you for taking the time to download and listen to this show. On tonights show we have William Woollard back in the kitchen to read Chapter 15 from his amazing book, Buddhism and the science of...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>William interviews Karen and Jason</title>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2012 12:50:23 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">5d3ca77a077fbd7b6a36b4e32a3915c8</guid>
                    <link>http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/william-interviews-karen-and-jason</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/1834764"/>
                    <description>&lt;p class="MsoNormal" style="tab-stops: 28.3pt 56.65pt 85.0pt 113.35pt 141.7pt 170.05pt 198.4pt 226.75pt 255.1pt 283.45pt 311.8pt 340.15pt;"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US"&gt;Thank you for taking the time to download and listen to the show. We are back with another episode of A Buddhist Podcast. On tonights show we read an editorial written by SGI President Ikeda encouraging young women and we play a recording in which William Woollard interviews Karen and Jason about the podcast.&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal" style="tab-stops: 28.3pt 56.65pt 85.0pt 113.35pt 141.7pt 170.05pt 198.4pt 226.75pt 255.1pt 283.45pt 311.8pt 340.15pt;"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US"&gt;As usual we have shout outs that criss cross the globe and some great music. On tonights show we play a song written by an SGI - UK member and sung by Olivia and Florence when they were 6 and 9 years old respectively. We play Cardboard Dreams by the very talented Ellie Jamison from Cambridge in the UK, listen to the lyrics, its really well written. Also we have two great tracks from the Podsafe Music Network, the amazing Molly Magdalain singing a track that definitely gets to Jason, its called Movin On. We finish with the amazing Dala Girls who sing Levi Blues that somehow always gets us smiling!&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal" style="tab-stops: 28.3pt 56.65pt 85.0pt 113.35pt 141.7pt 170.05pt 198.4pt 226.75pt 255.1pt 283.45pt 311.8pt 340.15pt;"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US"&gt;We send you our very best for a truly wonderful week and thank you from the bottom of our hearts for all your support and encouragement!&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="70347820" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/William_interviews_Karen_and_Jason.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:13:10</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Thank you for taking the time to download and listen to the show. We are back with another episode of A Buddhist Podcast. On tonights show we read an editorial written by SGI President Ikeda encouraging young women and we play a recording in which...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Buddhism and the science of happiness - chapter 14</title>
                    <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2012 21:14:25 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">384212e73a3f9d706e04e50b26d2b7a3</guid>
                    <link>http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/buddhism-and-the-science-of-happiness-chapter-14</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/1819033"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Happy New Year everyone! Welcome to another episode of A Buddhist Podcast! On tonights show we have the wonderful William Woollard reading chapter 14 from Buddhism and the science of happiness.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We have two tracks from the Podsafe Music Network. Firstly we play What To Do With Michael by the Candy Butchers. Secondly we play a new artist to the show, Molly Magdalain singing Gentle War from her album The Open Road.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As usual we have the shoutouts and chat from us. Thank you so much for listening, take care and have a great week.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="41248069" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/Buddhism_and_the_science_of_happiness_-_Chapter_14.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>42:51</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Happy New Year everyone! Welcome to another episode of A Buddhist Podcast! On tonights show we have the wonderful William Woollard reading chapter 14 from Buddhism and the science of happiness.
We have two tracks from the Podsafe Music Network....</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>On Practicing the Buddhas Teachings - part 2</title>
                    <pubDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2011 19:08:36 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">ce096a16058172c8e20b43ebbc4e4a13</guid>
                    <link>http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/on-practicing-the-buddhas-teachings-part-2</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/1802073"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Thank you for downloading this show and welcome to another episode of A Buddhist Podcast. On tonights show we have a lecture from Jason. The lecture is based on President Ikeda's third lecture on Nichiren Daishonins letter, On Practicing the Buddha's Teachings. Here is a snifter of some the subjects we cover:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sitting down to study with the Buddha&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Handing over responsibility to the youth&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Practicing as the Buddha taught&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Changing ourselves changes the world&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Compassion amidst our struggle&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Doing the right thing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Chanting Nam-myoho-renge-kyo&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A real king in the religious world&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We have a very moving experience from Sharon in Hong Kong as well as shoutouts that criss cross the globe! Courtesy of the Podsafe Music Network, we play Some People Say from the Saucier album by Ed &amp;amp; Jojo aka the Supersuckers and quite possibly one of our most favourite tracks, Great Day by Jody Gnant!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you so much for listening to the show, we really appreciate your encouragement and supporting emails and contacts. Please take great care of each other and have a most fabulous week.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="72583454" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/On_Practicing_the_Buddhas_Teachings_part_2.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:15:37</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Thank you for downloading this show and welcome to another episode of A Buddhist Podcast. On tonights show we have a lecture from Jason. The lecture is based on President Ikeda's third lecture on Nichiren Daishonins letter, On Practicing the Buddha's...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Buddhism and the science of happiness - chapters 12 and 13</title>
                    <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2011 20:12:01 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">cdc97cc2e21a571b1e9eabb2ed981124</guid>
                    <link>http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/buddhism-and-the-science-of-happiness-chapters-12-and-13</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/3954806"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;We are back with a very full show for you tonight. We have the wonderful William Woollard reading from his new book, Buddhism and the science of happiness. Tonight he reads Chapters 12 and 13! Great news that his earlier book, The Reluctant Buddhist is now available in Spanish!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Also tonight we were very lucky to have the amazing Lucille Barclay who came to our home to give her experience and took part in the show as well!&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We play four tracks tonight from the Podsafe Music Network. First up is Stavia with Lucky Day, then Wonder by the Fire Apes, Rocky Votolato with White Daisy Passing and finally Can't Believe by Pippa Rogers.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As usual we have shout outs and we pop a bottle of champagne to celebrate 6 years of doing the show and 1.3 million downloads! Have a fabulous week everyone!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="68802165" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/Buddhism_and_the_science_of_happiness_-_chapters_12_and_13.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:11:23</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>We are back with a very full show for you tonight. We have the wonderful William Woollard reading from his new book, Buddhism and the science of happiness. Tonight he reads Chapters 12 and 13! Great news that his earlier book, The Reluctant Buddhist...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Buddhism and the science of happiness - Chapter 11</title>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2011 21:26:19 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">240b8335f6707542fa35127aea8e89b1</guid>
                    <link>http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/buddhism-and-the-science-of-happiness-chapter-11</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/1735015"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;We are back with another show! Tonight we have William Woollard reading Chapter 11 of his great book, Buddhism and the science of happiness.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Also we have an experience from the wonderful Steve Sant (picture of both of us in the artwork for this show!) and music from the Podsafe Music Network. We play two songs from the band, Black Lab. You might want to turn it up, and some of you might want to turn it down for their tracks, Broken Heart and Without You!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Shoutouts and chat from Karen and Jason. Thank you so much for listening. Have a wonderful week wherever you are.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="49731007" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/Buddhism_and_the_science_of_happiness_-_Chapter_11.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>51:44</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>We are back with another show! Tonight we have William Woollard reading Chapter 11 of his great book, Buddhism and the science of happiness.
Also we have an experience from the wonderful Steve Sant (picture of both of us in the artwork for this show!)...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Buddhism and the science of happiness - Chapter 10</title>
                    <pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2011 19:45:57 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">67c1b93fa8e5b43ff857caec257a73e6</guid>
                    <link>http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/buddhism-and-the-science-of-happiness-chapter-10</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/1717736"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to another episode of A Buddhist Podcast! On tonights show we have the wonderful William Woollard reading from his amazing book, Buddhism and science of happiness. Tonigh he reads Chapter 10!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Also on the show we have music from Nick Daugherty who sings Movin' Higher and the great band, a long time favourite of ours, Carbon Leaf with The War Was in Colour. Both tracks tonight are available for us to play thanks to the Podsafe Music Network at Mevio.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We have shoutouts and banter between Karen and Jason. Thank you again for listening. Take great care and have a fabulous week!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="58292646" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/Buddhism_and_the_science_of_happiness_-_Chapter_10.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:00:36</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Welcome to another episode of A Buddhist Podcast! On tonights show we have the wonderful William Woollard reading from his amazing book, Buddhism and science of happiness. Tonigh he reads Chapter 10!
Also on the show we have music from Nick Daugherty...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>On practising the Buddha's teachings - Lecture</title>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2011 11:54:12 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">bd9f054db242886d93f3f13e96c96c74</guid>
                    <link>http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/on-practising-the-buddha-s-teachings-lecture</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/1707690"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome back to another episode of A Buddhist Podcast! We have been away travelling, but we are back with a lecture for you based on President Ikeda's lecture from SGI Newsletter NL7973XV. The lecture is about a letter written by Nichiren Daishonin called, "On Practicing The Buddha's Teachings". Themes include:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My first campaign&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The correct teacher&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Four powers&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The brave question&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;42 years of preparation&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Golden words&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Shakabuku and Shoju&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Practicing correctly&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As usual our music tonight comes from Podsafe Music Network at Musicalley.com. We play Round the Bend by Adrina Thorpe and Anywhere Under The Moon by the Dala Girls.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once again, if you want a shout out on the show, write and let us know or click the link on the left hand side of our website "Shoutouts". If you have a great experience of practicing this Buddhism that you would be happy for us to read on the show, you can click the link for Experiences on the site!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you so much for listening, take care and have a wonderful week.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="59090956" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/On_practicing_the_Buddhas_teachings.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:01:25</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Welcome back to another episode of A Buddhist Podcast! We have been away travelling, but we are back with a lecture for you based on President Ikeda's lecture from SGI Newsletter NL7973XV. The lecture is about a letter written by Nichiren Daishonin...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Buddhism and the science of happiness - chapter 8 and 9</title>
                    <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2011 22:02:38 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">48c919c335c4804f6b6f6b3ec5ac6e43</guid>
                    <link>http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/buddhism-and-the-science-of-happiness-chapter-8-and-9</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/1643920"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;We are so pleased to be back with you tonight with another show! We have William Woollard reading chapters 8 and 9 from his great book, Buddhism and the science of the happiness!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We have music from the Podsafe Music Network who are currently having their website upgraded for a better experience so check it out! The music we play is from Phil Ayoub who sings Goodnight Kiss, Dala with their great track Levi Blues and the amazing Stavia singing one of our favourites, Lucky Day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We have the shoutouts and our travel itinerary for the next frew months. Have a fantastic week everyone!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="59978258" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/Buddhism_and_the_science_of_happiness_chapter_8_and_9.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:02:19</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>We are so pleased to be back with you tonight with another show! We have William Woollard reading chapters 8 and 9 from his great book, Buddhism and the science of the happiness!
We have music from the Podsafe Music Network who are currently having...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Buddhism and the science of happiness - Chapter 7</title>
                    <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2011 13:20:18 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">dd44a6f80d198f065af2627dc79b5dd5</guid>
                    <link>http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/buddhism-and-the-science-of-happiness-chapter-7</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/1606493"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Here we are again for another episode of A Buddhist Podcast! On tonights packed show we begin with the wonderful William Woollard reading chapter 7 from his book, Buddhism and the science of happiness. The book is available on Amazon and is in English, Italian and Spanish and probably many more languages in the future.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dash and Donna from Sacramento join us in our kitchen for the shout outs and for an amazing experience from Stevie Knights.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tonights music again comes from the great folks at Mevio.com. We play two older tracks tonight, Title and Registration by Deathcab for Cutie and the very talented Matthew Ebel sings I Know Your There..&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you want a shout out on the show, let us know by clicking the link on the left hand side of our website "Shoutouts", or you can send us a note if you have the iPhone, IPad or Android app for A Buddhist Podcast. If you have a great experience of practicing this Buddhism that you would be happy for us to read on the show, you can click the link to submit your experiences on the site!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you so much for continuing to listen, have a wonderful week, stay safe and look after yourself and everyone around you.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="57413731" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/Buddhism_and_the_Science_of_Happiness_-_Chapter_7.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>59:41</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Here we are again for another episode of A Buddhist Podcast! On tonights packed show we begin with the wonderful William Woollard reading chapter 7 from his book, Buddhism and the science of happiness. The book is available on Amazon and is in...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Buddhism and the Science of Happiness - Chapter 5 and 6</title>
                    <pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2011 20:13:19 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">6b07b687daf3947ffae2843c8bffacfb</guid>
                    <link>http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/buddhism-and-the-science-of-happiness-chapter-5-and-6</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/1586982"/>
                    <description>&lt;div style="background-image: initial; background-attachment: initial; background-origin: initial; background-clip: initial; background-color: #ffffff; font: normal normal normal 13px/19px Georgia, 'Times New Roman', 'Bitstream Charter', Times, serif; font-family: Times; font-size: medium; padding: 0.6em; margin: 0px;"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tonights show is very full! We have the wonderful&amp;nbsp;&lt;a title="Link to William on wikipedia" href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/William_Woollard" _mce_href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/William_Woollard" target="_blank"&gt;William Woollard&amp;nbsp;&lt;/a&gt;reading chapters 5 and 6 from his amazing book,&lt;a title="Link to book on Amazon" href="http://www.amazon.co.uk/Buddhism-Science-Happiness-Personal-Exploration/dp/1907652736" _mce_href="http://www.amazon.co.uk/Buddhism-Science-Happiness-Personal-Exploration/dp/1907652736" target="_blank"&gt;&amp;nbsp;Buddhism and the Science of Happiness&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;nbsp;We play three tracks tonight.&amp;nbsp;&lt;a title="Link to the album on ITunes" href="http://itunes.apple.com/gb/album/winning-hand-ep/id429249730" _mce_href="http://itunes.apple.com/gb/album/winning-hand-ep/id429249730" target="_blank"&gt;Spoons&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;and&amp;nbsp;&lt;a title="Link to album on Itunes" href="http://itunes.apple.com/gb/album/winning-hand-ep/id429249730" _mce_href="http://itunes.apple.com/gb/album/winning-hand-ep/id429249730" target="_blank"&gt;Winning Hand&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;by&amp;nbsp;&lt;a title="Link to Sheri Millers website" href="http://www.sherimiller.com/" _mce_href="http://www.sherimiller.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Sheri Miller&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;are from her brand new album, Winning Hand. Our thanks to the&lt;a href="http://musicalley.com" _mce_href="http://musicalley.com" target="_blank"&gt;Podsafe Music Network&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;for facilitating the playing of tonights music.&amp;nbsp;To finish the show we play the wake up track,&amp;nbsp;&lt;a title="Link to Love is True on ITunes" href="http://itunes.apple.com/gb/album/milk-it-single/id417212321" _mce_href="http://itunes.apple.com/gb/album/milk-it-single/id417212321" target="_blank"&gt;Love is True&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;by&amp;nbsp;&lt;a title="link to the website of The Palpitations" href="http://www.thepalpitations.co.uk/" _mce_href="http://www.thepalpitations.co.uk/" target="_blank"&gt;The Palpitations&lt;/a&gt;.If you like Karen's wonderful voice, listen in to her swiss german making a brief vocal appearance! Shoutouts to friends across the globe! Take great care and have a fabulous week. Thank you so much for listening.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="64544826" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/Buddhism_and_the_Science_of_Happiness_-_Chapter_5_and_6.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:07:09</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Tonights show is very full! We have the wonderful&amp;nbsp;William Woollard&amp;nbsp;reading chapters 5 and 6 from his amazing book,&amp;nbsp;Buddhism and the Science of Happiness.&amp;nbsp;We play three tracks tonight.&amp;nbsp;Spoons&amp;nbsp;and&amp;nbsp;Winning...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Buddhism and the Science of Happiness - Chapter 4</title>
                    <pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2011 20:30:11 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">c3aa828614ccf0d07bb4a5633a41390c</guid>
                    <link>http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/buddhism-and-the-science-of-happiness-chapter-4</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/1577457"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to another evening of A Buddhist Podcast!. Tonight we are very fortunate to be able to have William Woollard reading Chapter 4 from his new book, Buddhism and the Science of Happiness. Congratulations to William on the books recent translation into Spanish as well!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We have two tracks from the Podsafe Music Network to play for you tonight. First off, we have Spencer Lee singing Burnin the Bed. Second we have the wonderful Lascivious Biddies with Hell of a Boy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We have another run of shout outs as well! Thank you so much for continuing to listen to the show, we have just gone over the million downloads milestone with Libsyn. Thank you for being with us. Have a wonderful week!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="46471193" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/Buddhism_and_Science_of_Happiness_-_Chapter_4.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>48:21</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Welcome to another evening of A Buddhist Podcast!. Tonight we are very fortunate to be able to have William Woollard reading Chapter 4 from his new book, Buddhism and the Science of Happiness. Congratulations to William on the books recent translation...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Letter to Jakunichi-Bo April 2011</title>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2011 10:04:57 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">b7c12b88475bede0f268e2d5f30fc072</guid>
                    <link>http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/letter-to-jakunichi-bo-april-2011</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/1567476"/>
                    <description>&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;Jason is back from Japan and we are back with another show! Tonight we have a lecture for you on Nichiren Daishonin&amp;rsquo;s writing, &amp;ldquo;Letter to Jakunichi-Bo&amp;rdquo;. Based on Newsletter 7676, this is the second time Jason has lectured on this writing, but it&amp;rsquo;s so different! Themes include:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;Forging ordinary human beings into buddhas&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;Gohonzon, a blue print for Buddhahood&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;What are the odds being able to practice&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;The four virtues&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;Bodhisattva Superior Practices&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;Three powerful enemies&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;The right teacher&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;Three presidents&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;Johan Galtung&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;Tonight we have music from the Podsafe Music Network. We play Joe Strummer and the Mescaleros singing Coma Girl and Kelly Brock with Cowboy Boots and Levis. We have shoutouts and a quick catch up with Jason&amp;rsquo;s last few weeks. The artwork for tonights show is of the cherry blossom in Tokyo last week.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;Thank you so much for waiting and for taking the time to download the show. Have a fabulous week!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="60531017" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/Letter_to_Jakunichi-Bo_April_2011.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:02:49</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Jason is back from Japan and we are back with another show! Tonight we have a lecture for you on Nichiren Daishonin&amp;rsquo;s writing, &amp;ldquo;Letter to Jakunichi-Bo&amp;rdquo;. Based on Newsletter 7676, this is the second time Jason has lectured on this...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Buddhism and the Science of Happiness</title>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2011 08:47:26 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">777e6f78df7282cdf61ea05dea6dba7f</guid>
                    <link>http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/buddhism-and-the-science-of-happiness</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/1542014"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Welcome back to another episode of A Buddhist Podcast! On tonights show we have the amazing William Woollard reading Chapter 3, "So What's Religion All About?", from his book, Buddhism and the Science of Happiness.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We also have some questions about chanting and about the relationship between the priesthood and the SGI, frank and honest opinions from Jason.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We have three great pieces of music courtesy of Mevio.com. &amp;nbsp;The first track is Katie Websters record, "Hard Loving Mama" ; the second is Tom Waits with "You Can Never Hold Back Spring" and finally we have Slackstring playing their timeless, kick back and relax "Sun Will Shine Again". If you like the music please check the Music page on our website where we have added links to help you find the music to buy if you want to.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Shoutouts to people from all over the world. You know every email, review on ITunes, shout out request, facebook message, tweet that we receive is such encouragement for us both, thank you for making the time to both listen to the show and to let us know you care. Have a fantastic week!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="63316144" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/A_Buddhist_Podcast_-_Buddhism_and_the_Science_of_Happiness_-_Chapter_3.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:05:57</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords>podcast,william,jason,music,religion,karen,tom,buddhism,buddha,webster,katie,waits,jarrett,sgi,woollard,priesthood,slackstring</itunes:keywords>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Welcome back to another episode of A Buddhist Podcast! On tonights show we have the amazing William Woollard reading Chapter 3, "So What's Religion All About?", from his book, Buddhism and the Science of Happiness.
We also have some questions about...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>A Buddhist Podcast - Buddhism and the Science of Happiness - Chapter 2</title>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2011 08:26:29 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">9d97631cfd126cb29d7d1d4ff442d9af</guid>
                    <link>http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/a-buddhist-podcast-buddhism-and-the-science-of-happiness-chapter-2</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/1531919"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Well, we seem to be on a roll! Welcome to another episode of A Buddhist Podcast. We are delighted to present Chapter 2 from William Woollards new book, Buddhism and the Science of Happiness. Reading, recording and editing this chapter really gave me pause to think!&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thanks to the wonderful podsafe music network at mevio.com we were able to bring you three fantastic tracks tonight. The first is from Yael Naim who sings New Soul. The second and third are from a great and talented duo called the Dala Girls from Toronto, Canada. We play two tracks from the Dala Girls, Levi Blues and Hockey Sweater.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We have an experience from John Renner in the US and we read the World Tribunes obituary for David Kasahara who recently passed away. Our shoutouts criss cross the world and also Jason answers a question as to what the quotes are on the family alter.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As usual look to the right hand side of our website for the shoutout link if you want to make use of it. Alternatively you can send us a note on the Android or Iphone app! Thank you so much for your continued support. Please take great care and have a fabulous week. Sometimes its hard, but chant and determine to win, there is always a way through.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="69791838" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/A_Buddhist_Podcast_-_Buddhism_and_the_Science_of_Happiness_-_Chapter_2.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:12:41</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Well, we seem to be on a roll! Welcome to another episode of A Buddhist Podcast. We are delighted to present Chapter 2 from William Woollards new book, Buddhism and the Science of Happiness. Reading, recording and editing this chapter really gave me...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>A Buddhist Podcast - Buddhism and the Science of Happiness</title>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2011 22:00:27 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">7a45a57aa63b7c4897911abd9bce7eb0</guid>
                    <link>http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/a-buddhist-podcast-buddhism-and-the-science-of-happiness</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/1493635"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;
&lt;div style="background-image: initial; background-attachment: initial; background-origin: initial; background-clip: initial; background-color: #ffffff; font: normal normal normal 13px/19px Georgia, 'Times New Roman', 'Bitstream Charter', Times, serif; font-family: Times; font-size: medium; padding: 0.6em; margin: 0px;"&gt;
&lt;div id="_mcePaste"&gt;And we are back with yet another episode of A Buddhist Podcast! Thank you so much for continuing to listen and for all of your support!&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id="_mcePaste"&gt;On tonights show we have Chapter 1 from&amp;nbsp;&lt;a title="Link to Buddhism and the Science of Happiness in the Waterstones bookshop" href="http://www.waterstones.com/waterstonesweb/products/william+woollard/buddhism+and+the+science+of+happiness/8332435/" target="_blank"&gt;Buddhism and the Science of Happiness&lt;/a&gt;, a wonderful book written and read by our dear friend William Woollard.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id="_mcePaste"&gt;We have music from the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a title="Link to the Podsafe Music Network" href="http://www.mevio.com/music" target="_blank"&gt;Podsafe Music Network&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;at mevio.com and tonight we play&amp;nbsp;&lt;a title="Link to Melissa Forbes on ITunes" href="http://itunes.apple.com/gb/album/no-more-mondays/id125302952" target="_blank"&gt;Melissa Forbes&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;track, Blackheart Blues and the amazing&amp;nbsp;&lt;a title="Link to Bombskare on ITunes" href="http://itunes.apple.com/gb/album/fistful-of-dynamite/id303525718" target="_blank"&gt;Bombskare&lt;/a&gt;with their track Don't Give It All Away!&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id="_mcePaste"&gt;If you want a shout out on the show, let us know by clicking the link on the left hand side of our website "Shoutouts", or you can send us a note if you have the iPhone or Android app for A Buddhist Podcast. If you want to share a great experience of practicing this Buddhism and you would be happy for us to read it on the show, click the link for Experiences on the site, remember to really to try to use language that anyone can understand.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id="_mcePaste"&gt;Thank you so much for listening, have a wonderful week, take great care of yourself and everyone around you.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="50462548" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/A_Buddhist_Podcast_-_Buddhism_and_the_Science_of_Happiness_-_Chapter_1.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>52:33</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>And we are back with yet another episode of A Buddhist Podcast! Thank you so much for continuing to listen and for all of your support!
On tonights show we have Chapter 1 from&amp;nbsp;Buddhism and the Science of Happiness, a wonderful book written and...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>A Buddhist Podcast - Buddhism and the Science of Happiness - Introduction</title>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jan 2011 17:30:27 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">f8afffa1c41d57c94e0bd03f31a1889f</guid>
                    <link>http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/a-buddhist-podcast-buddhism-and-the-science-of-happiness-introduction</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/1460212"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;
&lt;div style="background-image: initial; background-attachment: initial; background-origin: initial; background-clip: initial; background-color: #ffffff; font: normal normal normal 13px/19px Georgia, 'Times New Roman', 'Bitstream Charter', Times, serif; font-family: Times; font-size: medium; padding: 0.6em; margin: 0px;"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Welcome to another episode of A Buddhist Podcast! Wow, twice in a month, this is a nice rhythm! Thank you for taking the time to download the show. Tonight we are proud to present our dear friend William Woollard, reading the introduction to his wonderful new book, Buddhism and the Science of Happiness. The printed book is also available on Amazon and elsewhere, and having heard and read quite a lot of it, I have to say it is a great book!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tonight's music comes from Mevio.com. We play Katie Herzig's track, "Sweeter than this" and the Cornish band, All the Fires, playing their track, The Anchor Song.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As usual, if you would like a shout out or to submit an experience, click the links on the right. You can also send them to us via the iPhone and Android apps for the show that are now available. Thank you so much again for all your support and encouragement. Have a wonderful, safe week and take care of yourselves and the people around you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="39022523" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/A_Buddhist_Podcast_-_Buddhism_and_the_Science_of_Happiness_-_Introduction.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>40:38</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Welcome to another episode of A Buddhist Podcast! Wow, twice in a month, this is a nice rhythm! Thank you for taking the time to download the show. Tonight we are proud to present our dear friend William Woollard, reading the introduction to his...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>A Buddhist Podcast - The Reluctant Buddhist - Chapter 16</title>
                    <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2011 19:28:17 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">bc9cd4fe5470d7afa8e66d84c7773679</guid>
                    <link>http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/-a-buddhist-podcast-the-reluctant-buddhist-chapter-16</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/1446177"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;!--StartFragment--&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;Happy New Year everyone! Welcome to another episode of A Buddhist Podcast. On tonights show we have the final chapter of the Reluctant Buddhist read by the author, the wonderful William Woollard. We also have news about his amazing new book, &amp;ldquo;Buddhism and the Science of Happiness&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;We read SGI President Ikeda&amp;rsquo;s New Year Message and of course the shoutouts!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;We play three tracks tonight, Last of the Superheros by American Heartbeat, Wonderwall by Melissa Rebronja and Let it Rain by Laura Clapp. Thank you to the artists for making this available on the Podsafe Music Network. The Podsafe Music Network have made so much of the music on the show possible and we really are grateful to them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;If you would like to for us to give you a shout out on the show, click the link on the left hand side of our website "Shoutouts". If you have a great experience of practicing this Buddhism that you would be happy for us to read on the show, you can click the link for Experiences on the site!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;Thank you to everyone for taking the time to listen to the show. Happy New Year!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!--EndFragment--&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="43565628" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/A_Buddhist_Podcast_-_The_Reluctant_Buddhist_-_Chapter_16.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>45:22</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Happy New Year everyone! Welcome to another episode of A Buddhist Podcast. On tonights show we have the final chapter of the Reluctant Buddhist read by the author, the wonderful William Woollard. We also have news about his amazing new book,...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>A Buddhist Podcast - The Reluctant Buddhist - Chapter 15</title>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 17 Oct 2010 17:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">555c5762e171dc12af06551a8af9b8d7</guid>
                    <link>http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/a-buddhist-podcast-the-reluctant-buddhist-chapter-15</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/1257723"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0.0px 0.0px 0.0px 0.0px; font: 12.0px Osaka;"&gt;Welcome back to another episode of A Buddhist Podcast. Tonight we the penultimate chapter from the wonderful William Woollard reading Chapter 15 of his popular book, The Reluctant Buddhist.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0.0px 0.0px 0.0px 0.0px; font: 12.0px Osaka;"&gt;Lots of shoutout tonight! We play two great tracks of music tonight. The first is Smile by the our friend Robin Lukas. The second is by Alison Crowe who sings This Little Bird. Our thanks to the&amp;nbsp; the Podsafe Music Network at musically.com.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0.0px 0.0px 0.0px 0.0px; font: 12.0px Osaka; min-height: 17.0px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0.0px 0.0px 0.0px 0.0px; font: 12.0px Osaka;"&gt;If you would like to for us to give you a shout out on the show, click the link on the left hand side of our website "Shoutouts". If you have a great experience of practicing this Buddhism that you would be happy for us to read on the show, you can click the link for Experiences on the site!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0.0px 0.0px 0.0px 0.0px; font: 12.0px Osaka;"&gt;Thank you to everyone for taking the time to listen to the show. Have a victorious week.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="53301206" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/A_Buddhist_Podcast_-_The_Reluctant_Buddhist_-_Chapter_15.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>55:31</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Welcome back to another episode of A Buddhist Podcast. Tonight we the penultimate chapter from the wonderful William Woollard reading Chapter 15 of his popular book, The Reluctant Buddhist.&amp;nbsp;
Lots of shoutout tonight! We play two great tracks of...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>A Buddhist Podcast - The Supremacy of the Law - Part 1</title>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 03 Oct 2010 00:24:06 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">ce9089fb613aa7a8364834a8524fcca5</guid>
                    <link>http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/a-buddhist-podcast-the-supremacy-of-the-law-part-1</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/1196188"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Welcome to tonights episode of A Buddhist Podcast, thank you for taking the time to download! Tonights lectures is based on President Ikeda's lecture on the first part of a letter written by Nichiren Daishonin to a lady called Nichimyo Shonin. The letter is called The Supremacy of the Law. Themes from this lecture include:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wir sind das Volk&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Be the change&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The heroine, Nichimyo&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No laws can change the human heart&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Practice Buddhism to become a great human being&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Lotus Sutra is the broadband of Buddhism&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If the Dragon Kings daughter can reveal Buddhahood - So Can We&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We cannot allow people to suffer because of the terrible leaders we have&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our courage ripples out to encourage others&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Help everyone we meet discover their greatness&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The music tonight is courtesy of the Podsafe Music Network at Musicalley.com. We play Planetary Woman by Eoghan Colgan and Inside of Me by the Ivy League.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once again, if you want a shout out on the show, write and let us know or click the link on the left hand side of our website "Shoutouts". If you have a great experience of practicing this Buddhism that you would be happy for us to read on the show, you can click the link for Experiences on the site!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you so much for listening, take care and have a fantastic week.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="50130591" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/A_Buddhist_Podcast_-_The_Supremacy_of_the_Law_-_Part_1.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>52:13</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Welcome to tonights episode of A Buddhist Podcast, thank you for taking the time to download! Tonights lectures is based on President Ikeda's lecture on the first part of a letter written by Nichiren Daishonin to a lady called Nichimyo Shonin. The...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>A Buddhist Podcast - Letter to the Brothers - August 2010</title>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 22 Aug 2010 17:05:39 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">0e9a071d82bdbd50fb3266123edb93dc</guid>
                    <link>http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/a_buddhist_podcast_letter_to_the_brothers_august_2010</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/1073790"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;
&lt;div style="color: #000000; font-family: Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif; font-size: 13px; background-image: initial; background-attachment: initial; background-origin: initial; background-clip: initial; background-color: #ffffff; margin: 8px;"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Welcome to another show! It has been a really long time, thank you for bearing with us. Jason has new work that requires a lot of hours and travel that we are still getting used to!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On tonights show we have a lecture on the letter that Nichiren Daishonin wrote to the Ikegami brothers in 1275, its called simply, &amp;ldquo;Letter to the Brothers&amp;rdquo;. Tonights lecture is based on President Ikeda&amp;rsquo;s lecture from SGI Newsletter 7832 and subjects include:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Buddhism is about overcoming negativity&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Walking the talk, the first three presidents of the Soka Gakkai&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Dad, the priest, the wives and the brothers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Faith is believing in peoples greatness&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We lose because of fear and influence&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We win because of wisdom and courage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Three obstacles and four devils&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Will power is not enough&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;United in purpose&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master your mind&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Change within creates change without&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We have wonderful experiences from Jay Osburn in Michigan (The artwork for this episode is of Charley) and Gerald White in Las Vegas in the US. We have shoutouts that really span the world and of course music. On tonights show we play&amp;nbsp;&lt;a title="Link to Nowisnow on ITunes" href="http://itunes.apple.com/gb/album/days-of-summer/id128862375?i=128862383"&gt;Days of Summer by Now is Now&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;and&amp;nbsp;&lt;a title="stavia on Itunes" href="http://itunes.apple.com/gb/album/lucky-day/id152418234?i=152418243"&gt;Lucky Day by Stavia&lt;/a&gt;, both courtesy of the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a title="Link to the Podsafe Music Network" href="http://www.musicalley.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Podsafe Music Network on musicalley.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We send you our very best for a truly wonderful week and thank you from the bottom of our hearts for all your support and encouragement!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="83069814" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/A_Buddhist_Podcast_-_Letter_to_the_Brothers_-_Aug_2010.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:26:31</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords>and,the,jason,devils,three,gerald,jay,to,brothers,international,obstacles,karen,president,white,buddhism,four,buddhist,buddha,jarrett,letter,soka,gakkai,nichiren,daishonin,daisaku,ikeda,daimoku,gosho,abuddhistpodcast,osburn,nowisnow,stavia</itunes:keywords>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Welcome to another show! It has been a really long time, thank you for bearing with us. Jason has new work that requires a lot of hours and travel that we are still getting used to!
On tonights show we have a lecture on the letter that Nichiren...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>A Buddhist Podcast - The Reluctant Buddhist - Chapter 14</title>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2010 14:43:48 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">cde1b335cfb52d4370834b3cb0853dbb</guid>
                    <link>http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/a_buddhist_podcast_the_reluctant_buddhist_chapter_14</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/898166"/>
                    <description>&lt;span style="color: rgb(0, 0, 0); font-family: Times; font-size: medium; line-height: 19px; "&gt;Welcome back to another episode of A Buddhist Podcast. Tonight we very fortunate to have&amp;nbsp;&lt;a title="Link to William Woollard on Wikipedia" href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/William_Woollard" mce_href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/William_Woollard" target="_blank"&gt;William Woollard&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;reading about the Buddhist view of eternal life in Chapter 14 of his popular book,&amp;nbsp;&lt;a title="Link to The Reluctant Buddhist website" href="http://www.thereluctantbuddhist.com/" mce_href="http://www.thereluctantbuddhist.com/" target="_blank"&gt;The Reluctant Buddhist&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div style="background-image: initial; background-attachment: initial; background-origin: initial; background-clip: initial; background-color: rgb(255, 255, 255); font: normal normal normal 13px/19px Georgia, 'Times New Roman', 'Bitstream Charter', Times, serif; padding-top: 0.6em; padding-right: 0.6em; padding-bottom: 0.6em; padding-left: 0.6em; margin-top: 0px; margin-right: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px; margin-left: 0px; color: rgb(0, 0, 0); font-family: Times; font-size: medium; "&gt;&lt;div id="_mcePaste"&gt;We have great experiences from Jane Moorhouse in France, Lance Fallin in Arizona and Eleanor Khartchenko in Italy. As usual we have some great music for you. The first two tracks we play are from the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a title="Link to the Podsafe Music Network at Mevio" href="http://www.mevio.com" mce_href="http://www.mevio.com" target="_blank"&gt;Podsafe Music Network&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;at&amp;nbsp;&lt;a title="Link to musicalley.com" href="http://www.musicalley.com" mce_href="http://www.musicalley.com" target="_blank"&gt;musically.com&lt;/a&gt;. We play&lt;a title="Links to Geoff Smiths website" href="http://thegeoffsmith.com/" mce_href="http://thegeoffsmith.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Geoff Smith (the creator of our theme music)&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;who performs is famous track,&amp;nbsp;&lt;a title="Link to Geoff Smith on ITunes" href="http://itunes.apple.com/gb/album/geoff-smith-tonewheels/id148121129" mce_href="http://itunes.apple.com/gb/album/geoff-smith-tonewheels/id148121129" target="_blank"&gt;Not on the radio&lt;/a&gt;. The second track is by the talented young Australian,&amp;nbsp;&lt;a title="Link to Lee Coulters website" href="http://leecoulter.com/" mce_href="http://leecoulter.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Lee Coulter&lt;/a&gt;, who performs She fell in love with the mirror. Finally we have a wonderful song written by Howard Jones and&amp;nbsp;&lt;a title="Link to Duncan Sheik on Wikipedia" href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Duncan_Sheik" mce_href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Duncan_Sheik" target="_blank"&gt;Dunkan Sheik&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;and performed by&amp;nbsp;&lt;a title="Link to Howard Jones website" href="http://howardjones.com/" mce_href="http://howardjones.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Howard Jones&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;on his Album,&amp;nbsp;&lt;a title="Link to Ordinary Heroes on ITunes" href="http://itunes.apple.com/gb/album/ordinary-heroes/id336943421" mce_href="http://itunes.apple.com/gb/album/ordinary-heroes/id336943421" target="_blank"&gt;Ordinary Heroes,&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;its called Someone You Need. Our sincere thanks to Howard Jones for the permission to play this track on the show.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div id="_mcePaste"&gt;If you would like to for us to give you a shout out on the show, click the link on the left hand side of our website "Shoutouts". If you have a great experience of practicing this Buddhism that you would be happy for us to read on the show, you can click the link for Experiences on the site!&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div id="_mcePaste"&gt;Thank you to everyone for taking the time to listen to the show. Have a truly amazing week.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="68971527" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/A_Buddhist_Podcast_-_The_Reluctant_Buddhist_-_Chapter_14.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:11:50</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords>the,william,jones,lee,geoff,smith,buddhism,howard,buddhist,buddha,coulter,soka,gakkai,sgi,woollard,reluctant,abuddhistpodcast</itunes:keywords>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Welcome back to another episode of A Buddhist Podcast. Tonight we very fortunate to have&amp;nbsp;William Woollard&amp;nbsp;reading about the Buddhist view of eternal life in Chapter 14 of his popular book,&amp;nbsp;The Reluctant Buddhist.We have great...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>A Buddhist Podcast - The Reluctant Buddhist - Chapter 13</title>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2010 12:57:30 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">12a4f2cfc859c3e0880317061158015c</guid>
                    <link>http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/a_buddhist_podcast_the_reluctant_buddhist_chapter_13</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/878181"/>
                    <description>We are back with another show! On tonights show we ahve the wonderful William Woollard reading Chapter 13 from his best selling book, The Reluctant Buddhist. We also have experiences from Claudia Blaszynzky in Sacramento and Robert 'Skip' Williams in Hong Kong.&amp;nbsp;&lt;div&gt;We play three tracks tonight! We have Danko Jones with First Date, Robin Lukas with Smile and Beth Thornley with Mr Lovely! We would like to thank Robin Lukas for letting us play Smile and also express our thanks to Musicalley.com for making the music of Danko Jones and Beth Thornley available for us to play.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We have shoutouts, truly from all over the world. Also tonight we include some of the unedited audio from the live video, "Behind the Scenes with A Buddhist Podcast". In the show tonight we make reference to Xavier Picks Peace exhibition and the forthcoming meeting of the SGI-UK Education Division meeting.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;On the site you will notice a new heading on the right, called shoutouts, click the link and send us your shoutout, this way we make sure we don't lose any of your precious names.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;If you have a question, an experience that you would like to share with us, get in touch, we love hearing from you.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Thank you so much for your support and encouragement, it always means so much to us. Have a wonderful week!&lt;/div&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="74141820" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/A_Buddhist_Podcast_-_The_Reluctant_Buddhist_-_Chapter_13.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:17:13</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords>podcast,the,william,jason,williams,a,jones,karen,skip,buddhism,robin,buddhist,buddha,beth,xavier,jarrett,pick,experiences,soka,gakkai,lukas,danko,daimoku,woollard,reluctant,thornley</itunes:keywords>
                    <itunes:subtitle>We are back with another show! On tonights show we ahve the wonderful William Woollard reading Chapter 13 from his best selling book, The Reluctant Buddhist. We also have experiences from Claudia Blaszynzky in Sacramento and Robert 'Skip' Williams in...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>A Buddhist Podcast - The Drum at the Gate of Thunder</title>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 16 May 2010 19:18:09 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">742e22a5cf9d88230095715c7b5004a4</guid>
                    <link>http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/a_buddhist_podcast_the_drum_at_the_gate_of_thunder</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/1807747"/>
                    <description>&lt;p style="margin: 0.0px 0.0px 0.0px 0.0px; font: 12.0px Helvetica"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0.0px"&gt;Welcome to another episode of A Buddhist Podcast! On tonights show we have a lecture on the letter that Nichiren Daishonin wrote to Sennichi-ama, its called The Drum at the Gate of Thunder. Subjects include:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0.0px 0.0px 0.0px 0.0px; font: 12.0px Helvetica; min-height: 14.0px"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0.0px"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0.0px 0.0px 0.0px 0.0px; font: 12.0px Helvetica"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0.0px"&gt;Hope spreads like fire&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0.0px 0.0px 0.0px 0.0px; font: 12.0px Helvetica; min-height: 14.0px"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0.0px"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0.0px 0.0px 0.0px 0.0px; font: 12.0px Helvetica"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0.0px"&gt;Sennichi-ama the sincere disciple&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0.0px 0.0px 0.0px 0.0px; font: 12.0px Helvetica; min-height: 14.0px"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0.0px"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0.0px 0.0px 0.0px 0.0px; font: 12.0px Helvetica"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0.0px"&gt;What does it mean to make an offering to the Lotus Sutra?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0.0px 0.0px 0.0px 0.0px; font: 12.0px Helvetica; min-height: 14.0px"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0.0px"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0.0px 0.0px 0.0px 0.0px; font: 12.0px Helvetica"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0.0px"&gt;Open the storehouse of your life&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0.0px 0.0px 0.0px 0.0px; font: 12.0px Helvetica; min-height: 14.0px"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0.0px"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0.0px 0.0px 0.0px 0.0px; font: 12.0px Helvetica"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0.0px"&gt;Blossom with hope&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0.0px 0.0px 0.0px 0.0px; font: 12.0px Helvetica; min-height: 14.0px"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0.0px"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0.0px 0.0px 0.0px 0.0px; font: 12.0px Helvetica"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0.0px"&gt;Even Devadatta attains Buddhahood&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0.0px 0.0px 0.0px 0.0px; font: 12.0px Helvetica; min-height: 14.0px"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0.0px"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0.0px 0.0px 0.0px 0.0px; font: 12.0px Helvetica"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0.0px"&gt;Women with the heart of a Lion King&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0.0px 0.0px 0.0px 0.0px; font: 12.0px Helvetica; min-height: 14.0px"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0.0px"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0.0px 0.0px 0.0px 0.0px; font: 12.0px Helvetica"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0.0px"&gt;Igniting the field of our unhappy karma&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0.0px 0.0px 0.0px 0.0px; font: 12.0px Helvetica; min-height: 14.0px"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0.0px"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0.0px 0.0px 0.0px 0.0px; font: 12.0px Helvetica"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0.0px"&gt;Did they die in the state of Buddhahood?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0.0px 0.0px 0.0px 0.0px; font: 12.0px Helvetica; min-height: 14.0px"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0.0px"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0.0px 0.0px 0.0px 0.0px; font: 12.0px Helvetica"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0.0px"&gt;The Drum at the Gate of Thunder&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0.0px 0.0px 0.0px 0.0px; font: 12.0px Helvetica; min-height: 14.0px"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0.0px"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0.0px 0.0px 0.0px 0.0px; font: 12.0px Helvetica"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0.0px"&gt;Merely seeing my mentor . . .&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0.0px 0.0px 0.0px 0.0px; font: 12.0px Helvetica; min-height: 14.0px"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0.0px"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0.0px 0.0px 0.0px 0.0px; font: 12.0px Helvetica"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0.0px"&gt;Thanks to the wonderful talent of the great Phil Campbell (follow him on twitter at @philcampbell) tonights show was streamed live on Bambuser and a recording of the unedited version of tonights show can be seen on our website.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0.0px 0.0px 0.0px 0.0px; font: 12.0px Helvetica; min-height: 14.0px"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0.0px"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0.0px 0.0px 0.0px 0.0px; font: 12.0px Helvetica"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0.0px"&gt;Shoutouts run out to our friends from across the globe!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0.0px 0.0px 0.0px 0.0px; font: 12.0px Helvetica; min-height: 14.0px"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0.0px"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0.0px 0.0px 0.0px 0.0px; font: 12.0px Helvetica"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0.0px"&gt;We play music from the very talented Jody Gnant, who sings her track, Great Day. We also play O'amanhecer (Dawn) by Paul Kouatchou, a beautiful song sung in Portuguese!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0.0px 0.0px 0.0px 0.0px; font: 12.0px Helvetica; min-height: 14.0px"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0.0px"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0.0px 0.0px 0.0px 0.0px; font: 12.0px Helvetica"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0.0px"&gt;From the bottom of our hearts, thank you so much for listening to the show tonight and for all your support. Have a truly amazing week.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0.0px 0.0px 0.0px 0.0px; font: 12.0px Helvetica; min-height: 14.0px"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0.0px"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0.0px 0.0px 0.0px 0.0px; font: 12.0px Helvetica; min-height: 14.0px"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing: 0.0px"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&amp;nbsp;</description>
                    <enclosure length="64030666" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/A_Buddhist_Podcast_-_The_Drum_at_the_Gate_of_Thunder.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:06:41</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords>the,of,jason,gate,drum,karen,buddhism,at,buddhist,buddha,thunder,jarrett,soka,gakkai,daisaku,ikeda,myo,sennichiama</itunes:keywords>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Welcome to another episode of A Buddhist Podcast! On tonights show we have a lecture on the letter that Nichiren Daishonin wrote to Sennichi-ama, its called The Drum at the Gate of Thunder. Subjects include:

Hope spreads like fire

Sennichi-ama the...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>A Buddhist Podcast - The Reluctant Buddhist Chapter 12</title>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 04 Apr 2010 09:35:42 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">56e27b17ccdad41b78ca53cbb209bbeb</guid>
                    <link>http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/_a_buddhist_podcast_the_reluctant_buddhist_chapter_12</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/1579831"/>
                    <description>&lt;!--StartFragment--&gt;

&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;Welcome to another episode of A Buddhist Podcast! On
tonights show we have the generous William Woollard who reads Chapter 12 from
his book, The Reluctant Buddhist! We also have Jason reading President Ikeda’s
editorial from 16th March 2010.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;On tonights show we have two great tracks to play for you.
The first is Tears in the Rain by The Palpitations. The second track comes from
&lt;a href="http://www.musicalley.com"&gt;Music Alley&lt;/a&gt; and is This Little Bird by Allison Crowe. Our thanks to The
Palpitations and Allison Crowe for making their music available to us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;We have the shoutouts as well and news that the podcast is
being listened to in 98 countries around the world!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;Thank you for your constant support and encouragement, we value
it so much. Have a fantastic week!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--EndFragment--&gt;


&amp;nbsp;</description>
                    <enclosure length="40991864" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/A_Buddhist_Podcast_-_The_Reluctant_Buddhist_-_Chapter_12.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>42:41</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords>podcast,william,jason,karen,buddhism,buddhist,buddha,study,jarrett,soka,gakkai,nichiren,daishonin,daisaku,ikeda,woollard,kosenrufu</itunes:keywords>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Welcome to another episode of A Buddhist Podcast! On
tonights show we have the generous William Woollard who reads Chapter 12 from
his book, The Reluctant Buddhist! We also have Jason reading President Ikeda’s
editorial from 16th March 2010.

On...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>A Buddhist Podcast - The one with Howard Hill</title>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 21 Mar 2010 22:19:31 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">6a2e7a7fd388566d12c6373c72577e5e</guid>
                    <link>http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/A_Buddhist_Podcast_-_The_One_with_Howard_Hill.mp3</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/738857"/>
                    <description>&lt;div&gt;We are back with another show! On tonights show we are very lucky to have a wonderful talk by Howard Hill from London in the UK!&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We also have music! We play Lonely Boy by Black Lab, Dharani by Robin Lukas and Goodbye Southern Skies by David McMillin.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We have an experience from Chris Yearley in Cyprus and the usual shoutouts!&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Thank you to everyone who encouraged and supported Jason during his recent trip to Austin and Sacramento. Your emails and support are a constant encouragement. Have a wonderful week!&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="76846680" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/A_Buddhist_Podcast_-_The_One_with_Howard_Hill.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:20:02</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords>black,jason,hill,david,karen,lab,buddhism,howard,robin,buddhist,jarrett,soka,gakkai,nichiren,daishonin,sgi,lukas,mcmillin</itunes:keywords>
                    <itunes:subtitle>We are back with another show! On tonights show we are very lucky to have a wonderful talk by Howard Hill from London in the UK!We also have music! We play Lonely Boy by Black Lab, Dharani by Robin Lukas and Goodbye Southern Skies by David McMillin.We...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>A Buddhist Podcast - The Reluctant Buddhist - Chapter 11</title>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2010 09:41:05 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">8683c15d3a57239b35e25b53d11fabac</guid>
                    <link>http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/A_Buddhist_Podcast_-_The_Reluctant_Buddhist_-_Chapter_11.mp3</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/1453758"/>
                    <description>&lt;span style="font-family: Times; font-size: medium; "&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: Georgia, 'Times New Roman', 'Bitstream Charter', Times, serif; font-size: 13px; line-height: 19px; "&gt;We have fought to create the space to bring you tonights show! On this show we have the gracious and kind&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/William_Woollard" mce_href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/William_Woollard"&gt;William Woollard&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;reading Chapter 11 from his book,&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://astore.amazon.co.uk/jasonjarrett-21/detail/1906210357" mce_href="http://astore.amazon.co.uk/jasonjarrett-21/detail/1906210357" title="Link to the The Reluctant Buddhist on Amazon" target="_blank"&gt;The Reluctant Buddhist&lt;/a&gt;. Its a very interesting chapter called, A Long and Healthy Life. The Reluctant Buddhist is selling extraordinarily well throughout the world and we understand is soon to be published in Spanish as well!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div style="background-image: initial; background-repeat: initial; background-attachment: initial; -webkit-background-clip: initial; -webkit-background-origin: initial; background-color: rgb(255, 255, 255); font: normal normal normal 13px/19px Georgia, 'Times New Roman', 'Bitstream Charter', Times, serif; padding-top: 0.6em; padding-right: 0.6em; padding-bottom: 0.6em; padding-left: 0.6em; margin-top: 0px; margin-right: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px; margin-left: 0px; background-position: initial initial; "&gt;&lt;p&gt;In addition, we an experience from Beth Bradley in Austin, Texas, USA. We have news about the forthcoming Iphone App for the show and the Ebooks of the lectures that will soon be available. We have shoutouts that cover the world, literally! We are also very pleased to have a poem called Sunflowers from the amazing Bob Kemp.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We have two tracks to play you tonight. The first is The World Is Yours by&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JTyLUCGbgiU" mce_href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JTyLUCGbgiU" title="Link to Stuart Powell on Youtube"&gt;Stuart Powell&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;and the second is a very catchy tune by&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://www.myspace.com/mattguitarboreham" mce_href="http://www.myspace.com/mattguitarboreham" title="Link to Matt Boreham on Myspace"&gt;Matt Boreham&lt;/a&gt;, its called Conversations! We would like to thank both of them for letting us play their music on the show.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jason is going to be at&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://www.sxsw.com/" mce_href="http://www.sxsw.com/" target="_blank"&gt;SXSW&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;in Austin Texas from the 10 - 16th March and if you are there he would love to meet you! On the 17th March Jason will be in Sacramento and would love the opportunity to meet with you there as well!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thank you for your support and encouragement, we do appreciate it so much. Have a fantastic week!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="52775398" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/A_Buddhist_Podcast_-_The_Reluctant_Buddhist_-_Chapter_11.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>54:58</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords>podcast,and,william,jason,corey,matt,life,a,long,bradley,karen,healthy,buddhism,bob,buddhist,buddha,stuart,beth,sxsw,jarrett,powell,kemp,soka,gakkai,nichiren,daishonin,sgi,gohonzon,daimoku,woollard,boreham,gosho,sunflowers</itunes:keywords>
                    <itunes:subtitle>We have fought to create the space to bring you tonights show! On this show we have the gracious and kind&amp;nbsp;William Woollard&amp;nbsp;reading Chapter 11 from his book,&amp;nbsp;The Reluctant Buddhist. Its a very interesting chapter called, A Long and...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>A Buddhist Podcast - The Reluctant Buddhist - Chapter 10</title>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jan 2010 15:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/index.php?post_id=568600#</guid>
                    <link>http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/a_buddhist_podcast_the_reluctant_buddhist_chapter_10</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/695236"/>
                    <description>Happy New Year Everyone!
On tonights show we have the stalwart William Woollard reading Chapter 10, 'The Challenge of Change' from his book, The Reluctant Buddhist.
Jason reads SGI President Ikeda's New Year Message and Karen reads two great experiences from young women in England and the United States. As usual we have shoutouts that cross the globe and some great music! Tonight we play Harley Loudon's track, "Will You Listen" on the PMN. Also on the PMN we play Stingrays great track, '143'. Not on the PMN, but recorded in our kitchen we also play a new track called, 'Rocks for Gold' by the one and only Jimmy Golding.
There is a competition, if you have one of our new decals, you can take a photograph of where you have put it and post it on Flickr.com or elsewhere and send the link and your mail address and size to us on the show. The image we like best, wins a TShirt!
Jason is going to be in Austin, Texas for SXSW, if you are there and want to meet up then send us an email.
Thank you all for your fantastic support and please take great care of yourselves wherever you are. Have a wonderful week.</description>
                    <enclosure length="62974146" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/A_Buddhist_Podcast_-_The_Reluctant_Buddhist_-_Chapter_10.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:05:35</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Happy New Year Everyone!
On tonights show we have the stalwart William Woollard reading Chapter 10, 'The Challenge of Change' from his book, The Reluctant Buddhist.
Jason reads SGI President Ikeda's New Year Message and Karen reads two great...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>A Buddhist Podcast - Letter from Sado - Part 1</title>
                    <pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2009 00:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/index.php?post_id=562980#</guid>
                    <link>http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/a_buddhist_podcast_letter_from_sado_part_1</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/695235"/>
                    <description>A very merry christmas to you! This last weekend we recorded tonights lecture in the kitchen of the amazing Jackie Evans from Gower and Swansea West District in West Wales. We had a wonderful welcome and met some great people! On our return we finished the show and are delighted to bring you tonight, a lecture on Nichiren Daishonin's writing, Letter from Sado.
The lecture is quite long and was recorded very late at night, so you might want to listen to it in parts! Subjects include:

Time is the biggest contribution we can make

I solemnly swear that I want to do good

Temples were an investment

The loss of each individual life matters

Clinging on to life

An ungrudging spirit

Use problems to become happy

Earnest resolve

Refuting mistaken teachings

Doing the right thing

The heart of a lion king

We play two tracks from the Podsafe Music Network, Panacea by Bill and Merry Christmas Angel by the wonderful Vittoria Conn.
Thank you so much for your continued support of the show, we really are very grateful.
Have a truly wonderful new year!</description>
                    <enclosure length="67540942" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/A_Buddhist_Podcast_-_Letter_from_Sado_-_Part_1.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:10:21</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>A very merry christmas to you! This last weekend we recorded tonights lecture in the kitchen of the amazing Jackie Evans from Gower and Swansea West District in West Wales. We had a wonderful welcome and met some great people! On our return we...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>A Buddhist Podcast - The Reluctant Buddhist - Chapter 9</title>
                    <pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2009 22:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/index.php?post_id=559050#</guid>
                    <link>http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/a_buddhist_podcast_the_reluctant_buddhist_chapter_9</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/695234"/>
                    <description>We are back with another show! Karen has gone to visit her parents in Switzerland, so our teenage daughter, Florence is standing in for her on tonights show. On this show we have the wonderful William Woollard talking about the oneness of self and environment from Chapter 9 of his excellent book, The Reluctant Buddhist. 
We have music from Vittoria Conn who sings Where Would You Be, which is now available on ITunes! We also have the very talented Harley Loudon from London who sings a song dedicated to her daughter Ella and the Future Group of the UK, its called Teenagers!
We will have another episode coming out before Christmas, so keep your eyes peeled for it!
If you have a question, an experience or a shoutout that you would like to share with us, get in touch, we love hearing from you.
Thank you for all your birthday wishes and constant support, it means alot to all of us. Have a wonderful week!</description>
                    <enclosure length="45004818" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/A_Buddhist_Podcast_-_The_Reluctant_Buddhist_-_Chapter_9.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>46:52</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>We are back with another show! Karen has gone to visit her parents in Switzerland, so our teenage daughter, Florence is standing in for her on tonights show. On this show we have the wonderful William Woollard talking about the oneness of self and...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>A Buddhist Podcast - Pete Morris and the Gohonzon</title>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 15 Nov 2009 20:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/index.php?post_id=549480#</guid>
                    <link>http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/a_buddhist_podcast_pete_morris_and_the_gohonzon</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/695233"/>
                    <description>Welcome to another episode of A Buddhist Podcast. On tonights show we have a special guest, the wonderful Peter Morris! Peter talks about a fundamental aspect of Nichiren Daishonin's Buddhism, the Gohonzon.
Karen reads an amazing experience from the lovely Erica Holding who lives in California!
We have great music as well! Tonight we have Howard Jones playing Love Never Wasted from his new album Ordinary Heroes. From the Podsafe Music Network we have Bobby Gentry singing Goldie Hawn. We also have, by special permission from the Lovespirals, their brand new track called Shine from their new album which drops this week, Future Past. You can get copies of the album signed by Ryan and Anji from their website and a free digital download.
Thank you so much for listening to the show and for your support, we never take it for granted and really do appreciate it.
Have a truly wonderful week!</description>
                    <enclosure length="76873407" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/A_Buddhist_Podcast_-_Pete_Morris_and_the_Gohonzon.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:20:04</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Welcome to another episode of A Buddhist Podcast. On tonights show we have a special guest, the wonderful Peter Morris! Peter talks about a fundamental aspect of Nichiren Daishonin's Buddhism, the Gohonzon.
Karen reads an amazing experience from the...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>A Buddhist Podcast - The Reluctant Buddhist - Chapter 8</title>
                    <pubDate>Sat, 31 Oct 2009 12:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/index.php?post_id=543867#</guid>
                    <link>http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/a_buddhist_podcast_the_reluctant_buddhist_chapter_8</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/695232"/>
                    <description>Welcome to another show! Tonight we have William Woollard reading Chapter 8 from his fantastic book, The Reluctant Buddhist.Whilst Jason was in Trets recently he was able to record an experience by the lovely Mary Mulligan from Brighton in the UK, who talks about how she began to practice. We have a beautiful poem from the great Bob Kemp and shoutouts that as usual criss cross the globe!Tonight we have music from the very talented Tracy Lyons who has a new track, Don't You Know on the Podsafe Music Network. We also play the one and only Cat Malojian, we can't help it, we love them and they play Peddigoe.We have some great new material lined up in the next few weeks and can't wait to share it with you!If you have a question, an experience or a shoutout that you would like to share with us, get in touch, we love hearing from you.We know people are still after our t-shirts and you can find them at http://www.pressoffers.co.uk/abuddhistpodcast2 our thanks to Polly and Helen of Pressoffers for their help with this.Thank you so much for your support and encouragement, it means so much to us. Have a fantastic week!
Welcome to another show! Tonight we have William Woollard reading Chapter 8 from his fantastic book, The Reluctant Buddhist.

Whilst Jason was in Trets recently he was able to record an experience by the lovely Mary Mulligan from Brighton in the UK, who talks about how she began to practice. We have a beautiful poem from the great Bob Kemp and shoutouts that as usual criss cross the globe!

Tonight we have music from the very talented Tracy Lyons who has a new track, Don't You Know on the Podsafe Music Network. We also play the one and only Cat Malojian, we can't help it, we love them and they play Peddigoe.

We have some great new material lined up in the next few weeks and can't wait to share it with you!

If you have a question, an experience or a shoutout that you would like to share with us, get in touch, we love hearing from you.

We know people are still after our t-shirts and you can find them at http://www.pressoffers.co.uk/abuddhistpodcast2 our thanks to Polly and Helen of Pressoffers for their help with this.

Thank you so much for your support and encouragement, it means so much to us. Have a fantastic week!</description>
                    <enclosure length="54266826" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/A_Buddhist_Podcast_-_The_Reluctant_Buddhist_-_Chapter_8.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>56:31</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Welcome to another show! Tonight we have William Woollard reading Chapter 8 from his fantastic book, The Reluctant Buddhist.Whilst Jason was in Trets recently he was able to record an experience by the lovely Mary Mulligan from Brighton in the UK, who...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>A Buddhist Podcast - Letter to Jakunichi-Bo</title>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 18 Oct 2009 15:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/index.php?post_id=538923#</guid>
                    <link>http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/a_buddhist_podcast_letter_to_jakunichi_bo</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/695231"/>
                    <description>Welcome to another episode of A Buddhist Podcast! Tonight we have a lecture from Jason based on a letter written by Nichiren Daishonin, called Letter to Jakunichi-Bo. Subjects include:
What does it mean to practice Buddhism correctly?
One to one support
The power of appreciation
What is the purpose of life?
Practice for oneself and others
Nam-myoho-renge-kyo embodies the four paramitas
What is fundamental darkness?
Illuminating the darkness of bullying
Nichiren, Sun Lotus
Leave nothing on the pitch
Being known as a votary of the Lotus Sutra
Noble envoys of Nichiren Daishonin
Tonight we play three tracks! Thanks to PW Fenton, we have Lea Gilmore singing Ride My Blues Away. From the Podsafe Music Network we have the Lovespirals singing This Truth and Great Big Sea singing Beat the Drum.
We have a correction we make and a reading of the wonderful poem by Christian Larson called The Optimists Creed.
We have so many shoutouts tonight from Amsterdam to Singapore, from London to New York and from Mexico to New Delhi! Its a packed show and we hope you enjoy it! Thank you for listening, have a wonderful week!</description>
                    <enclosure length="73048826" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/ABP_-_Letter_to_Jakunichi-B.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:16:05</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Welcome to another episode of A Buddhist Podcast! Tonight we have a lecture from Jason based on a letter written by Nichiren Daishonin, called Letter to Jakunichi-Bo. Subjects include:
What does it mean to practice Buddhism correctly?
One to one...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>A Buddhist Podcast - The Reluctant Buddhist - Chapter 7</title>
                    <pubDate>Sat, 26 Sep 2009 22:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/index.php?post_id=530621#</guid>
                    <link>http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/a_buddhist_podcast_the_reluctant_buddhist_chapter_7</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/695230"/>
                    <description>Hello Everyone!
Tonight we are very glad to bring you William Woollard reading Chapter 7 from his book, The Reluctant Buddhist. The chapter is all about Karma, and its a very interesting listen.
As usual we have global shout outs as well as a beautiful poem from Kim Seagrave in Australia. We play "Love is not Wasted" from the imminent Howard Jones album, Ordinary Heroes which debuts on November 3rd this year.
We also play one of our favourite bands, they are Cat Malojian from Northern Ireland, a truly great band. They sing Pettigoe!
If you have wondering about our tshirts, you can get them now at http://www.pressoffers.co.uk/abuddhistpodcast2 our thanks to Polly and Helen of Pressoffers for their help with this. We hope very soon to add some new photos to the shop and the new blue colour!

Thank you so much for your support and encouragement. Wherever you are have a wonderful week!</description>
                    <enclosure length="47251656" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/ABPTRBC7t2.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>49:13</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Hello Everyone!
Tonight we are very glad to bring you William Woollard reading Chapter 7 from his book, The Reluctant Buddhist. The chapter is all about Karma, and its a very interesting listen.
As usual we have global shout outs as well as a...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>A Buddhist Podcast - The Essentials for Attaining Buddhahood - Revisite</title>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 07 Sep 2009 13:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/index.php?post_id=523527#</guid>
                    <link>http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/a_buddhist_podcast_the_essentials_for_attaining_buddhahood_revisite</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/695229"/>
                    <description>Welcome to another episode of A Buddhist Podcast! On tonights show we have a lecture on the letter that Nichiren Daishonin wrote to Soya Kyoshin, its called The Essentials for Attaining Buddhahood. Subjects include:

Who was Soya Kyoshin?
Essentials are not Optional
Bodhisattva Superior Practices and the Latter day of the Law
Reality and wisdom
Don't bend the teachings to suit your karma
Misguided priests versus correct teacher
Challenging wrong doing
Standing firm with a teenage daughter
Bridging the gap between people and Buddhism
My mentor
And of course we have the shoutouts and also . . . we also have three brand new songs.

I think, we may be the first podcast to debut two new tracks by Howard Jones. "Soon you'll go" and "Love never wasted" are from Howard's new album, Ordinary Heroes, which is being released on November 3rd. For more information take a look at his website here. Thank you Howard for letting us play these tracks

We also debut a wonderful new song from Vittoria Conn, it's called "Where would you be" which will be appearing very soon! As soon as we have a location on ITunes or elsewhere we will post the link here.

If you are looking for the tshirts you can get them from our tshirt shop which is generously powered by the wonderfulPressoffers.co.uk. Thank you so much for listening tonight, have a fantastic week!</description>
                    <enclosure length="60226396" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/A_Buddhist_Podcast_-_The_Essentials_for_Attaining_Buddhahood_-_Revisited.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:02:44</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Welcome to another episode of A Buddhist Podcast! On tonights show we have a lecture on the letter that Nichiren Daishonin wrote to Soya Kyoshin, its called The Essentials for Attaining Buddhahood. Subjects include:

Who was Soya...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>A Buddhist Podcast - The Reluctant Buddhist - The Experiences Part 1</title>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2009 09:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/index.php?post_id=517969#</guid>
                    <link>http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/a_buddhist_podcast_the_reluctant_buddhist_the_experiences_part_1</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/695228"/>
                    <description>For those of you who are familiar with William Woollards excellent book, The Reluctant Buddhist, and have been listening along on the podcast, you will have noticed something. The experiences from Chapters 5 and 6 were missing. This is because William really wanted to have someone else read them, and that someone tonight is the wonderfully warm and loving person that is his wife, Sarah.

So reading The Story of Joanna from Chapter 6 and The Story of Sally from Chapter 5 of The Reluctant Buddhist is Sarah Woollard.

Then we have music from Heather Sullivan. She sings Stronger from the Podsafe Music Network.

We find out what happened to Jason this month, we have shout outs and we read a letter from an SGI member, Frank Amatefe in Ghana, Africa.

We finish with another track from the Podsafe Music Network by Angelique Kidjo called Gimme Shelter featuring Joss Stone.

We have some great shows lined up for you and are so excited about all the different developments that are happening. Look at for a new look to the website that is coming soon and also for a new colour of our t-shirts, Stone Blue! If you are looking for the tshirts you can get them from http://www.pressoffers.co.uk/abuddhistpodcast2 

Thank you so much for your constant support and encouragement. Have a truly wonderful week!</description>
                    <enclosure length="51194930" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/A_Buddhist_Podcast_-_The_Reluctant_Buddhist_-_The_Experiences_Part_1.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>53:19</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>For those of you who are familiar with William Woollards excellent book, The Reluctant Buddhist, and have been listening along on the podcast, you will have noticed something. The experiences from Chapters 5 and 6 were missing. This is because William...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>A Buddhist Podcast - SGI-UK - A Spirit of Study</title>
                    <pubDate>Fri, 07 Aug 2009 21:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/index.php?post_id=512725#</guid>
                    <link>http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/a_buddhist_podcast_sgi_uk_a_spirit_of_study</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/695227"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;We have been working on tonights show for a long time. SGI-UK asked
us to help them put a show together about their view of the spirit of
study within SGI-UK.&lt;br/&gt;
Subjects include:&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;A brief explanation about Nichiren Daishonin's Buddhism&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;An explanation about SGI-UK's Study program&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A dialogue on going through the study program&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experiences from new members and old about taking the study exam.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finally we have some shoutouts and some great music from the one and
only Cat Malojian. On tonights show we play Made in America from Cat
Malojians new album, &lt;a href="http://itunes.apple.com/WebObjects/MZStore.woa/wa/viewAlbum?id=324559642&amp;s=143444" mce_href="http://itunes.apple.com/WebObjects/MZStore.woa/wa/viewAlbum?id=324559642&amp;s=143444" title="Link to Cat Malojians new album on Itunes" target="_blank"&gt;The Dawn Chorus&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br/&gt;
Thank you to everyone who made tonights show possible including
everyone who chanted for Jason to get well enough to leave hospital.
Both Karen and I are sincerely grateful! Have a truly fantastic week!&lt;br mce_bogus="1"/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="76434147" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/A_Buddhist_Podcast_-_SGI-UK_A_Spirit_of_Study.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:19:37</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>We have been working on tonights show for a long time. SGI-UK asked
us to help them put a show together about their view of the spirit of
study within SGI-UK.
Subjects include:


A brief explanation about Nichiren Daishonin's BuddhismAn...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>A Buddhist Podcast - On Repaying Debts of Gratitude</title>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jul 2009 21:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/index.php?post_id=505202#</guid>
                    <link>http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/a_buddhist_podcast_on_repaying_debts_of_gratitude</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/695226"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to another show, tonights show is a lecture on the writing
of Nichiren Daishonin called On Repaying Debts of Gratitude. Some of
the points include:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;What is debt of gratitude anyway?&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;28th April 1253, remember that speech?&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A lifetime of struggle&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ssshhh! the Three Great Secret Laws&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Without sparing our voice&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Depth of teaching and depth of struggle&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Drove this teaching to hell and back&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;How China get called China?&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Putting people first&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Three Virtues&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Use each struggle as a means to become happier&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Songs for this show come from Musicalley.com, part of &lt;a target="_blank" mce_href="http://uk.mevio.com/" href="http://uk.mevio.com/" title="Link to Mevio"&gt;Mevio&lt;/a&gt; the new name for Podshow! We play &lt;a target="_blank" mce_href="http://itunes.apple.com/WebObjects/MZStore.woa/wa/viewAlbum?id=192533730&amp;s=143444" href="http://itunes.apple.com/WebObjects/MZStore.woa/wa/viewAlbum?id=192533730&amp;s=143444" title="link to Jimmy Golding on ITunes"&gt;Rocket to the Moon&lt;/a&gt; by &lt;a target="_blank" mce_href="http://www.jimmgolding.com" href="http://www.jimmgolding.com/" title="link to Jimmy Golding's website"&gt;Jimmy Golding&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a target="_blank" mce_href="http://itunes.apple.com/WebObjects/MZStore.woa/wa/viewAlbum?id=260390703&amp;s=143444" href="http://itunes.apple.com/WebObjects/MZStore.woa/wa/viewAlbum?id=260390703&amp;s=143444" title="Link to Black Lab on Itunes"&gt;Mine Again&lt;/a&gt; by Black Lab.&lt;br/&gt;
Thank you so much from the bottom of our hearts for listening, for
encouraging and for supporting us in this adventure. Have a wonderful
week.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="59561971" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/A_Buddhist_Podcast_-_On_Repaying_Debts_of_Gratitude.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:02:02</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Welcome to another show, tonights show is a lecture on the writing
of Nichiren Daishonin called On Repaying Debts of Gratitude. Some of
the points include:

What is debt of gratitude anyway?28th April 1253, remember that speech?A lifetime of...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>A Buddhist Podcast - The Reluctant Buddhist - Chapter 6</title>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2009 21:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/index.php?post_id=499632#</guid>
                    <link>http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/a_buddhist_podcast_the_reluctant_buddhist_chapter_6</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/695225"/>
                    <description>Well tonight we have truly great explanation of the Buddhist concept known as the Ten Worlds as William Woollard reads Chapter 6 from The Reluctant Buddhist!

We have music from the Podsafe Music Network tonight with Lee Coulter playing  Booty Voodoo and Rocky Votolato with White Daisy Passing.

More shoutouts from across the globe and chipper conversation from Jason and Karen who, at home in England are enjoying the wonderful summer! 

Thank you for listening and thank you so much for your encouragement. Have a fantastic week!</description>
                    <enclosure length="45666338" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/A_Buddhist_Podcast_-_The_Reluctant_Buddhist_-_Chapter_6.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>47:34</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Well tonight we have truly great explanation of the Buddhist concept known as the Ten Worlds as William Woollard reads Chapter 6 from The Reluctant Buddhist!

We have music from the Podsafe Music Network tonight with Lee Coulter playing  Booty...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>A Buddhist Podcast - Hell is the Land of Tranquil Light</title>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jun 2009 20:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/index.php?post_id=494251#</guid>
                    <link>http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/a_buddhist_podcast_hell_is_the_land_of_tranquil_light</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/695224"/>
                    <description>We can hardly believe that it is almost exactly half way through 2009! Wow! Tonight we bring you a lecture on the letter written by Nichiren Daishonin called, Hell is the Land of Tranquil Light. Some of the subject teasers for tonight include:
We need to reveal Buddhahood to overcome our karma
Lets try and remember the names of our mothers
The icy wind of thoughtless encouragement
The ten worlds exist in life and death
Giving 150% . . .in small bursts
Are you in a prison of someone elses making?
Changing circumstances won't change karma
Attaining Buddhahood just as you are
It is human to feel grief when someone dies
Gohonzon is the baseline of Buddhahood
Chant first, shout later.

We have music for you from the Podsafe Music Network. First up is Carbon Leaf with A Life Less Ordinary. We close the show with Shines Right Through Me by the amazing Great Big Sea! The links we have for the tracks will take you through to where you can buy them on iTunes and the links for the names will take you through to their own website.

Karen and I are busy posting off orders for our new Tshirts! If you have yours and you send us a photograph, we will consider putting it on the artwork for the show, so send them in to jason(at)thejarretts.com!
Thankyou for your comments and encouragement. Thank you for all the support you give us, we really do feel and appreciate it. Please take great care and have the most amazing and wonderful week!</description>
                    <enclosure length="52409643" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/A_Buddhist_Podcast_-_Hell_is_the_Land_of_Tranquil_Light.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>54:35</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>We can hardly believe that it is almost exactly half way through 2009! Wow! Tonight we bring you a lecture on the letter written by Nichiren Daishonin called, Hell is the Land of Tranquil Light. Some of the subject teasers for tonight include:
We...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>A Buddhist Podcast - The Reluctant Buddhist - Chapter 5</title>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2009 11:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/index.php?post_id=488734#</guid>
                    <link>http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/A_Buddhist_Podcast_-_The_Reluctant_Buddhist_-_Chapter_5.mp3</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/695222"/>
                    <description>We are back on schedule tonight with the wonderful William Woollard reading Chapter 5, "What do we mean by happiness?", from his book The Reluctant Buddhist which is now being reprinted and translated into more languages!

We have shoutouts and some great music. Tonight we play Rocket to the Moon by the wonderful Jimmy Golding and Day by Now is Now. Both artists are on the Podsafe Music Network.

We have some great new material to bring to you and we welcome your feedback, reviews, experiences and contributions. For those people who have been asking about a tshirt, you can get them now at http://www.pressoffers.co.uk/abuddhistpodcast2 our thanks to Polly and Helen of Pressoffers for their help with this.

Thank you for your support and encouragement, we do appreciate it so much. Have a fantastic week!</description>
                    <enclosure length="42514267" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/A_Buddhist_Podcast_-_The_Reluctant_Buddhist_-_Chapter_5.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>44:17</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>We are back on schedule tonight with the wonderful William Woollard reading Chapter 5, "What do we mean by happiness?", from his book The Reluctant Buddhist which is now being reprinted and translated into more languages!

We have shoutouts and some...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>A Buddhist Podcast - Letter to Misawa</title>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 24 May 2009 11:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/index.php?post_id=483288#</guid>
                    <link>http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/A_Buddhist_Podcast_-_Letter_to_Misawa.mp3</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/695220"/>
                    <description>Tonight we have a lecture on "Letter to Misawa". This lectures is about many things, but one thing is for sure it does address the three obstacles and four devils. Perhaps because it does so it might explain why it has taken 5 months to write 3 times, why cables went missing right before we started the show and a myriad of others obstacles emerged! Some of tonights themes include:


Practicing correctly involves transforming the negativity in the world around you
Three obstacles and four devils
What is the devil king of the 6th heaven anyway?
Nikko takes it to the man
Self reliant faith
The Gohonzon certifies that Buddhahood exists
Some experience of overcoming obstacles
What do you want to break through?
Why is the Soka Gakkai different?

Its a full show and along with the shout outs we play three tracks tonight from the Podsafe Music Network (http://www.mevio.com)
We play Code Monkey by Jonathan Coulton (http://music.podshow.com/music/listeners/artistdetails.php?BandHash=97007092b961d7e9a7d77c2614ee0086) who sings Code Monkey http://www.jonathancoulton.com/ 
http://itunes.apple.com/WebObjects/MZStore.woa/wa/viewAlbum?id=211036259&amp;s=143444

And we play two tracks from Adrina Thorpe (http://music.podshow.com/music/listeners/artistdetails.php?BandHash=a892daf89e5efee9bd4705bbf8c092fc) who sings  Coming Home and Fly Fly Fly
She is also on iTunes!
http://itunes.apple.com/WebObjects/MZStore.woa/wa/viewAlbum?id=64954602&amp;s=143444

In response to the many requests for TShirts we are now able to offer them for almost half the previous price and twice the quality! Thanks Polly Earnest and Helen Steyner of PressOffers.com who have created the shop for us!

Thank you for all your support, encouragement, comments and input! It is such great good fortune to be able to do this podcast.</description>
                    <enclosure length="76049791" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/A_Buddhist_Podcast_-_Letter_to_Misawa.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:19:13</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Tonight we have a lecture on "Letter to Misawa". This lectures is about many things, but one thing is for sure it does address the three obstacles and four devils. Perhaps because it does so it might explain why it has taken 5 months to write 3 times,...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>A Buddhist Podcast - The Reluctant Buddhist - Chapter 4</title>
                    <pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2009 20:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/index.php?post_id=475714#</guid>
                    <link>http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/A_Buddhist_Podcast_-_The_Reluctant_Buddhist_-_Chapter_4.mp3</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/695218"/>
                    <description>On tonights show, William Woollard reads Chapter 4 from his wonderful book, The Reluctant Buddhist. The chapter is called A Question of Faith and its a great listen.

Also on tonight we have an experience from Estelle Jackson, a member of the Students Division in SGI-UK. 

As usual we have shoutouts that criss cross the world and music from the Podsafe Music Network. We play Vittoria Conn's track called Mirror and a podcasting anthem, Not On The Radio by Geoff Smith.

The show tonight is absolutely packed! We know we have been sometime in getting you a show and so tonights episode lasts for 78 minutes or so, so it will fit on a CD if you want to burn it for a friend!

We have some more shows ready for you and are looking forward to putting them out in the next few weeks! Thank you for your support and encouragement, we do appreciate it so much. Have a wonderful week!</description>
                    <enclosure length="75470270" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/A_Buddhist_Podcast_-_The_Reluctant_Buddhist_-_Chapter_4.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:18:36</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>On tonights show, William Woollard reads Chapter 4 from his wonderful book, The Reluctant Buddhist. The chapter is called A Question of Faith and its a great listen.

Also on tonight we have an experience from Estelle Jackson, a member of the...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>A Buddhist Podcast - Life Span Chapter - Part 2 - Jigage</title>
                    <pubDate>Sat, 28 Mar 2009 14:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/index.php?post_id=448301#</guid>
                    <link>http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/a_buddhist_podcast_life_span_chapter_part_2_jigage</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/695217"/>
                    <description>Welcome to another episode of A Buddhist Podcast. Tonight we continue with our new series of lectures on the Jigage portion of Gongyo by looking at the meaning of the words, Nyorai Juryo hon dai juroku! Haven't you ever wondered what it means? This poem of life is so amazing. Some of the headings include:
What does gongyo mean?
Lotus Sutra for the Latter Day of the Law
Wisdom illuminates ignorance
Nichiren Daishonin, the true Buddha
Causing the sun of hope to dawn
Shelley on Dante
A practice to perpetuate
Every character is a shining buddha
Living the poem of life
You can't use force to create change
Our victories are your victories
Walt Whitman, Song of Myself
Seek out your true self!
Live like the waterfall
Once again the music for tonights show is a blatant expression of how much we love the music of Cat Malojian! We play Pettigoe and Life Rolls On, which you can find on iTunes!
Thank you for all the comments, emails and messages of support, we truly appreciate every single last one of them. One last point, our love goes out to Dash and Donna, we are so happy to know that Donna is out of hospital and on the mend!
Have a wonderful week.</description>
                    <enclosure length="68370712" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/A_Buddhist_Podcast_-_Lifespan_Chapter_-_Part_Two.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:11:13</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Welcome to another episode of A Buddhist Podcast. Tonight we continue with our new series of lectures on the Jigage portion of Gongyo by looking at the meaning of the words, Nyorai Juryo hon dai juroku! Haven't you ever wondered what it means? This...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>A Buddhist Podcast - Introduction to the Lifespan Chapter</title>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2009 23:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/index.php?post_id=431221#</guid>
                    <link>http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/a_buddhist_podcast_introduction_to_the_lifespan_chapter</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/695216"/>
                    <description>Finally, we are back! We are so pleased to do this show tonight, so pleased to be able to share this with you! After 3 years we have decided to finish our lecture series on Gongyo! Tonights lecture is an introduction to the Juryo Chapter, the 16th Chapter of the Lotus Sutra, known as the Lifespan Chapter! Some of the headings include:
Traveller
Where do we come from and where are we going?
How can life be eternal if we all die?
Overview of the Lotus Sutra
Eternity is an aspect of life
Do you ride the shopping trolley of life?
Mentor and Disciple
Nichiren the human being
White knuckle daimoku
Our lives are one with the universe
We are the Bodhisattvas of the Earth
Striving for self worth
Unprecedented Challenge
Music for tonights show comes from the great talent of Cat Malojian! These two lads from Northern Ireland make great music, and we love it. Tonight they play Who Knows? and Goodnight. If you like their music, pop over to ITunes and buy some!
Thank you for all your messages of support and encouragement, we hope you enjoy tonights show!</description>
                    <enclosure length="59174787" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/A_Buddhist_Podcast_-_Introduction_to_the_Lifespan_Chapter.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:01:38</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Finally, we are back! We are so pleased to do this show tonight, so pleased to be able to share this with you! After 3 years we have decided to finish our lecture series on Gongyo! Tonights lecture is an introduction to the Juryo Chapter, the 16th...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>A Buddhist Podcast - On The Buddha's Prophecy</title>
                    <pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2008 22:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/index.php?post_id=416304#</guid>
                    <link>http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/a_buddhist_podcast_on_the_buddha_s_prophecy</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/695215"/>
                    <description>Another full show!

Tonights lecture is on Nichiren Daishonin's teaching called, On The Buddha's Prophecy. The lecture is about the purpose of Buddhist practice. Some of the headings include:

A Leap Month!
Life at Ichinosawa
Bodhisattva Medicine King
Former, Middle and Latter Day of the Law
Doing time in the "When I" Prison
The teaching, the teacher and the mission
What did the priests do for 700 years?
The Soka Gakkai fullfills the Buddha's Prophecy
Its time to create happiness
We have President Ikeda's New Year's message for 2009, read by Ken George. There are shoutouts and music from Ioda Promonet including "Balance" by Sara Tavares which you can buy here at iTunes Music Store

The second track we play tonight is by Cohen which is also availabe here!Gold Is Where You Find It (mp3)

We are proud members of the Ioda Alliance!

Thankyou for all your support and encouragement! Have a fantastic week.</description>
                    <enclosure length="75207269" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/A_Buddhist_Podcast_-_On_The_Buddhas_Prophecy.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:18:20</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Another full show!

Tonights lecture is on Nichiren Daishonin's teaching called, On The Buddha's Prophecy. The lecture is about the purpose of Buddhist practice. Some of the headings include:

A Leap Month!
Life at Ichinosawa
Bodhisattva...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>A Buddhist Podcast - Action for Happiness</title>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2008 14:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/index.php?post_id=408198#</guid>
                    <link>http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/a_buddhist_podcast_action_for_happiness</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/695214"/>
                    <description>Tonights show is so full!

Tonights lectures is based on guidance that President Ikeda gave earlier this year about the four points for victory. The four points are Prayer, Action, Unity and the Oneness of Mentor and Disciple. This lecture is about the second theme, Action! The main points of the lecture include:

Developing our own individual attitude to faith
Taking responsibility for the happiness of where we live
The roar of the tiger of death
Take the initiative and make new friends
We reveal buddhahood in our behaviour
The old man in the park
What is the Buddha's great teaching?
Living with my mentor
Three powerful enemies
If not you then who?
We have a poem from Rabindranath Tagore called The Stream of Life. The music to accompany this poem is the Indian National Anthem, the words of which were also written by Rabindranath Tagore.
We have a question, and a lot of shoutouts from around the world.
We have music, courtesy of Promonet tonight! We have Be the Change from the album Elephant Power by MC Yogi. We also have Atlas from the album Arabesque by Belly Dance which you can buy here at ITunes!
We are proud members of the Ioda Alliance!
We would also like to express our thanks to Anji Bee for her help in finding music for this show. Anji has a great podcast and we are both big fans of her band the Love Spirals.</description>
                    <enclosure length="71603465" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/A_Buddhist_Podcast_-_Action_for_Happiness.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:14:35</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Tonights show is so full!

Tonights lectures is based on guidance that President Ikeda gave earlier this year about the four points for victory. The four points are Prayer, Action, Unity and the Oneness of Mentor and Disciple. This lecture is about...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>A Buddhist Podcast - The Reluctant Buddhist - Chapter 3</title>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2008 11:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/index.php?post_id=403602#</guid>
                    <link>http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/a_buddhist_podcast_the_reluctant_buddhist_chapter_3</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/695213"/>
                    <description>Have you ever wanted an explanation of where this Buddhism came from to give to your friends or family to help explain your practice? Well that is what the substance of tonights show is! William Woollard reads Chapter 3 from his extraordinary book, The Reluctant Buddhist!

We have shoutouts and the music tonight comes from Beth Thornley. Its not like us to only play one artist, but we liked both of the tracks! So from Beth Thornley we play Mr Lovely and Birmingham. As usual we are very grateful to the Podsafe Music Network for providing us with the ability to play this music on our show.

We are working on two new shows which will be appearing in the next few weeks! Thank you so much for listening to the show and for all your wonderful feedback. Have a great week and take care of yourselves and the people around you.</description>
                    <enclosure length="61806587" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/A_Buddhist_Podcast_-_The_Reluctant_Buddhist_-_Chapter_3.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:04:22</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Have you ever wanted an explanation of where this Buddhism came from to give to your friends or family to help explain your practice? Well that is what the substance of tonights show is! William Woollard reads Chapter 3 from his extraordinary book,...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>A Buddhist Podcast - Special Edition - Grade 2 Study Support</title>
                    <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2008 10:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/index.php?post_id=398094#</guid>
                    <link>http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/a_buddhist_podcast_special_edition_grade_2_study_support</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/695212"/>
                    <description>Tonight's show is a bit of an experiment! For some time now we have had a lot of requests from listeners to provide support for the level 2 study courses that are taking place in Europe at the moment. This study will culminate in an exam in mid November for those who want to take it. William Woollard has also had many requests for support in this activity, so we have got together to produce a special edition show!

The exam consists of 5 sections, A, B, C, D and E. Each section has a number of questions. In the exam you will be asked one question from each section. On this podcast, William has prepared an answer for every question. It is NOT a model answer but the kind of answer that William would make based upon the study material provided. Remember the questions require you to use the study material rather than your existing knowledge.

If you are not a member of SGI in Europe at the moment but you would like to follow along, you can hop over to this site and download the study material we are looking at! Remember you need to look for the Grade 2 material.

If you are doing the Grade 1 study course, you still might find value in listening to the show as both Grade 1 and Grade 2 share the same questions in Section E about the Priesthood.

In between all of this study material, we have still found time for some music. On tonight's show we play a wonderful track by Black Lab called Lonely Boy and for the second time on the show Great Day by the amazing Jody Gnant. Music courtesy of the Podsafe Music Network

Thank you for downloading the show! We have a great show coming up in 2 weeks so keep an eye out for it! Thank you as well for all your support.</description>
                    <enclosure length="85275705" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/A_Buddhist_Podcast_-_Special_Edition_-_Grade_2_Study_Support.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:28:49</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Tonight's show is a bit of an experiment! For some time now we have had a lot of requests from listeners to provide support for the level 2 study courses that are taking place in Europe at the moment. This study will culminate in an exam in mid...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>A Buddhist Podcast - The Reluctant Buddhist - Chapter 1 part 2 and Much More</title>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2008 06:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/index.php?post_id=393682#</guid>
                    <link>http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/a_buddhist_podcast_the_reluctant_buddhist_chapter_1_part_2_and_much_more</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/695211"/>
                    <description>Well we have a bit of an extravaganza for you this week! Kicking of the show is William Woollard who completes the second half of Chapter 1 from The Reluctant Buddhist. Karen reads a truly inspiring contribution from Cindy Woodland from Canada! We have more shoutouts that cross the globe and we attempt to answer a question about how we as parents interest our children in Buddhist Practice.

Tonight we play three tracks from the Podsafe Music Network, Anduze with Just Feel Good, Lee Coulter with I Would Love and Black Lab with Broken Heart!.

Keep a look out for a special show coming out next week. William Woollard has put together some great study material surrounding the Level 2 Study Exam that is taking place in Europe in November.

Thank you so much for taking the time to listen to the show, for writing to let us know how you feel about about it, for your encouragement on Facebook and for the great comments on the website. From the bottom of our hearts, Thank you! Have a wonderful week.</description>
                    <enclosure length="67108713" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/A_Buddhist_Podcast_-_Chapter_1_Part_2_and_Much_More.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:09:54</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Well we have a bit of an extravaganza for you this week! Kicking of the show is William Woollard who completes the second half of Chapter 1 from The Reluctant Buddhist. Karen reads a truly inspiring contribution from Cindy Woodland from Canada! We...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>A Buddhist Podcast - Prayer</title>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2008 21:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/index.php?post_id=387995#</guid>
                    <link>http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/a_buddhist_podcast_prayer</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/695210"/>
                    <description>Thanks to Jessica Miller who not only did the wonderful artwork for tonights show but also came up with the idea of asking Kevin Robinson to give tonights lecture. Kevin originally gave this lecture at the North London Area Course at Trets in September this year (2008). 
I travelled up to London and we recorded this lecture at Kevin's wonderful home. Its about Prayer and we hope you enjoy listening to it as much as we enjoyed recording and putting it together!

Great shoutouts from the wonderful Karen and some wonderful music from Mark Erelli singing The Only Way and Bob Gentry singing Goldie Hawn! Both tracks are available from the Podsafe Music Network.

Again we had planned to play the second half of William Woollards Chapter 1 tonight. However, we wanted to include an interview that we are working on but we did not manage to get it done in time! Bear with us and we hope the next show will include the second half!

Thank you so much for listening and for your encouraging comments and emails. Enjoy the show and have a great week.</description>
                    <enclosure length="49270755" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/A_Buddhist_Podcast_-_Prayer.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>51:19</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Thanks to Jessica Miller who not only did the wonderful artwork for tonights show but also came up with the idea of asking Kevin Robinson to give tonights lecture. Kevin originally gave this lecture at the North London Area Course at Trets in...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>A Buddhist Podcast - Reply to Sairen-bo</title>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2008 22:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/index.php?post_id=382828#</guid>
                    <link>http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/a_buddhist_podcast_reply_to_sairen_bo</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/695209"/>
                    <description>Tonights show is a lecture on Nichiren Daishonin's letter called 'Reply to Sairen-bo'.The theme is once more on the mentor disciple relationship . Themes include:

Trapped for 3 score years and 10
The disciple chooses the mentor
What is Buddhahood?
Devil kings and demons
I don't want to spend my life in the toilet of mankind
What qualifies the mentor?
Creating a whirlpool of joy.

In honour of 25 years playing music, we play, from the Podsafe Music Network, Howard Jones and his song Building our own Future. We are also lucky enough to have a great track from Peter Robinson called Roar of the Wind for the men of the South of England.

Originally we had planned to play the second half of William Woollards Chapter 1 tonight. However, we wanted to include an interview that we are working on but we did not manage to get it done in time! So the next show will include the second half!

Thank you for listening and for your encouragement comments and kind emails. Your support is really welcomed, have a great week.</description>
                    <enclosure length="62113823" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/A_Buddhist_Podcast_-_Reply_to_Sairen-bo.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:04:42</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Tonights show is a lecture on Nichiren Daishonin's letter called 'Reply to Sairen-bo'.The theme is once more on the mentor disciple relationship . Themes include:

Trapped for 3 score years and 10
The disciple chooses the mentor
What is...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>A Buddhist Podcast - The Reluctant Buddhist - Chapter 1 part 1</title>
                    <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2008 09:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/index.php?post_id=376187#</guid>
                    <link>http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/a_buddhist_podcast_the_reluctant_buddhist_chapter_1_part_1</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/695207"/>
                    <description>Tonight we are very pleased to have William Woollard back on the show. William reads the first half of Chapter 1 from his book, The Reluctant Buddhist. 
We have shoutouts that span the globe and a great poem from Bob Kemp from Bournemouth in the UK.
Thank you so much to William Wey who provided the artwork for this weeks show!
Tonights music comes from the Podsafe Music Network. We play White Feather by Phil Ayoub and Inside of Me by The Ivy League.
Thank you for listening and for the wonderful comments and kind emails. Your support is really welcomed, have a great week.</description>
                    <enclosure length="49665696" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/A_Buddhist_Podcast_-_The_Reluctant_Buddhist_-_Chapter_1.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>51:44</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Tonight we are very pleased to have William Woollard back on the show. William reads the first half of Chapter 1 from his book, The Reluctant Buddhist. 
We have shoutouts that span the globe and a great poem from Bob Kemp from Bournemouth in the...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>A Buddhist Podcast - Bodhisattvas of the Earth</title>
                    <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2008 15:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/index.php?post_id=368813#</guid>
                    <link>http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/a_buddhist_podcast_bodhisattvas_of_the_earth</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/695206"/>
                    <description>Tonight we are looking another passage from Nichiren Daishonin's letter to Sairen-bo, &lt;a href="http://www.sgilibrary.org/view.php?page=216&amp;m=1&amp;q=heritage%20of%20the%20ultimate%20law%20of%20life" title="Link to the full text of the letter"&gt;The Heritage of the Ultimate Law of Life&lt;/a&gt;. The theme of tonights lecture is the Bodhisattvas of the Earth and it includes the following headings!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;div style="margin-left: 40px;"&gt;What is Buddhism about?&lt;br/&gt;Bodhisattva Superior Practices&lt;br/&gt;Belief is not enough&lt;br/&gt;The Mystic Law is life itself&lt;br/&gt;What does Nam-myoho-renge-kyo mean?&lt;br/&gt;Our lives are the candles of life&lt;br/&gt;Flushing with the Mystic Law&lt;br/&gt;Blowing away negativity&lt;br/&gt;Nurturing life&lt;br/&gt;Tapping our toes to the tune of the Mystic Law&lt;br/&gt;Awakening others to the greatness within their lives&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;We have a wonderful experience from Jonathan Steele and shoutouts that stretch across the world!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Tonights music comes from the &lt;a href="http://music.podshow.com/music/listeners/artistdetails.php?BandHash=8bc1b7a5a418648df44ac18bed817933" title="Amy Regan"&gt;Podsafe Music Network&lt;/a&gt;. We play a great relaxing kick back tune from &lt;a href="http://www.slackstring.com"&gt;Slackstring&lt;/a&gt; called &lt;a href="http://music.podshow.com/music/listeners/artistdetails.php?BandHash=e4967629e3ece2e3d6637a794654f79b" title="Slackstring"&gt;Sun Again Will Shine&lt;/a&gt;. Also tonight we have a really great tune from singer songwriter &lt;a href="http://www.amyregan.com/index2.php"&gt;Amy Regan&lt;/a&gt;, what an amazing voice, she sings &lt;a href="http://"&gt;Everybody Needs Somewhere To Go&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="http://"&gt;.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Thank you for listening and for the wonderful comments and kind emails. Your support is really welcomed, have a great week.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br type="_moz"/&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="64827824" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/A_Buddhist_Podcast_-_Bodhisattvas_of_the_Earth.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:07:31</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Tonight we are looking another passage from Nichiren Daishonin's letter to Sairen-bo, The Heritage of the Ultimate Law of Life. The theme of tonights lecture is the Bodhisattvas of the Earth and it includes the following headings!What is Buddhism...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>A Buddhist Podcast - Mentor and Disciple</title>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2008 13:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/index.php?post_id=356065#</guid>
                    <link>http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/a_buddhist_podcast_mentor_and_disciple</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/695205"/>
                    <description>On tonights show we study a passage from the writing, The Heritage of the Ultimate Law of Life. The theme of tonights lecture is the mentor disciple relationship and it includes the following headings!
The Tsukuhara Debate
The purpose of Buddhism
The Buddha was not a bronze statue
Hardships strengthen our happiness
Human revolution produced human gold
Mount Sumeru
Tsunasaburo Makiguchi
Josei Toda
Daisaku Ikeda
What happens when the mentor passes away?
Again its another full show with shoutouts that criss cross the globe and music from the Podsafe Music Network. On tonights show we play Ocean from Zach Ashton and Great Day from the wonderful Jody Gnant.Thank you so much for your support of the show, have a great week.</description>
                    <enclosure length="63392001" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/A_Buddhist_Podcast_-_Mentor_and_Disciple.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:06:02</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>On tonights show we study a passage from the writing, The Heritage of the Ultimate Law of Life. The theme of tonights lecture is the mentor disciple relationship and it includes the following headings!
The Tsukuhara Debate
The purpose of...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>A Buddhist Podcast - Yet I feel joy</title>
                    <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2008 09:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/index.php?post_id=347029#</guid>
                    <link>http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/a_buddhist_podcast_yet_i_feel_joy</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/695204"/>
                    <description>Tonights lecture is based on a letter written by Nichiren Daishonin called, “Condolences on a Deceased Husband”. Highlight headlines include:
1278 - So what? 
Li Ju-hsien 
Yet I feel joy 
Dr Martin Luther King
Hated more than thieves
The price of piety
Curtailing liberties
Prayer rooted in action
A fingernail of dirt
Music from tonights show is from the Podsafe Music Network. Its a double bill from the great band Great Big Sea. We play two of their tracks, Own True Way and Something Beautiful. There are shout outs and slurps of tea and I have no idea how it all fitted in! Thank you for listening. If you like the show let us know or post a review on Itunes! Have a great week!</description>
                    <enclosure length="65624913" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/A_Buddhist_Podcast_-_Yet_I_feel_joy.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:08:21</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>A Buddhist Podcast - Yet I feel joy</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>A Buddhist Podcast - The Reluctant Buddhist</title>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2008 19:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/index.php?post_id=341059#</guid>
                    <link>http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/a_buddhist_podcast_the_reluctant_buddhist</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/695203"/>
                    <description>On tonights show we are delighted to have a guest appearance from William Woollard. William made the journey to Forest Row and was kind enough to let us record him reading Chapter 2 of his book, The Reluctant Buddhist. Its very personal and I found myself captivated while I was recording. Thank you so much William!We have shoutouts and great music from The Reveals who sing Want You Back and Sarah Vonderhaar whose beautiful voice gets you welcoming the summer with I Got Sunshine!Our next lecture is being written and should be up very soon! Thank you so much for listening!</description>
                    <enclosure length="43041880" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/A_Buddhist_Podcast_-_The_Reluctant_Buddhist.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>44:50</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>On tonights show we are delighted to have a guest appearance from William Woollard. William made the journey to Forest Row and was kind enough to let us record him reading Chapter 2 of his book, The Reluctant Buddhist. Its very personal and I found...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>A Buddhist Podcast - On the Treasure Tower</title>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2008 21:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/index.php?post_id=325673#</guid>
                    <link>http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/A_Buddhist_Podcast_-_On_the_Treasure_Tower.mp3</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/695201"/>
                    <description>We are back! Tonights show begins with a lecture on the letter Nichiren Daishonin worte to his 83 year old disciple Abutsu-bo. The letter is called On the Treasure Tower. Points include:
An incredible seeking spirit;
What is the treasure tower?;
We are the treasure tower;
What? You don't like your reality?;
Forests of treasure towers;
Seven kinds of treasure;
The Gohonzon is the blueprint of our lives;
The family treasure.
After the lecture we play Here and Now by Mike Erelli from the Podsafe Music Network. Next up, Karen reads an experience from the wonderful Roxanne Rae. Then we have shoutouts that cross the globe and we have a special finish. We close with a beautiful song by the amazing Peter Robinson, its called A Piece of Mirror.
If you are looking for more experiences about practicing this Buddhism, have a look at The Buddha Next Door, a wonderful book 
Have a great week and take great care!</description>
                    <enclosure length="73131377" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/A_Buddhist_Podcast_-_On_the_Treasure_Tower.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:16:10</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>We are back! Tonights show begins with a lecture on the letter Nichiren Daishonin worte to his 83 year old disciple Abutsu-bo. The letter is called On the Treasure Tower. Points include:
An incredible seeking spirit;
What is the treasure tower?;
We...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>A Buddhist Podcast - The Buddha, Geoff and Me - Chapter 16</title>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2008 21:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/index.php?post_id=315637#</guid>
                    <link>http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/a_buddhist_podcast_the_buddha_geoff_and_me_chapter_16</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/695200"/>
                    <description>Well, here is the final chapter of this amazing novel. &lt;br/&gt;Chapter 16 of The Buddha, Geoff and Me, a novel by Eddy Canfor-Dumas.
Read by Kevin Eldon. Music by Howard Jones. Artwork by Jessica Miller.
Sincere thanks to Coralyn Sheldon, Jasper Bentinck, Peter Osborn and
Dialogics. The producer was Jason Jarrett. A new chapter appears every
two weeks. If you like the book it is available on Amazon and you can
find it in the stores on the sidebar!&lt;br/&gt;New lecture still in works!&lt;br type="_moz"/&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="14014741" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/A_Buddhist_Podcast_-_The_Buddha_Geoff_and_Me_-_Chapter_16.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>14:35</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Well, here is the final chapter of this amazing novel. Chapter 16 of The Buddha, Geoff and Me, a novel by Eddy Canfor-Dumas.
Read by Kevin Eldon. Music by Howard Jones. Artwork by Jessica Miller.
Sincere thanks to Coralyn Sheldon, Jasper Bentinck,...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>A Buddhist Podcast - The Buddha, Geoff and Me - Chapter 15</title>
                    <pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2008 19:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/index.php?post_id=310317#</guid>
                    <link>http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/A_Buddhist_Podcast_-_The_Buddha_Geoff_and_Me_-_Chapter_15.mp3</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/695199"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Thank you so much for your patience, now at last Chapter 15 is here, this episode was unusually challenging to put together, thank you to everyone for their help!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chapter 15 of The Buddha, Geoff and Me, a novel by Eddy
Canfor-Dumas. Read by Kevin Eldon. Music by Howard Jones. Artwork by
Jessica Miller. Sincere thanks to Coralyn Sheldon, Jasper Bentinck,
Peter Osborn and Dialogics. The producer was Jason Jarrett. A new
chapter appears every two weeks. If you like the book it is available
on Amazon and you can find it in the stores on the sidebar!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Have a wonderful week! New lecture coming soon.&lt;br type="_moz"/&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="31801569" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/A_Buddhist_Podcast_-_The_Buddha_Geoff_and_Me_-_Chapter_15.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>33:07</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Thank you so much for your patience, now at last Chapter 15 is here, this episode was unusually challenging to put together, thank you to everyone for their help!

Chapter 15 of The Buddha, Geoff and Me, a novel by Eddy
Canfor-Dumas. Read by Kevin...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>A Buddhist Podcast - The Buddha, Geoff and Me - Chapter 14</title>
                    <pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2008 21:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/index.php?post_id=305442#</guid>
                    <link>http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/A_Buddhist_Podcast_-_The_Buddha_Geoff_and_Me_-_Chapter_14.mp3</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/695198"/>
                    <description>Chapter 14 of The Buddha, Geoff and Me, a novel by Eddy
Canfor-Dumas. Read by Kevin Eldon. Music by Howard Jones. Artwork by
Jessica Miller. Sincere thanks to Coralyn Sheldon, Jasper Bentinck,
Peter Osborn and Dialogics. The producer was Jason Jarrett. A new
chapter appears every two weeks. If you like the book it is available
on Amazon and you can find it in the stores on the sidebar!</description>
                    <enclosure length="27948451" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/A_Buddhist_Podcast_-_The_Buddha_Geoff_and_Me_-_Chapter_14.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>29:06</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Chapter 14 of The Buddha, Geoff and Me, a novel by Eddy
Canfor-Dumas. Read by Kevin Eldon. Music by Howard Jones. Artwork by
Jessica Miller. Sincere thanks to Coralyn Sheldon, Jasper Bentinck,
Peter Osborn and Dialogics. The producer was Jason...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>A Buddhist Podcast - The Buddha, Geoff and Me - Chapter 13</title>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jan 2008 19:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/index.php?post_id=300862#</guid>
                    <link>http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/A_Buddhist_Podcast_-_The_Buddha_Geoff_and_Me_-_Chapter_13.mp3</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/695197"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;We have arrived at Chapter 13!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;If you like it, share it!Chapter 12
of The Buddha, Geoff and Me, a novel by Eddy Canfor-Dumas. Read by
Kevin Eldon. Music by Howard Jones. Artwork by Jessica Miller. Sincere
thanks to Coralyn Sheldon, Jasper Bentinck, Peter Osborn and Dialogics.
The producer was Jason Jarrett. A new chapter appears every two weeks.
If you like the book it is available on Amazon and you can find it in
the stores on the sidebar!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Children, Karen and I are doing our best and we have food on the table!&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="38844375" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/A_Buddhist_Podcast_-_The_Buddha_Geoff_and_Me_-_Chapter_13.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>40:27</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>We have arrived at Chapter 13!
If you like it, share it!Chapter 12
of The Buddha, Geoff and Me, a novel by Eddy Canfor-Dumas. Read by
Kevin Eldon. Music by Howard Jones. Artwork by Jessica Miller. Sincere
thanks to Coralyn Sheldon, Jasper...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>A Buddhist Podcast - The Buddha, Geoff and Me - Chapter 12</title>
                    <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2008 07:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/index.php?post_id=296820#</guid>
                    <link>http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/A_Buddhist_Podcast_-_The_Buddha_Geoff_and_Me_-_Chapter_12.mp3</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/695196"/>
                    <description>We hope you enjoy Chapter 12!&amp;nbsp; If you like it, share it!
&lt;p&gt;Chapter 12 of The Buddha, Geoff and Me, a novel by Eddy
Canfor-Dumas. Read by Kevin Eldon. Music by Howard Jones. Artwork by
Jessica Miller. Sincere thanks to Coralyn Sheldon, Jasper Bentinck,
Peter Osborn and Dialogics. The producer was Jason Jarrett. A new
chapter appears every two weeks. If you like the book it is available
on Amazon and you can find it in the stores on the sidebar!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you for all the wonderful feedback! Have a terrific week!&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="37571595" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/A_Buddhist_Podcast_-_The_Buddha_Geoff_and_Me_-_Chapter_12.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>39:08</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>We hope you enjoy Chapter 12!&amp;nbsp; If you like it, share it!
Chapter 12 of The Buddha, Geoff and Me, a novel by Eddy
Canfor-Dumas. Read by Kevin Eldon. Music by Howard Jones. Artwork by
Jessica Miller. Sincere thanks to Coralyn Sheldon, Jasper...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>A Buddhist Podcast - The Buddha, Geoff and Me - Chapter 11</title>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2007 13:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/index.php?post_id=292137#</guid>
                    <link>http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/A_Buddhist_Podcast_-_The_Buddha_Geoff_and_Me_-_Chapter_11.mp3</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/695195"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;A very happy new year to one and all! Towards a year of Capable People and Development!&lt;br/&gt;
Here is Chapter 11! I loved working on this episode! If you like it, share it!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Chapter 11 of The Buddha, Geoff and Me, a novel by Eddy Canfor-Dumas.
Read by Kevin Eldon. Music by Howard Jones. Artwork by Jessica Miller.
Sincere thanks to Coralyn Sheldon, Jasper Bentinck, Peter Osborn and
Dialogics. The producer was Jason Jarrett. A new chapter appears
every two weeks. If you like the book it is available on Amazon and you
can find it in the stores on http://www.abuddhistpodcast.com !&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="32892793" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/A_Buddhist_Podcast_-_The_Buddha_Geoff_and_Me_-_Chapter_11.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>34:15</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>A very happy new year to one and all! Towards a year of Capable People and Development!
Here is Chapter 11! I loved working on this episode! If you like it, share it!
Chapter 11 of The Buddha, Geoff and Me, a novel by Eddy Canfor-Dumas.
Read by...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>A Buddhist Podcast - The Izu Exile</title>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 17 Dec 2007 21:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/index.php?post_id=288525#</guid>
                    <link>http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/a_buddhist_podcast_the_izu_exile</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/695194"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Well, finally, we are back with a lecture on The Izu Exile! &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We talk about:&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Yasaburo and his wife&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Appreciation&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Standing up for what is right, no matter what&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Buddhist Gods are practical&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Become respected in the community&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The music for tonights show comes from the Podsafe Music Network and includes:&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.btpodshow.com/music/?artist_id=4658" mce_href="http://www.btpodshow.com/music/?artist_id=4658" title="Link to Vittoria Conn on the PMN"&gt;Vittoria Conn singing Merry Christmas Angel&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.btpodshow.com/music/?artist_id=11754" mce_href="http://www.btpodshow.com/music/?artist_id=11754" title="Link to Mark Stoney on the PMN"&gt;Mark Stoney singing Jailbird&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A sincere and special thanks to everyone who has supported us.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We
have copies of the two books we mention The Buddha Next Door and The
Reluctant Buddhist in the online shops in the right hand column!&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We wanted also to make reference to some information we talk about in the show!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Jason gets interviewed by &lt;a href="http://www.thepodcastsisters.com/2007/11/show-026---soci.html#" mce_href="http://www.thepodcastsisters.com/2007/11/show-026---soci.html#"&gt;The Podcast Sisters&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Jason gets interviewed by Robin Maiden from &lt;a href="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/m.podshow.com/media/135/episodes/86479/insytworks-86479-11-08-2007.mp3" mce_href="http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/m.podshow.com/media/135/episodes/86479/insytworks-86479-11-08-2007.mp3"&gt;Insytworks&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The beautiful art of &lt;a href="http://www.susannahkelly.com/" mce_href="http://www.susannahkelly.com/"&gt;Susannah Kelly&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://continuitytalk.com/" mce_href="http://continuitytalk.com"&gt;ContinuityTalk&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://forestrowradio.com/" mce_href="http://forestrowradio.com"&gt;ForestRowRadio&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="58121782" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/A_Buddhist_Podcast_-_The_Izu_Exile.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:00:32</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Well, finally, we are back with a lecture on The Izu Exile! 
We talk about:


Yasaburo and his wifeAppreciationStanding up for what is right, no matter whatBuddhist Gods are practicalBecome respected in the community

The music for tonights show...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>A Buddhist Podcast - The Buddha, Geoff and Me - Chapter 10</title>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 09 Dec 2007 19:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/index.php?post_id=285883#</guid>
                    <link>http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/A_Buddhist_Podcast_-_The_Buddha_Geoff_and_Me_-_Chapter_10.mp3</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/695193"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Thank you everyone for your encouragement, happy to deliver Chapter
10, this was quite an adventure but here it is. I am currently nearly
finished with a new lecture and hope to have it out in the next few
days!&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Chapter 10 of The Buddha, Geoff and Me, a novel by Eddy
Canfor-Dumas. Read by Kevin Eldon. Music by Howard Jones. Artwork by
Jessica Miller. Sincere thanks to Coralyn Sheldon, Jasper Bentinck,
Peter Osborn and Dialogics. The producer was Jason Jarrett. A new
chapter will appear every two weeks. If you like the book it is
available on Amazon and you can find it in the stores on the sidebar! &lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="32894130" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/A_Buddhist_Podcast_-_The_Buddha_Geoff_and_Me_-_Chapter_10.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>34:15</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Thank you everyone for your encouragement, happy to deliver Chapter
10, this was quite an adventure but here it is. I am currently nearly
finished with a new lecture and hope to have it out in the next few
days!

Chapter 10 of The Buddha, Geoff...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>A Buddhist Podcast - The Buddha, Geoff and Me - Chapter 9</title>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 25 Nov 2007 22:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/index.php?post_id=281337#</guid>
                    <link>http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/A_Buddhist_Podcast_-_The_Buddha_Geoff_and_Me_-_Chapter_9.mp3</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/695192"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;And bang on time, we have another chapter of this brilliant book!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chapter 9 of The Buddha, Geoff and Me, a novel by Eddy Canfor-Dumas.
Read by Kevin Eldon. Music by Howard Jones. Artwork by Jessica Miller.
Sincere thanks to Coralyn Sheldon, Jasper Bentinck, Peter Osborn and
Dialogics. The producer was Jason Jarrett. A new chapter will appear
every two weeks. If you like the book it is available on Amazon.&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="26082338" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/A_Buddhist_Podcast_-_The_Buddha_Geoff_and_Me_-_Chapter_9.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>27:10</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>And bang on time, we have another chapter of this brilliant book!

Chapter 9 of The Buddha, Geoff and Me, a novel by Eddy Canfor-Dumas.
Read by Kevin Eldon. Music by Howard Jones. Artwork by Jessica Miller.
Sincere thanks to Coralyn Sheldon,...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>A Buddhist Podcast - The Buddha, Geoff and Me - Chapter 8</title>
                    <pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2007 16:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/index.php?post_id=277696#</guid>
                    <link>http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/The_Buddha_Geoff_and_Me_-_Chapter_8.mp3</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/695190"/>
                    <description>Thank you for your patience. Theres an interesting story in the struggle to get this ready to go! Thank you.&lt;br/&gt;Chapter 8 of The Buddha, Geoff and Me, a novel by Eddy
Canfor-Dumas. Read by Kevin Eldon. Music by Howard Jones. Artwork by
Jessica Miller. Sincere thanks to Coralyn Sheldon, Jasper Bentinck,
Peter Osborn and Dialogics. The producer was Jason Jarrett. A new
chapter will appear every two weeks. If you like the book it is
available on Amazon and all over! The book’s website is &lt;a href="http://www.amazon.co.uk/gp/product/1844135683/026-0099646-2446073?ie=UTF8&amp;tag=jasonjarrett-21&amp;linkCode=xm2&amp;creativeASIN=1844135683"&gt;The Buddha, Geoff and Me&lt;/a&gt;.</description>
                    <enclosure length="31707677" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/The_Buddha_Geoff_and_Me_-_Chapter_8.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>33:01</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Thank you for your patience. Theres an interesting story in the struggle to get this ready to go! Thank you.Chapter 8 of The Buddha, Geoff and Me, a novel by Eddy
Canfor-Dumas. Read by Kevin Eldon. Music by Howard Jones. Artwork by
Jessica Miller....</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>A Buddhist Podcast - The Buddha, Geoff and Me - Chapter 7</title>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2007 09:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/index.php?post_id=266818#</guid>
                    <link>http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/The_Buddha_Geoff_and_Me_-_Chapter_7.mp3</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/695188"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Here it is!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chapter 7 of The Buddha, Geoff and Me, a novel by Eddy Canfor-Dumas.
Read by Kevin Eldon. Music by Howard Jones. Artwork by Jessica Miller.
Sincere thanks to Coralyn Sheldon, Jasper Bentinck, Peter Osborn and
Dialogics. The producer was Jason Jarrett. A new chapter will appear
every two weeks. If you like the book it is available on Amazon and all
over! The book’s website is The Buddha, Geoff and Me.
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="29582080" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/The_Buddha_Geoff_and_Me_-_Chapter_7.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>30:48</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Here it is!

Chapter 7 of The Buddha, Geoff and Me, a novel by Eddy Canfor-Dumas.
Read by Kevin Eldon. Music by Howard Jones. Artwork by Jessica Miller.
Sincere thanks to Coralyn Sheldon, Jasper Bentinck, Peter Osborn and
Dialogics. The producer...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>A Buddhist Podcast - Sacramento - Part 1</title>
                    <pubDate>Thu, 04 Oct 2007 22:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/index.php?post_id=263129#</guid>
                    <link>http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/A_Buddhist_Podcast__-__Sacramento_-__Part_1.mp3</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/695186"/>
                    <description>Tonights show was recorded over this last weekend in &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Sacramento"&gt;Sacramento&lt;/a&gt;,
California. It was made possible thanks to the experiences and
commitment of the most amazing members who shared their lives with
Jason and microphones to give you this show.&lt;br/&gt;
We recorded more material which we will be including in forthcoming shows. The music for tonights show comes from the &lt;a href="http:///"&gt;Podsafe Music Network&lt;/a&gt; and includes:&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;a href="http://music.podshow.com/music/listeners/artistdetails.php?BandHash=7d408c275d4f21102da59a97840ee701"&gt;Border Blasters&lt;/a&gt;, Next time you see me&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;a href="http://music.podshow.com/music/listeners/artistdetails.php?BandHash=876d55dbf0e29133c3ed0bcfb0ee5d4a"&gt;Sharon Jones&lt;/a&gt;, 100 days and 100 nights&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;a href="http://music.podshow.com/music/listeners/artistdetails.php?BandHash=46c485513c1225b012ce6667ed1d5148"&gt;Otis Redding&lt;/a&gt;, Shake&lt;br/&gt;
A sincere and special thanks to Donna Parten and Dash Antel and all the
members of SGI-USA who made my recent trip to the US so successful.</description>
                    <enclosure length="58939012" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/A_Buddhist_Podcast__-__Sacramento_-__Part_1.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:01:23</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Tonights show was recorded over this last weekend in Sacramento,
California. It was made possible thanks to the experiences and
commitment of the most amazing members who shared their lives with
Jason and microphones to give you this show.
We...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Buddhist Podcast - The Buddha, Geoff and Me - Chapter 6</title>
                    <pubDate>Sat, 29 Sep 2007 16:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/index.php?post_id=261188#</guid>
                    <link>http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/_buddhist_podcast_the_buddha_geoff_and_me_chapter_6</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/695185"/>
                    <description>Here is Chapter 6!

Chapter 6 of The Buddha, Geoff and Me, a novel by Eddy Canfor-Dumas. Read by Kevin Eldon. Music by Howard Jones. Artwork by Jessica Miller. Sincere thanks to Coralyn Sheldon, Jasper Bentinck, Peter Osborn and Dialogics. The producer was Jason Jarrett. A new chapter will appear every two weeks. If you like the book it is available on Amazon and all over! The book’s website is The Buddha, Geoff and Me.</description>
                    <enclosure length="25409207" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/The_Buddha_Geoff_and_Me_-_Chapter_6.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>26:28</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Here is Chapter 6!

Chapter 6 of The Buddha, Geoff and Me, a novel by Eddy Canfor-Dumas. Read by Kevin Eldon. Music by Howard Jones. Artwork by Jessica Miller. Sincere thanks to Coralyn Sheldon, Jasper Bentinck, Peter Osborn and Dialogics. The...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>A Buddhist Podcast - Tatsunokuchi</title>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2007 12:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/index.php?post_id=256648#</guid>
                    <link>http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/A_Buddhist_Podcast_-_Tatsunokuchi.mp3</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/695184"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Well finally we are back with another show! Tonights show is about the letter, The Persecution at Tatsunokuchi. Among all the things we cover we look:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* Background on Tatsunokuchi&lt;br /&gt; * Taurid Arietid Meteor stream, right on time&lt;br /&gt; * Shijo Kingo 16 years without a Gohonzon&lt;br /&gt; * The Master Disciple pipeline&lt;br /&gt; * Big goal = Big life&lt;br /&gt; * Fighting fear&lt;br /&gt; * Postcard from Japan&lt;br /&gt; * Faith is nothing unusual&lt;br /&gt; * Our karmic GPS&lt;br /&gt; * Teachers&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tonight we have 'The Music' from &lt;a title="David Usher on the PMN" href="http://music.podshow.com/music/listeners/artistdetails.php?BandHash=374d033c0b55ec78b821d778c253a13a"&gt;David Usher&lt;/a&gt;. To commemorate the 50th Anniversary of Josei Toda&amp;rsquo;s declaration against nuclear weapons, we play 'Trinity' by &lt;a title="Vittoria Conn on the PMN" href="http://music.podshow.com/music/listeners/artistdetails.php?BandHash=fabc7825814ef11f2661a819697f975a"&gt;Vittoria Conn&lt;/a&gt;. Both David and Vittoria are artists on the &lt;a title="Link to PMN" href="http://music.podshow.com/"&gt;Podsafe Music Network&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt; Thank you for listening!&lt;br /&gt; If you have a question or an experience you would like to send us, write to karen(at)thejarretts.com or jason(at)thejarretts.com&lt;br /&gt; If you get a moment, and you would like to, we would really appreciate it if you could write us a review on ITunes. Have a great week!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="57006068" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/A_Buddhist_Podcast_-_Tatsunokuchi.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>59:22</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Well finally we are back with another show! Tonights show is about the letter, The Persecution at Tatsunokuchi. Among all the things we cover we look:
* Background on Tatsunokuchi * Taurid Arietid Meteor stream, right on time * Shijo Kingo 16 years...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>A Buddhist Podcast - The Buddha, Geoff and Me - Chapter 5</title>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2007 12:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/index.php?post_id=256253#</guid>
                    <link>http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/The_Buddha_Geoff_and_Me_-_Chapter_5.mp3</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/695183"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;And right on time . . . Chapter 5!&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Chapter 5 of &lt;em&gt;The Buddha, Geoff and Me&lt;/em&gt;, a novel by Eddy
Canfor-Dumas. Read by Kevin Eldon. Music by Howard Jones. Artwork by
Jessica Miller. Sincere thanks to Coralyn Sheldon, Jasper Bentinck,
Peter Osborn and Dialogics. The producer was Jason Jarrett. A new
chapter will appear every two weeks. If you like the book it is
available on Amazon and all over! The book’s website is &lt;a href="http://www.thebuddhageoffandme.com/" target="_blank" title="Home page for the book, The Buddha Geoff and Me"&gt;The Buddha, Geoff and Me. &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;We have recorded another show of A Buddhist Podcast, but some of the recording was missing so we are re-recording tonight!
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="34200566" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/The_Buddha_Geoff_and_Me_-_Chapter_5.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>35:37</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>And right on time . . . Chapter 5!



Chapter 5 of The Buddha, Geoff and Me, a novel by Eddy
Canfor-Dumas. Read by Kevin Eldon. Music by Howard Jones. Artwork by
Jessica Miller. Sincere thanks to Coralyn Sheldon, Jasper Bentinck,
Peter Osborn...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>A Buddhist Podcast - The Buddha, Geoff and Me - Chapter 4</title>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 03 Sep 2007 17:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/index.php?post_id=251926#</guid>
                    <link>http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/The_Buddha_Geoff_and_Me_-_Chapter_4.mp3</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/695182"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;And now for the amazing Chapter 4!&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Chapter 4 of &lt;em&gt;The Buddha, Geoff and Me&lt;/em&gt;, a novel by Eddy
Canfor-Dumas. Read by Kevin Eldon. Music by Howard Jones. Artwork by
Jessica Miller. Sincere thanks to Coralyn Sheldon, Jasper Bentinck,
Peter Osborn and Dialogics. The producer was Jason Jarrett. A new
chapter will appear every two weeks. If you like the book it is
available on Amazon and all over! The book’s website is &lt;a href="http://www.thebuddhageoffandme.com/" target="_blank" title="Home page for the book, The Buddha Geoff and Me"&gt;The Buddha, Geoff and Me. &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;p&gt;We are working on a new talk about discarding the transient and
revealing the true! Thank you so much for downloading the show, have a
wonderful week!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="16670880" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/The_Buddha_Geoff_and_Me_-_Chapter_4.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>17:21</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>And now for the amazing Chapter 4!


Chapter 4 of The Buddha, Geoff and Me, a novel by Eddy
Canfor-Dumas. Read by Kevin Eldon. Music by Howard Jones. Artwork by
Jessica Miller. Sincere thanks to Coralyn Sheldon, Jasper Bentinck,
Peter Osborn and...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>A Buddhist Podcast - Summer Spesh</title>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 26 Aug 2007 08:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/index.php?post_id=249193#</guid>
                    <link>http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/A_Buddhist_Podcast_-_Summer_Spesh.mp3</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/695181"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to a different kind of show. In response to a number of
listener requests we have put together the Summer Spesh, a show that
brings together some of the listeners favourite music from previous
shows, some inspirational quotes, some poetry and an interview between
Peter Osborne and Eddy Canfor-Dumas, the author of The Buddha, Geoff
and Me. Music from tonights show includes:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a mce_href="http://music.podshow.com/music/listeners/artistdetails.php?BandHash=fabc7825814ef11f2661a819697f975a" title="Vittoria Conn on the PMN" href="http://music.podshow.com/music/listeners/artistdetails.php?BandHash=fabc7825814ef11f2661a819697f975a"&gt;Vittoria Conn singing Mirror&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;a mce_href="http://music.podshow.com/music/listeners/artistdetails.php?BandHash=5538385ac96aa74fdbe73f2cc4df6a93" title="Dave Potts on the PMN" href="http://music.podshow.com/music/listeners/artistdetails.php?BandHash=5538385ac96aa74fdbe73f2cc4df6a93"&gt; $12.99 by Dave Potts&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;a mce_href="http://music.podshow.com/music/listeners/artistdetails.php?BandHash=c223ff0affc3956f4744c87e59879b05" title="Howard Jones on the PMN" href="http://music.podshow.com/music/listeners/artistdetails.php?BandHash=c223ff0affc3956f4744c87e59879b05"&gt; Building Our Own Future by Howard Jones&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;a mce_href="http://music.podshow.com/music/listeners/artistdetails.php?BandHash=148cefe228e814695760e94419a9a1f8" title="Bill on the PMN" href="http://music.podshow.com/music/listeners/artistdetails.php?BandHash=148cefe228e814695760e94419a9a1f8"&gt; Bill singing Panacea&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;a mce_href="http://music.podshow.com/music/listeners/artistdetails.php?BandHash=3b32a7f188afce82403a2745ccdeda25" title="Eoghan Colgan on the PMN" href="http://music.podshow.com/music/listeners/artistdetails.php?BandHash=3b32a7f188afce82403a2745ccdeda25"&gt; Eoghan Colgan with Planetary Woman&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;a mce_href="http://music.podshow.com/music/listeners/artistdetails.php?BandHash=96b439ff757e79c8df631087cd2e3af4" title="Selsted Church of England Primary School on the PMN" href="http://music.podshow.com/music/listeners/artistdetails.php?BandHash=96b439ff757e79c8df631087cd2e3af4"&gt; Selsted Church of England Primary School with Save Our School&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;a mce_href="http://music.podshow.com/music/listeners/artistdetails.php?BandHash=c00e4235450a33d751ce365c733db216" title="Supersuckers on the PMN" href="http://music.podshow.com/music/listeners/artistdetails.php?BandHash=c00e4235450a33d751ce365c733db216"&gt; Supersuckers with Some People Say&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;a mce_href="http://music.podshow.com/music/listeners/artistdetails.php?BandHash=280202729dad1ad3a780a4d20afbe39b" title="Matthew Ebel on the PMN" href="http://music.podshow.com/music/listeners/artistdetails.php?BandHash=280202729dad1ad3a780a4d20afbe39b"&gt; Matthew Ebel singing Drive Away&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All the music from tonights show is from the &lt;a mce_href="http://music.podshow.com" title="Podsafe Music Network" href="http://music.podshow.com/"&gt;Podsafe Music Network&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br/&gt;
We will be back in a couple of weeks with a a lecture on The
Persecution at Tatsunokuchi Gosho. Next week is episode 4 of The
Buddha, Geoff and Me. Thank you for listening!&lt;br/&gt;
If you have a question or an experience you would like to send us, write to karen(at)thejarretts.com or jason(at)thejarretts.com&lt;br/&gt;
If you get a moment, and you would like to, it really does help spread
the word if you could write us a review on ITunes. Have a great week!
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="58381462" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/A_Buddhist_Podcast_-_Summer_Spesh.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:00:48</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Welcome to a different kind of show. In response to a number of
listener requests we have put together the Summer Spesh, a show that
brings together some of the listeners favourite music from previous
shows, some inspirational quotes, some poetry...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>A Buddhist Podcast - The Buddha, Geoff and Me - Chapter 3</title>
                    <pubDate>Fri, 17 Aug 2007 19:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/index.php?post_id=246374#</guid>
                    <link>http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/The_Buddha_Geoff_and_Me_-_Chapter_3.mp3</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/695180"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Right on time we have Chapter 3 of &lt;em&gt;The Buddha, Geoff and Me&lt;/em&gt;, a
novel by Eddy Canfor-Dumas. Read by Kevin Eldon. Music by Howard Jones.
Artwork by Jessica Miller. Sincere thanks to Coralyn Sheldon, Jasper
Bentinck, Peter Osborn and Dialogics. The producer was Jason Jarrett. A
new chapter will appear every two weeks. If you like the book it is
available on Amazon and all over! The book’s website is &lt;a href="http://www.thebuddhageoffandme.com/" target="_blank" title="Home page for the book, The Buddha Geoff and Me"&gt;The Buddha, Geoff and Me. &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;p&gt;We are still working on a couple of shows! Please bear with us!&amp;nbsp; Thank you so much for downloading the show, have a wonderful
week!&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="33930977" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/The_Buddha_Geoff_and_Me_-_Chapter_3.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>35:20</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Right on time we have Chapter 3 of The Buddha, Geoff and Me, a
novel by Eddy Canfor-Dumas. Read by Kevin Eldon. Music by Howard Jones.
Artwork by Jessica Miller. Sincere thanks to Coralyn Sheldon, Jasper
Bentinck, Peter Osborn and Dialogics. The...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>A Buddhist Podcast - The Buddha, Geoff and Me - Chapter 2</title>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 05 Aug 2007 07:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/index.php?post_id=242116#</guid>
                    <link>http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/BGAM_Chapter_2.mp3</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/695179"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;And . . . here is chapter 2 of &lt;em&gt;The Buddha, Geoff and Me&lt;/em&gt;,
a novel by Eddy Canfor-Dumas. Read by Kevin Eldon. Music by Howard
Jones. Artwork by Jessica Miller. Sincere thanks to Coralyn Sheldon,
Jasper Bentinck, Peter Osborn and Dialogics. The producer was Jason
Jarrett. A new chapter will appear every two weeks. If you like the
book it is available on Amazon and all over! The book’s website is &lt;a href="http://www.thebuddhageoffandme.com/" target="_blank" title="Home page for the book, The Buddha Geoff and Me"&gt;The Buddha, Geoff and Me. &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are working on a couple of shows, one of which will be appearing next week! Thank you so much for downloading the show, have a wonderful week!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are still collecting gosho quotes and favourite guidance passages for the Summer Spesh show, please send them to us at jason(at)thejarretts.com or karen(at)thejarretts.com. Please remember to reference the pages or source!&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="29197637" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/BGAM_Chapter_2.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>30:24</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>And . . . here is chapter 2 of The Buddha, Geoff and Me,
a novel by Eddy Canfor-Dumas. Read by Kevin Eldon. Music by Howard
Jones. Artwork by Jessica Miller. Sincere thanks to Coralyn Sheldon,
Jasper Bentinck, Peter Osborn and Dialogics. The...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>A Buddhist Podcast - The Buddha Geoff and Me - Chapter 1</title>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2007 13:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/index.php?post_id=237966#</guid>
                    <link>http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/The_Buddha_Geoff_and_Me_-_Chapter_1.mp3</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/695178"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Well . . . we promised it would come and here is the first chapter
of The Buddha Geoff and Me, a novel by Eddie Canfor-Dumas. Kevin Eldon
does the narration, Peter Osborne provides the introductions and
credits. Music was exclusively written and recorded for The Buddha
Geoff and Me by Howard Jones. Artwork was by Jessica Miller. The producer was Jason Jarrett!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A new chapter will appear every two weeks, if you like the book it is available on Amazon and all over! The books website is &lt;a title="Home page for the book, The Buddha Geoff and Me" target="_blank" mce_href="http://www.thebuddhageoffandme.com" href="http://www.thebuddhageoffandme.com/"&gt;The Buddha Geoff and Me&amp;nbsp;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We will be back very soon with a podcast about Buddhism and Relationships!&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="32410282" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/The_Buddha_Geoff_and_Me_-_Chapter_1.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>33:45</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Well . . . we promised it would come and here is the first chapter
of The Buddha Geoff and Me, a novel by Eddie Canfor-Dumas. Kevin Eldon
does the narration, Peter Osborne provides the introductions and
credits. Music was exclusively written and...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>A Buddhist Podcast - Part 2 - On Attaining Buddhahood</title>
                    <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jul 2007 16:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/index.php?post_id=234530#</guid>
                    <link>http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/A_Buddhist_Podcast_-_Part_2_On_Attaining_Buddhahood.mp3</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/695177"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to another show! In this show we look at the second half of On Attaining Buddhahood, which includes:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;For what reason do we live out our lives?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;There are not two lands, pure and impure in themselves&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Isn't the weather miserable?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The schisms of ism's&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Polishing our mirror&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Revealing the gleaming motorcycle within&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Chanting in the morning&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Myoho-renge-kyo&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Apple Tree Sutra&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mastering our minds&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Teachers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tonights show also includes an obituary of &lt;a href="http://www.shinyatomi.com/"&gt;Shin Yatomi&lt;/a&gt; ), written by Donna Parten and read by Karen and Vittoria Conn. We would like to express our deepest condolences to his wife Carolyn and his family and to all who knew and loved him.&lt;br /&gt; Tonight we have music from The SGI-UK Glorious Life Choir who sing 'For the sake of Peace'. This is a great song written by Cory Josias, Veronica Turner, Malcolm Connell, Alex Golding and Howard Jones. We also play music from the &lt;a href="http://music.podshow.com/"&gt;Podsafe Music Network&lt;/a&gt;. We play 'Turnaround' by &lt;a href="http://music.podshow.com/music/listeners/artistdetails.php?BandHash=fabc7825814ef11f2661a819697f975a"&gt;Vitttoria Conn&lt;/a&gt;! Our thanks to Jessica Miller for the wonderful artwork, our lives touching the fabric of life.&lt;br /&gt; Thank you for listening!&lt;br /&gt; If you have a question or an experience you would like to send us, write to karen(at)thejarretts.com or jason(at)thejarretts.com&lt;br /&gt; If you get a moment, and you would like to, we would really appreciate it if you could write us a review on ITunes. Have a great week!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="64556474" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/A_Buddhist_Podcast_-_Part_2_On_Attaining_Buddhahood.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:07:14</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Welcome to another show! In this show we look at the second half of On Attaining Buddhahood, which includes:

For what reason do we live out our lives?
There are not two lands, pure and impure in themselves
Isn't the weather miserable?
The...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>A Buddhist Podcast - Letter to the Brothers</title>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jun 2007 18:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/index.php?post_id=223976#</guid>
                    <link>http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/A_Buddhist_Podcast_-__Letter_to_the_Brothers.mp3</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/695176"/>
                    <description>Welcome to tonights show! Tonights lectures is about overcoming the negativity that rises up whenever we want to change the direction of our lives.&lt;br/&gt;Some soundbites...&lt;br/&gt;1. Are you the protagonist or are you in the audience?&lt;br/&gt;2. Problems are the exercise for our spiritual life&lt;br/&gt;3. A pile of obstacles!&lt;br/&gt;4. You are gorgeous, but I need to do Gongyo first!&lt;br/&gt;5. A pile of devils!&lt;br/&gt;6. So what did Nichiren do about problems?&lt;br/&gt;7. What happens when the disciples stand up?&lt;br/&gt;8. An axiom of faith to be passed on not hidden.&lt;br/&gt;9. Thats what friends are for!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;It is a long show and we pull no bones about challenging the negativity that meets us fist for fist when we want to create change in our lives and&lt;br/&gt;the world around us!&lt;br/&gt;Picking the music for tonights show was a challenge too! Our great friend Vittoria Conn is preparing a final release mix for her new song Turnaround but we werent able to get to it in time for the recording! Never mind! We'll do our best to get it to you next time!&amp;nbsp; However, we have some really appropriate music from the &lt;a href="http://music.podshow.com/"&gt;Podsafe Music Network&lt;/a&gt;. We play 'I would Love' by &lt;a href="http://music.podshow.com/music/listeners/artistdetails.php?BandHash=dd2b595079fac48d4706a4e4f683bb36"&gt;Lee Coulter&lt;/a&gt; and 'Into the Groove' from the one and only &lt;a href="http://music.podshow.com/music/listeners/artistdetails.php?BandHash=ccfa9e635455c12ca7c2f363fbd02f26"&gt;Ziggy Marley&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;br/&gt;Lots of shoutouts across the world tonight! Taplow Court Open Days and Live Arts Festival 2007 are upon us, Sundays from 27 May - 29 July, plus National Heritage Day on the 9th September. Its open from 2pm to 5.30pm and there is a wonderful exhibition - The Happiest Days of Their Lives? - Children through the Ages at Taplow and Beyond. Admission Free.&lt;br/&gt;Thank you for listening!&lt;br/&gt;If you have a question or an experience you would like to send us, write to karen(at)thejarretts.com or jason(at)thejarretts.com&lt;br/&gt;If you get a moment, and you would like to, we would really appreciate it if you could write us a review on ITunes. Have a great week!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="64928522" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/A_Buddhist_Podcast_-__Letter_to_the_Brothers.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:07:38</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Welcome to tonights show! Tonights lectures is about overcoming the negativity that rises up whenever we want to change the direction of our lives.Some soundbites...1. Are you the protagonist or are you in the audience?2. Problems are the exercise for...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>A Buddhist Podcast - On Attaining Buddhahood</title>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 20 May 2007 16:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/index.php?post_id=216671#</guid>
                    <link>http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/a_buddhist_podcast_on_attaining_buddhahood</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/695175"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img title="Casey and Quinn are getting married congratulations" src="http://www.abuddhistpodcast.com/q%26c.jpg" alt="Casey and Quinn are getting married congratulations" align="top" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Welcome to tonights show! The lecture tonight is based on SGI President Daisaku Ikeda&amp;rsquo;s lectures in 2006 on the letter writing by Nichiren Daishonin, 'On Attaining Buddhahood in this Lifetime'.&lt;br /&gt; The highlights include&lt;br /&gt; 1. 20 Years with Gohonzon&lt;br /&gt; 2. Two approaches for overcoming suffering&lt;br /&gt; 3. Religion is a privilege and not an obligation&lt;br /&gt; 4. Grasping the mystic truth&lt;br /&gt; 5. Daimoku of faith and Daimoku of action&lt;br /&gt; 6. Revealing Buddhahood just as you are&lt;br /&gt; 7. Three meanings of Myo&lt;br /&gt; 8. Is your life a  complete pain in the backside?&lt;br /&gt; 9. I am Nam-myoho-renge-kyo&lt;br /&gt; 10. I&amp;rsquo;ve been doing all these activities and not getting benefit!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Great experience from Larry Congdon of Buffalo!&lt;br /&gt; Music for tonights show comes from the &lt;a href="http://music.podshow.com/"&gt;Podsafe Music Network&lt;/a&gt;. We play Kind of Grey by &lt;a title="Link to Delaware on the PMN" href="http://music.podshow.com/music/listeners/artistdetails.php?BandHash=d22fb958d9aa01734582e88cd9053cbe"&gt;Delaware&lt;/a&gt; and Goodnight Kiss from &lt;a title="Link to Phil Ayoub on the PMN" href="http://music.podshow.com/music/listeners/artistdetails.php?BandHash=8aa8aa088d2e9f70b265936ed280d5f3"&gt;Phil Ayoub&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt; We forgot to say but will remember next time&amp;hellip; the wonderful Quinn Hunter and Casey McGonigle are going to get married and they are the artwork for this weeks show! Congratulations!&lt;br /&gt; Roxanne Rae has some great &lt;a href="http://www.roxannerae.com/pdf/transforming.pdf"&gt;articles on anger&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt; And Celine Dufay is appearing in &lt;a href="http://www.kcl.ac.uk/french"&gt;Leocadia&lt;/a&gt; at Kings College London, Dates are Wed 30th Thurs 31st and Friday 1st June 7pm performances. Booking is available by the french dept- see more info from &lt;a href="http://kcl.facebook.com/group.php?gid=2340419774"&gt;facebook&lt;/a&gt;. Email: &lt;a href="mailto:kclfrenchplay@yahoo.co.uk"&gt;kclfrenchplay@yahoo.co.uk&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Thank you for listening!&lt;br /&gt; If you have a question or an experience you would like to send us, write to karen@thejarretts.com or jason@thejarretts.com&lt;br /&gt; If you get a moment, and you would like to, we would really appreciate it if you could write us a review on ITunes. Have a great week!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="63542469" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/A_Buddhist_Podcast_-_On_Attaining_Buddhahood.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:06:11</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Welcome to tonights show! The lecture tonight is based on SGI President Daisaku Ikeda&amp;rsquo;s lectures in 2006 on the letter writing by Nichiren Daishonin, 'On Attaining Buddhahood in this Lifetime'. The highlights include 1. 20 Years with Gohonzon 2....</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>A Buddhist Podcast - Three Kinds of Treasure Part 2</title>
                    <pubDate>Sat, 07 Apr 2007 23:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/index.php?post_id=201147#</guid>
                    <link>http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/A_Buddhist_Podcast_-_Three_Kinds_of_Treasure_Part_2.mp3</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/695174"/>
                    <description>Welcome to tonights show, the second half of the lecture on the letter from Nichiren Daishonin to Shijo Kingo, &lt;a href="http://www.sgilibrary.org/view.php?page=848"&gt;The Three Kinds of Treasure&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;Picking up from &lt;a href="http://media.libsyn.com/media/abuddhistpodcast/A_Buddhist_Podcast_-_Three_Kinds_of_Treasure_-_Part_1.mp3"&gt;Part 1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Where does the Master/Disciple relationship come from?&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Daisaku Ikeda&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;I would rather go to hell with you&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Complaining changes nothing&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Its rare to be born a human being&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Gain the trust of your community&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Three Kinds of Treasure&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Cherish the vow to work for human happiness&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Striving&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;
Music for tonights show comes from the &lt;a href="http://"&gt;Podsafe Music Network&lt;/a&gt;. We play Building Our Own Future by &lt;a href="http://music.podshow.com/music/producers/producerLibrary/artistdetails.php?BandHash=c223ff0affc3956f4744c87e59879b05"&gt;Howard Jones&lt;/a&gt; and Inside of Me by &lt;a href="http://music.podshow.com/music/producers/producerLibrary/artistdetails.php?BandHash=744fc46782e5166e55479adb6a4c7938"&gt;Ivy League&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br/&gt;If you have a question or an experience you would like to send us, write to karen@thejarretts.com or jason@thejarretts.com&lt;br/&gt;If you get a moment, and you would like to, we would really appreciate it if you could write us a review on ITunes. Have a great week!&lt;br type="_moz"/&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="63999207" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/A_Buddhist_Podcast_-_Three_Kinds_of_Treasure_Part_2.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:06:39</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Welcome to tonights show, the second half of the lecture on the letter from Nichiren Daishonin to Shijo Kingo, The Three Kinds of TreasurePicking up from Part 1Where does the Master/Disciple relationship come from?Daisaku IkedaI would rather go to...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>A Buddhist Podcast - Eileens lecture on Earthly Desires are Enlightenment</title>
                    <pubDate>Sat, 10 Mar 2007 23:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/index.php?post_id=190887#</guid>
                    <link>http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/a_buddhist_podcast_eileens_lecture_on_earthly_desires_are_enlightenment</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/695173"/>
                    <description>Tonights show is so full we had to get it out! With a wonderful lecture by Eileen Beckmann on Earthly Desires are Enlightenment, shoutouts and an experience from Matt McMillan. &lt;br/&gt;We have music from &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Sandie_Shaw"&gt;Sandie Shaw&lt;/a&gt;, a 60th Birthday mix of &amp;quot;&lt;a href="http://www.sandieshaw.com/"&gt;A Puppet on a String&amp;quot;&lt;/a&gt;. Also, thanks to Promonet, we are able to play Black Labs track, &amp;quot;Mine Again&amp;quot;, if you like the track buy it from &lt;a href="http://phobos.apple.com/WebObjects/MZStore.woa/wa/viewAlbum?playlistId=210761472&amp;s=143444&amp;i=210761474"&gt;ITunes&lt;/a&gt; on March 22nd as part of the &lt;a href="http://www.bumrushthecharts.com/"&gt;Bumrush the Charts&lt;/a&gt; campaign!&lt;br/&gt;Thank you so much for downloading the show, for your emails and for supporting the show.&lt;br/&gt;Don't worry we will get Part 2 of The Three Kinds of Treasure out in the next couple of weeks, in the mean time, take care, stand tall and have a great week!&lt;br/&gt;Email us with questions, feedback or experiences!&lt;br/&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="64795663" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/A_Buddhist_Podcast_-_Earthly_Desires.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:07:29</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Tonights show is so full we had to get it out! With a wonderful lecture by Eileen Beckmann on Earthly Desires are Enlightenment, shoutouts and an experience from Matt McMillan. We have music from Sandie Shaw, a 60th Birthday mix of &amp;quot;A Puppet on a...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>A Buddhist Podcast - Three Kinds of Treasure Part 1</title>
                    <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2007 01:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/index.php?post_id=185108#</guid>
                    <link>http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/a_buddhist_podcast_three_kinds_of_treasure_part_1</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/695172"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;So we are back, life has been very busy indeed!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And tonights talk is based on the Gosho, &lt;a href="http://www.sgilibrary.org/view.php?page=835&amp;q=The%20Hero%20of%20the%20World"&gt;&lt;a href="http://http://www.sgi-usa.org/buddhism/library/Nichiren/Gosho/3KindsTreasure.htm"&gt;Three Kinds of Treasure&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Lighthouses&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;What is my purpose in life?&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Master and Disciple&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Our struggle&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Winning where we are right now&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Cliffhanger&lt;br type="_moz"/&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tonights music comes from the &lt;a href="http://www.abuddhistpodcast.com/"&gt;Podsafe Music Network&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;a href="http://http://music.podshow.com/music/producers/producerLibrary/artistdetails.php?BandHash=fabc7825814ef11f2661a819697f975a"&gt;Vittoria Conn&lt;/a&gt; sings Mirror and &lt;a href="http://music.podshow.com/music/producers/producerLibrary/artistdetails.php?BandHash=835a96cfbeeff69de8100818165ccfba"&gt;Black Lab&lt;/a&gt; sing us out with Broken Heart. Thank you for listening, have a terrific week&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yorkshire Tea came from the wonderful &lt;a href="http://www.yorkshiretea.co.uk/"&gt;Bettys &amp;amp; Taylors of Harrogate&lt;/a&gt; and while you are making a cuppa go and check out the &lt;a href="http://www.bumrushthecharts.com"&gt;Bum Rush the Charts campaign&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="72298679" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/A_Buddhist_Podcast_-_Three_Kinds_of_Treasure_-_Part_1.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:15:18</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>So we are back, life has been very busy indeed!
And tonights talk is based on the Gosho, Three Kinds of Treasure

LighthousesWhat is my purpose in life?Master and DiscipleOur struggleWinning where we are right nowCliffhanger

Tonights music comes...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>A Buddhist Podcast - The Hero of the World</title>
                    <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2007 01:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/index.php?post_id=173783#</guid>
                    <link>http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/A_Buddhist_Podcast_-_The_Hero_of_the_World.mp3</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/695171"/>
                    <description>Happy New Year!&lt;br/&gt;Tonights talk is based on the Gosho, &lt;a href="http://www.sgilibrary.org/view.php?page=835&amp;q=The%20Hero%20of%20the%20World"&gt;The Hero of the World&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;Shijo Kingo&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Is it daytime yet?&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Riding the waves of life&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Victory or defeat is a matter of the heart&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Buddhism is reason&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Daisaku Ikeda&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The fight of our lives&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;
Tonights music comes from the &lt;a href="http://www.abuddhistpodcast.com/"&gt;Podsafe Music Network&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;nbsp; &lt;a href="http://music.podshow.com/music/producers/producerLibrary/artistdetails.php?BandHash=3b32a7f188afce82403a2745ccdeda25"&gt;Eoghan Colghan&lt;/a&gt; sings Planetary Woman and &lt;a href="http://music.podshow.com/music/producers/producerLibrary/artistdetails.php?BandHash=dec31db79fb9b68bd5b9f6bf80e8d38c"&gt;Move&lt;/a&gt; sing us out with Leave Your Problems. Yorkshire Tea came from the wonderful &lt;a href="http://www.yorkshiretea.co.uk"&gt;Bettys &amp;amp; Taylors of Harrogate&lt;/a&gt; and while you are making a cuppa you should have a mosey on over to &lt;a href="http://www.LorenzFineArt.net"&gt;Heidi Lorenz art gallery&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br/&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="56989571" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/A_Buddhist_Podcast_-_The_Hero_of_the_World.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>59:21</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Happy New Year!Tonights talk is based on the Gosho, The Hero of the WorldShijo KingoIs it daytime yet?Riding the waves of lifeVictory or defeat is a matter of the heartBuddhism is reasonDaisaku IkedaThe fight of our lives
Tonights music comes from...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>A Buddhist Podcast - Happiness in this World</title>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2006 23:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/index.php?post_id=162460#</guid>
                    <link>http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/abp24_Happiness_in_this_world.mp3</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/695170"/>
                    <description>Tonights lecture is based on the gosho, Happiness in this World. Some of the headings include:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;Why we practice Faith&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Opening the door to our Buddha wisdom&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Snakes in the cupboard&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Tatsunokuchi - walking the talk&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Mutual possession of the ten worlds&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;My friend Jack&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;If you want a drink, stay at home with your wife&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Strenthen your faith more than ever&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;
Oh, new one, book review! The book we reviewed tonight was &lt;a href="http://www.amazon.com/Quest-Global-Peace-Rotblat-Nuclear/dp/1845112792/sr=8-1/qid=1166399727/ref=pd_bbs_sr_1/102-5153927-6237751?ie=UTF8&amp;s=books"&gt;A Quest for Global Peace&lt;/a&gt; by Joseph Rotblat &amp;amp; Daisaku Ikeda. The book was published by I.B. Tauris in 2007 and the ISBN numbers we have are ISBN 978-1-84511-279-0 and ISBN 1-84511-279-2.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Music from tonights show comes from the &lt;a href="http://"&gt;Podsafe Music Network&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;a href="http://music.podshow.com/music/producers/producerLibrary/artistdetails.php?BandHash=5032570f7e7ea6adffd90058e3628da8"&gt;Stavia&lt;/a&gt; sings Lucky Day and the wonderful &lt;a href="http://music.podshow.com/music/producers/producerLibrary/artistdetails.php?BandHash=fabc7825814ef11f2661a819697f975a"&gt;Vittoria Conn&lt;/a&gt; sings a great christmas number, Merry Christmas Angel. And three anonymous young women sing, on behalf of all the young women who sang at the recent UK District Leaders Training Course at Trets, a poem by President Ikeda.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Peace and Goodwill to everyone!&lt;br type="_moz"/&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="66175745" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/abp24_Happiness_in_this_world.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:08:55</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Tonights lecture is based on the gosho, Happiness in this World. Some of the headings include:Why we practice FaithOpening the door to our Buddha wisdomSnakes in the cupboardTatsunokuchi - walking the talkMutual possession of the ten worldsMy friend...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>A Buddhist Podcast - Eileens Lecture</title>
                    <pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2006 09:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/index.php?post_id=155942#</guid>
                    <link>http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/a_buddhist_podcast_eileens_lecture</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/695169"/>
                    <description>Welcome to tonights show!&lt;br/&gt;
Tonights lecture is called, The Vow and it is given by our guest
lecturer Eileen Beckmann! The women of the SGI are so incredible! I
really hope this is the start of many lectures! We are so grateful to
Eileen, thank you so much.&lt;br/&gt;
Music tonights is from Geoff Smith and Matthew Ebel. &lt;a href="http://music.podshow.com/music/producers/producerLibrary/artistdetails.php?BandHash=91f6bc9ba66421768cc215f33ad693b7" mce_href="http://music.podshow.com/music/producers/producerLibrary/artistdetails.php?BandHash=91f6bc9ba66421768cc215f33ad693b7" title="Geoff Smith on the PMN"&gt;Geoff&lt;/a&gt; sings Some Christmas Hugging which you can find at either &lt;a href="http://www.thegeoffsmith.com/" mce_href="http://www.thegeoffsmith.com" title="Geoffs Home page"&gt;thegeoffsmith.com&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href="http://music.podshow.com/" mce_href="http://music.podshow.com" title="Podsafe Music Network"&gt;music.podshow.com&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;a href="http://music.podshow.com/music/producers/producerLibrary/artistdetails.php?BandHash=280202729dad1ad3a780a4d20afbe39b" mce_href="http://music.podshow.com/music/producers/producerLibrary/artistdetails.php?BandHash=280202729dad1ad3a780a4d20afbe39b" title="Matthew Ebel on the PMN"&gt;Matthew Ebel&lt;/a&gt; sings a song that definitely rips at your heart, Tennessee Never Cried and you can find Matthews music at &lt;a href="http://abuddhistpodcast.com/music.podshow.com" mce_href="http://abuddhistpodcast.com/music.podshow.com" title="Podsafe Music Network"&gt;music.podshow.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br/&gt;
Recent developments and improvements at Podshow mean that you can now
support these artists by buying the tracks if you like the music!&lt;br/&gt;
We've got shout outs from all over and a great experience from Andre de Wit from the Netherlands.&lt;br/&gt;
The cover art for tonights show is a photograph taken of Karen and I at &lt;a href="http://podcastconuk.btpodshow.com/" mce_href="http://podcastconuk.btpodshow.com/" title="PodcastconUK, video of Karen here somewhere!"&gt;PodcastconUK&lt;/a&gt; by&amp;nbsp; our great friend CC Chapman, the grand meister flash of &lt;a href="http://www.managingthegray.com/" mce_href="http://www.managingthegray.com/" title="Managing the Gray"&gt;Managing the Gray&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://www.accidenthash.com/" mce_href="http://www.accidenthash.com/" title="Accident Hash - Great Music Podcast"&gt;Accident Hash&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="http://u-turncafewp.podshow.com/" mce_href="http://u-turncafewp.podshow.com/" title="U-Turn Cafe"&gt;U-Turn Cafe&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;br/&gt;
Have a great week!&lt;br/&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="59732207" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/abp23_-_Eileens_Lecture.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:02:13</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Welcome to tonights show!
Tonights lecture is called, The Vow and it is given by our guest
lecturer Eileen Beckmann! The women of the SGI are so incredible! I
really hope this is the start of many lectures! We are so grateful to
Eileen, thank you...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>A Buddhist Podcast - Experiences and Fire Alarms</title>
                    <pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2006 23:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/index.php?post_id=150651#</guid>
                    <link>http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/a_buddhist_podcast_experiences_and_fire_alarms</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/695168"/>
                    <description>Well things have been mad busy! On tonights show we have two amazing experiences from Mens Division members in Los Angeles and India!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;div style="margin-left: 40px;"&gt;Life Poem - Daisaku Ikeda&lt;br/&gt;Pawan Desais experience&lt;br/&gt;Matt Macmillans experience&lt;br/&gt;The fire alarm&lt;br/&gt;And Karen is back with a vengeance, with her Shout Outs!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Music tonight is from the Podsafe Music Network at &lt;a href="http://music.podshow.com"&gt;music.podshow.com&lt;/a&gt; and comes from the very talented &lt;a href="http://music.podshow.com/music/producers/producerLibrary/artistdetails.php?BandHash=91f6bc9ba66421768cc215f33ad693b7"&gt;Geoff Smith&lt;/a&gt; singing Take Me Back&amp;nbsp; and the &lt;a href="http://music.podshow.com/music/producers/producerLibrary/artistdetails.php?BandHash=c00e4235450a33d751ce365c733db216"&gt;Supersuckers&lt;/a&gt; singing Some People Say!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;New line of lectures on their way to see us into our second year!&lt;br/&gt;Comments, ideas, experiences et al, we'd love to hear from you, drop us a line at &lt;a href="http://"&gt;karen@thejarretts.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Have a great and wonderful week!</description>
                    <enclosure length="45491808" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/abp22_Experiences_nov.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>47:23</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Well things have been mad busy! On tonights show we have two amazing experiences from Mens Division members in Los Angeles and India!Life Poem - Daisaku IkedaPawan Desais experienceMatt Macmillans experienceThe fire alarmAnd Karen is back with a...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>A Buddhist Podcast - The Dragon Gate</title>
                    <pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2006 04:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/index.php?post_id=139792#</guid>
                    <link>http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/a_buddhist_podcast_the_dragon_gate</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/695167"/>
                    <description>&amp;nbsp;Well! Jason is back from the &lt;a href="http://www.portablemediaexpo.com/"&gt;Podcast Expo&lt;/a&gt; in Ontario, California and the mission North to meet Donna and Dash in &lt;a href="http://www.cityofsacramento.org/"&gt;Sacramento&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;br/&gt;Tonight, the lecture is on the letter Nichiren Daishonin wrote to Nanjo Tokimitsu, &lt;a href="http://sgi-usa.org/buddhism/library/Nichiren/wnd/concord/pages.view/1002.html"&gt;The Dragon Gate gosho&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br/&gt;Children are well, life is mad busy and tonight we talk about;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;1. Nanjo Tokimitsu&lt;br/&gt;2. Living with a sense of purpose&lt;br/&gt;3. Shariputra versus Bodhisattva Never Disparaging&lt;br/&gt;4. Get your head out of the trenches!&lt;br/&gt;5. With my deep respect!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Shoutouts to my friend Matt McMillan, the crew at &lt;a href="http://www.jazzfly.co.uk"&gt;Jazzfly&lt;/a&gt;, my new friends &lt;a href="http://www.managingthegray.com"&gt;CC Chapman&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="http://www.thegeoffsmith.com"&gt;Geoff Smith&lt;/a&gt;! The amazing &lt;a href="http://digitalexperiencepodcast.com/"&gt;Pam &amp;amp; Lance&lt;/a&gt; Heath, Ewan Spence, Linda Mills, &lt;a href="http://musicianscooler.com/"&gt;David Jackson&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://www.coverville.com"&gt;Brian &amp;amp; Tina&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://www.brotherloverocks.com"&gt;Brother Love&lt;/a&gt;, Aaron Burcell, &lt;a href="http://rockandrollgeekwp.podshow.com/"&gt;Michael Butler&lt;/a&gt; and all the incredible people we met at the Podcast Expo&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The music from tonights show comes from the &lt;a href="http://music.podshow.com"&gt;Podsafe Music Network&lt;/a&gt; at music.podshow.com. The lecture was a little longer tonight so we only played one tune, the legendary &lt;a href="http://"&gt;Brother Love&lt;/a&gt;, singing Summertime! &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;If you would like to send us an experience, feedback, question or comment, drop us a line at &lt;a href="mailto:karen@thejarretts.com"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration: underline;"&gt;karen@thejarretts.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href="mailto:jason@thejarretts.com"&gt;jason@thejarretts.com&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.jimmygolding.com"&gt;Jimmy Golding&lt;/a&gt; is playing &lt;a href="http://http://www.jazzfly.co.uk"&gt;Jazzfly&lt;/a&gt; in London on Friday 13th! and yes Jason will be there! If you are in London, get down to Trebovir Road in Earls Court and check out &lt;a href="http://www.jazzfly.co.uk"&gt;Jazzfly&lt;/a&gt;. Great people, great music, human happiness in action.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Deepest thanks to Dash and Donna for such a wonderful stay. Jason is gutted he lost the intro!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Have a great week!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Ohâ�¦nearly forgot, they donâ��t sponsor us but they are really cool, they are the &lt;a href="http://www.ethicalsuperstore.com"&gt;ethicalsuperstore.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br type="_moz"/&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="60474593" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/A_Buddhist_Podcast_-The_Dragon_Gate.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:02:59</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords>gate,dragon,buddhism,buddhist,buddha,purpose,soka,gakkai,nichiren,nanjo,tokimitsu,nikko,shonin,atsuhara,pme06</itunes:keywords>
                    <itunes:subtitle>The Dragon Gate</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>A Buddhist Podcast - Nine Consciousnesses</title>
                    <pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2006 22:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/index.php?post_id=131033#</guid>
                    <link>http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/a_buddhist_podcast_nine_consciousnesses</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/695166"/>
                    <description>Tonights we talk about the Nine Consciousnesses in the midst of a bout
of colds, sneezes and coughs that have enveloped the house this week!
We talk about;&lt;br/&gt;

&lt;br/&gt;

1. 5 senses&lt;br/&gt;

2. Trapped in the cage of our 7th Consciousness&lt;br/&gt;

3. Karmic River&lt;br/&gt;

4. Palace of the Ninth Consciousness&lt;br/&gt;

5. Starlit Hawaii&lt;br/&gt;

&lt;br/&gt;

Shoutouts to everyone from Gibbo in LA to Mike Hellier touring Europe!
Selsted Primary School get&amp;nbsp; reprieve and Vittoria offers an experience
about chanting for her mothers situation.&lt;br/&gt;

&lt;br/&gt;

As usual music from tonights show comes from the Podsafe Music Network at &lt;a href="http://music.podshow.com/"&gt;music.podshow.com&lt;/a&gt;. We play &lt;a href="http://music.podshow.com/music/producers/producerLibrary/artistdetails.php?BandHash=5538385ac96aa74fdbe73f2cc4df6a93"&gt;Dave Pottz&lt;/a&gt; song, $12.99 and we close with the wonderful children of &lt;a href="http://music.podshow.com/music/producers/producerLibrary/artistdetails.php?BandHash=96b439ff757e79c8df631087cd2e3af4"&gt;Selsted Church of England Primary School&lt;/a&gt; singing, Save Our School, because they did save it!&lt;br/&gt;

&lt;br/&gt;

If you would like to send us an experience, feedback, question or comment, drop us a line at &lt;a href="mailto:karen@thejarretts.com"&gt;karen@thejarretts.com&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href="mailto:jason@thejarretts.com"&gt;jason@thejarretts.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;

&lt;br/&gt;

Oh...and if your in London and its Friday night and your thinking, where should we go? Go down to Earls Court and check out &lt;a href="http://www.myspace.com/jazzfly"&gt;Jazzfly&lt;/a&gt; at My Place Great people, great music, kosen rufu in action.&lt;br/&gt;

&lt;br/&gt;

Have a great week!&lt;br/&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="49543018" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/abp20_-_Nine_Consciousnesses.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>51:36</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Tonights we talk about the Nine Consciousnesses in the midst of a bout
of colds, sneezes and coughs that have enveloped the house this week!
We talk about;



1. 5 senses

2. Trapped in the cage of our 7th Consciousness

3. Karmic...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>A Buddhist Podcast - Correct Teaching</title>
                    <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2006 22:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/index.php?post_id=126118#</guid>
                    <link>http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/a_buddhist_podcast_correct_teaching</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/695165"/>
                    <description>Tonights show returns with a talk on the correct teaching and includes:&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;br/&gt;
&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 1. 3 Proofs&lt;br/&gt;
&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 2. If you wish to free yourself...&lt;br/&gt;
&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 3. How do I percieve the mystic Truth&lt;br/&gt;
&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 4. T'ien T'ai&lt;br/&gt;
&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 5. Potted early history of Nichiren Daishonin&lt;br/&gt;
&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 6. Meaning of Nam Myoho Renge Kyo&lt;br/&gt;
&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 7. Our mission should we choose to accept it...&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;br/&gt;
Karens voice gets better and better. More shoutouts. Happy Birthday to
Dash. Congratulations to Rosie Miles! Great Question - Do you have to
be a vegetarian to practice Buddhism? (I hope not...or I am in trouble)&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;br/&gt;
Music from tonights show comes from the &lt;a href="http://music.podshow.com/" mce_href="http://music.podshow.com" target="_blank"&gt;Podsafe Music Network&lt;/a&gt; at music.podshow.com. We play &lt;a href="http://music.podshow.com/music/producers/producerLibrary/artistdetails.php?BandHash=a892daf89e5efee9bd4705bbf8c092fc" mce_href="http://music.podshow.com/music/producers/producerLibrary/artistdetails.php?BandHash=a892daf89e5efee9bd4705bbf8c092fc" target="_blank"&gt;Adrina Thorpe&lt;/a&gt;'s amazing song is called Fly Fly Fly and we also played, the acoustic version of See the Sun from &lt;a href="http://music.podshow.com/music/producers/producerLibrary/artistdetails.php?BandHash=835a96cfbeeff69de8100818165ccfba" mce_href="http://music.podshow.com/music/producers/producerLibrary/artistdetails.php?BandHash=835a96cfbeeff69de8100818165ccfba" target="_blank"&gt;Black Lab&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
Have a wonderful week! &lt;br/&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="46009633" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/abp19_-_Correct_teachings.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>47:55</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Tonights show returns with a talk on the correct teaching and includes:

&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 1. 3 Proofs
&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 2. If you wish to free yourself...
&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 3. How do I percieve the mystic Truth
&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 4. T'ien T'ai
&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 5....</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>A Buddhist Podcast - Making a Great Vow</title>
                    <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2006 23:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/index.php?post_id=117001#</guid>
                    <link>http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/a_buddhist_podcast_making_a_great_vow</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/695164"/>
                    <description>Tonights show begins with a talk on a great vow and includes:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;Faith and courage&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Original desire of the Buddha&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Deeper the roots&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;US troops at Gatwick&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Now thats what I call a great vow&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;
Karen has some great shownotes and reads an experience from Henry Leong from Singapore, Shout outs to everyone and the challenges facing &lt;a href="http://www.sokagakkai-france.asso.fr/"&gt;SGI France&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Music from tonights show comes from Natives of the New Dawn, their song is called Good Day and you can get it from the Podsafe Music Network. We also played, Building our own Future with kind permission from Howard Jones. &lt;a href="http://www.howardjones.com/"&gt;Howard has a great album called Revolution of the Heart&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Have a wonderful week!&lt;br type="_moz"/&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="59016911" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/abp18_-_Great_Vow.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:01:28</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Tonights show begins with a talk on a great vow and includes:Faith and courageOriginal desire of the BuddhaDeeper the rootsUS troops at GatwickNow thats what I call a great vow
Karen has some great shownotes and reads an experience from Henry Leong...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>A Buddhist Podcast - Lotus Sutra Chapter 2 Part 8 - Why we recite the ten factors 3 times!</title>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2006 23:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/index.php?post_id=110811#</guid>
                    <link>http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/a_buddhist_podcast_lotus_sutra_chapter_2_part_8_why_we_recite_the_ten_factors_3_times_</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/695163"/>
                    <description>Tonights show closes our series of talks on Chapter 2 of the Lotus Sutra, the part we recite in Gongyo. tonights lectures covers: &lt;br/&gt;&lt;div style="margin-left: 40px;"&gt;A summary of everything so far;&lt;br/&gt;Why we recite the ten factors three times in Gongyo;&lt;br/&gt;The middle way;&lt;br/&gt;Buddhism in daily life; &lt;br/&gt;Letting go of our lesser self. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;The Music from tonights show comes from &lt;a href="http://music.podshow.com/music/producers/producerLibrary/artistdetails.php?BandHash=fabc7825814ef11f2661a819697f975a"&gt;Vittoria Conn who performs her song, &amp;quot;Mirror&amp;quot;&lt;/a&gt; and the &lt;a href="http://music.podshow.com/music/listeners/artistdetails.php?BandHash=96b439ff757e79c8df631087cd2e3af4"&gt;Church of England Selsted Primary School who sing Save our School&lt;/a&gt; - &lt;a href="http://www.sceps.uklinux.net/selsted.php"&gt;take a minute to go along to their website to see what they are doing to keep their school&lt;/a&gt;. Both songs can be bought from the Podsafe Music Network at music.podshow.com&lt;br/&gt;Special thanks to &lt;a href="http://www.sant-media.co.uk/"&gt;Steve Sant&lt;/a&gt; for his great support and the wonderful artwork he has let us use for tonights show.&lt;br/&gt;Vittoria is performing Mirror at Kosen Rufu Gongyo&amp;nbsp; at the White Plains Activity Centre in New York on August 6th at 9am!&lt;br type="_moz"/&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="56203834" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/A_Buddhist_Podcast_-_Chap2_Lotus_Sutra_Part_8_-_Why_do_we_do_the_last_bit_3_times_.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>58:32</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Tonights show closes our series of talks on Chapter 2 of the Lotus Sutra, the part we recite in Gongyo. tonights lectures covers: A summary of everything so far;Why we recite the ten factors three times in Gongyo;The middle way;Buddhism in daily life;...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>A Buddhist Podcast - Lotus Sutra Ch2 Part 7 - The True Entity of all Phenomena</title>
                    <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2006 01:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/index.php?post_id=106037#</guid>
                    <link>http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/a_buddhist_podcast_lotus_sutra_ch2_part_7_the_true_entity_of_all_phenomena</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/695162"/>
                    <description>So tonight we are back with our lectures on Chapter 2 of the Lotus Sutra. This show is about the most important part of Chapter 2, one of the most important parts of the Lotus Sutra, and includes:&lt;br/&gt;1. A summary of everything we have talked about so far, and;&lt;br/&gt;2. The true entity of all phenomena;&lt;br/&gt;3. The ten factors;&lt;br/&gt;4. The Gohonzon within us;&lt;br/&gt;5. Bathtubs and apples!&lt;br/&gt;Then we play some great music by &lt;a href="http://music.podshow.com/music/producers/producerLibrary/artistdetails.php?BandHash=cfa653041e758b4b37826c7a6231f734"&gt;Rebecca Haviland&lt;/a&gt; and the track is called What are you?&lt;br/&gt;We hear an incredible experience from Akenabah Begay, from the Navojo tribe of North America and the shout outs to everyone who wrote to us! And we can't forget the &lt;a href="http://www.sgi-norcal.org"&gt;Latino SGI event in Northern California&lt;/a&gt; on September 10th 2006 in San Francisco!&lt;br/&gt;The show closes out with Goodbye Southern Skies from &lt;a href="http://music.podshow.com/music/producers/producerLibrary/artistdetails.php?BandHash=f38b75da9eb0579bc494f5b4bb0c9359"&gt;David McMilllin&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Donâ��t forget, if you have an experience or feedback or just want to say hello, drop us a line at &lt;a href="mailto:jason@thejarretts.com"&gt;jason@thejarretts.com&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href="mailto:karen@thejarretts.com"&gt;karen@thejarretts.com&lt;/a&gt;. Thank you to everyone that writes an email or puts a comment on a website or ITunes, it is so encouraging to hear from you!&lt;br/&gt;Thank you to everyone for your support and encouragement. Have a truly fantastic Have a great week! &lt;br/&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="60779345" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/abp16_-_Chap2_Lotus_Sutra_Part_7_-_The_True_Entity_of_Life.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:03:18</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>So tonight we are back with our lectures on Chapter 2 of the Lotus Sutra. This show is about the most important part of Chapter 2, one of the most important parts of the Lotus Sutra, and includes:1. A summary of everything we have talked about so far,...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>A Buddhist Podcast - Heritage of the Ultimate Law of Life</title>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2006 23:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/index.php?post_id=99773#</guid>
                    <link>http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/abp15_-_11th_June_06_Heritage_of_the_Law.mp3</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/695161"/>
                    <description>Yes... its the mother of cliffhangers!&lt;br/&gt;Tonight we are taking a brief gap in our series of Lectures on the Lotus Sutra, just for this week! Instead, we are going to study an extract from a letter the Daishonin wrote to Sairen-Bo. The letter is called &lt;a href="http://sgi-usa.org/buddhism/library/Nichiren/wnd/concord/pages.view/216.html"&gt;The Heritage of the Ultimate Law of Life&lt;/a&gt;. Tonight we talk about:&lt;br/&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 1.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Each moment is the last moment of our lives&lt;br/&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 2.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 1000 Buddhas&lt;br/&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; 3.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Many in body but one in mind&lt;br/&gt;For the music on tonights show I am grateful to &lt;a href="http://soccershout.com"&gt;Soccershout&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://www.bitjobs.net/"&gt;Bitjobs for the Masses&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://globaldom.libsyn.com"&gt;Green Dragon&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://"&gt;Tartan Podcast&lt;/a&gt; and of course &lt;a href="http://www.threefromleith.com/"&gt;Three from Leith&lt;/a&gt;. All of these great podcasters helped me source the music this week which comes from the &lt;a href="http://music.podshow.com/"&gt;Podsafe Music Network&lt;/a&gt; and was...&lt;a href="http://music.podshow.com/music/producers/producerLibrary/artistdetails.php?BandHash=53741ff06cba0cd4db099bf54ed39901"&gt;Death Cab for Cutie&lt;/a&gt; singing Title and Registration and &lt;a href="http://"&gt;Team Salt&lt;/a&gt; with Roundabouts.&lt;br/&gt;We are already preparing the 7th and final lecture on Chapter 2 of the Lotus Sutra for the next show! Don't forget, if you have an experience or feedback or just want to say hello, drop us a line at &lt;a href="http://"&gt;jason@thejarretts.com&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href="mailto:karen@thejarretts.com"&gt;karen@thejarretts.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br/&gt;Thank you to everyone for your support and encouragement. Have a truly fantastic week!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="63975131" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/abp15_-_11th_June_06_Heritage_of_the_Law.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:06:38</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Yes... its the mother of cliffhangers!Tonight we are taking a brief gap in our series of Lectures on the Lotus Sutra, just for this week! Instead, we are going to study an extract from a letter the Daishonin wrote to Sairen-Bo. The letter is called...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>A Buddhist Podcast - Lotus Sutra Ch2 Part 6 Soft and gentle words</title>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2006 23:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/index.php?post_id=95289#</guid>
                    <link>http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/abp14_-_LS_Ch2_Pt6_28th_May_06.mp3</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/695160"/>
                    <description>Tonights show includes:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;The 6th Lecture on the Hopen Pon or Chapter 2 of the Lotus Sutra, more on the meaning of Gongyo. Soft and gentle words, parents and paradigms, no more shingles and flushing out karma;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The music on tonights show was firstly Wake Up by the &lt;a href="http://music.podshow.com/music/producers/producerLibrary/artistdetails.php?BandHash=8aac3f3c8d5e16d22fa774a2fc22e66e"&gt;Butterfly Catchers&lt;/a&gt; and finally Booty Voodoo from &lt;a href="http://music.podshow.com/music/producers/producerLibrary/artistdetails.php?BandHash=dd2b595079fac48d4706a4e4f683bb36"&gt;Lee Coulter&lt;/a&gt;. All music is from the &lt;a href="http://music.podshow.com"&gt;Podsafe Music Network&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;What is the information surrounding the 49th day after someone dies? Dispelling another priesthood cashcow.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;
Have a fantastic week!&lt;br/&gt;If you have an experience or feedback or just want to say hi, drop us a line at &lt;a href="mailto:jason@thejarretts.com"&gt;jason@thejarretts.com&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href="mailto:karen@thejarretts.com"&gt;karen@thejarretts.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br type="_moz"/&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="58626359" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/abp14_-_LS_Ch2_Pt6_28th_May_06.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:01:04</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Tonights show includes:The 6th Lecture on the Hopen Pon or Chapter 2 of the Lotus Sutra, more on the meaning of Gongyo. Soft and gentle words, parents and paradigms, no more shingles and flushing out karma;The music on tonights show was firstly Wake...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>A Buddhist Podcast - Lotus Sutra Ch2 Part 5 Immeasurable Mercy and Earth Charter</title>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2006 00:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/index.php?post_id=90482#</guid>
                    <link>http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/a_buddhist_podcast_lotus_sutra_ch2_part_5_immeasurable_mercy_and_earth_charter</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/695159"/>
                    <description>The moment I got back tonight from the &lt;a href="http://www.sgi-uk.org"&gt;SGI-UK&lt;/a&gt; Mens Division Leaders Course in Coventry and Karen said, OK! Lets do the podcast!&lt;br/&gt;So...tonights show includes:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;Lecture on Part 5 on the Hopen Pon or Chapter 2 of the Lotus Sutra, covering a refresher on what we have done so far, immeasurable mercy, unlimited eloquence and fearlessness;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Music from &lt;a href="http://music.podshow.com/music/producers/producerLibrary/artistdetails.php?BandHash=44b9a96912540e728cbe1a14a94ba0cc"&gt;Jimmy Golding'&lt;/a&gt;s album, Be Good, Be Bad, Be Mine. The songs we play tonight are excellent! Big Hearted Man and Can't Stop The Rain, from the Podsafe Music Network at &lt;a href="http://music.podshow.com/"&gt;music.podshow.com&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Karen talks &lt;a href="http://www.earthcharter.org/"&gt;Earth Charter&lt;/a&gt; and President Ikedas childrens books&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;
As usual you can send us feedback or comments to us at&lt;br/&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="mailto:jason@thejarretts.com"&gt;jason@thejarretts.com&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href="mailto:karen@thejarretts.com"&gt;karen@thejarretts.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Have a great week!&lt;br type="_moz"/&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="55832837" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/abp13_-_LS_Ch2_Pt5_14th_May_06.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>58:09</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>The moment I got back tonight from the SGI-UK Mens Division Leaders Course in Coventry and Karen said, OK! Lets do the podcast!So...tonights show includes:Lecture on Part 5 on the Hopen Pon or Chapter 2 of the Lotus Sutra, covering a refresher on what...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>A Buddhist Podcast - Part 4 of Chapter 2 Expedient Means &amp; Wisdom</title>
                    <pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2006 23:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/index.php?post_id=85328#</guid>
                    <link>http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/abp12_-_LS_Ch2_Pt4_29th_April_06.mp3</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/695158"/>
                    <description>Tonights lecture on Chapter 2 covers the phrase, Sho-i sha ga. Nyorai hoben. Chiken hara-mitsu. Kai i gu-soku! Thank you to my amazing Karen for making it possible and to the warm encouragement of Mr Johnny Hindes
Thank you to everybody for downloading the show.
The music tonight comes from Kevin Reeves and Bobby Gentry from music.podshow.com
Best wishes to everyone</description>
                    <enclosure length="57120234" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/abp12_-_LS_Ch2_Pt4_29th_April_06.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>59:30</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Tonights lecture on Chapter 2 covers the phrase, Sho-i sha ga. Nyorai hoben. Chiken hara-mitsu. Kai i gu-soku! Thank you to my amazing Karen for making it possible and to the warm encouragement of Mr Johnny Hindes
Thank you to everybody for...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>A Buddhist Podcast - Part 3 of Chapter 2 Expedient Means and Earthly Desires</title>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2006 00:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/index.php?post_id=80513#</guid>
                    <link>http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/abp11_-_LS_Ch2_Pt3_15th_April_06.mp3</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/695157"/>
                    <description>We have reversed the running order of the show tonight, study first, music, experience, question and answers! The study is the 3rd lecture in a series on the Hoben Pon or the 2nd Chapter of the Lotus Sutra. We hope you enjoy it. &lt;br/&gt;More music from the &lt;a href="http://www.podshow.com"&gt;Podsafe Music Network&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="63975428" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/abp11_-_LS_Ch2_Pt3_15th_April_06.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:06:38</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords>buddhism,buddhist,soka,gakkai,nichiren,kosen,rufu,gohonzon</itunes:keywords>
                    <itunes:subtitle>More from the kitchen table on Part 3, Chapter 2 of the Lotus Sutra</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Finally - A Buddhist Podcast Promo</title>
                    <pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2006 21:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/index.php?post_id=79169#</guid>
                    <link>http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/A_Buddhist_Podcast_Promo.mp3</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/695155"/>
                    <description>Finally&lt;/span&gt;, we have produced a promo! Let us know what you think. Thank you so much for subscribing to the show!&lt;/span&gt; Enjoy the rest of this week. Update on Lizzie Obard from John Marder, &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&amp;quot;Lizzie woke up this afternoon. She has been looking at people and seems to hear things. The physio says she can move her limbs. She isn't fitting despite not being on the really heavy anti-convolsants. She&amp;#160; will continue to be sedated tonight and we think that tomorrow they will aim to bring her round properly and have her breathing herself. This is all such fantastic news and shows a massive turnaround since the awful things we were hearing on Friday. Of course there is still a long way to go in getting Lizzie better but what we have seen shows what all that Daimoku can do. Thank you so much to everybody and lets please keep that Daimoku rota roaring on for the fortnight and see fantastic proof. Thank you so much.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&amp;#160;Jason and Karen&lt;br/&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="1063047" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/A_Buddhist_Podcast_Promo.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:06</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords>buddhism,buddhist,soka,gakkai,nichiren,kosen,rufu,gohonzon</itunes:keywords>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Promo</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>A Buddhist Podcast - Karen gets her own mic for Part 2 Chapter 2 Lotus Sutra</title>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/index.php?post_id=75956#</guid>
                    <link>http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/abp10_-_LS_Ch2_Pt2_2nd_April_2006.mp3</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/695154"/>
                    <description>Karen has her own microphone! Questions on Men and Women, differences between Nichiren Daishonins Buddhism and other forms of Buddhism and is chanting Nam Myoho Renge Kyo a meditation? The  lecture/study talk is on the second page of Gongyo, the second part of Chapter 2 of the Lotus Sutra. Getting harder not easier, this was a real challenge of confidence to see it through. We hope you enjoy it.
The show ends with &amp;quot;Panacea&amp;quot; from the Birthday Suit album by Bill from the Podsafe Music Network. If you like it, visit music.podshow.com. Podsafe Music Network is a great source of new music. Have a great week!</description>
                    <enclosure length="55333068" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/abp10_-_LS_Ch2_Pt2_2nd_April_2006.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>57:38</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords>buddhism,lotus,soka,gakkai,nichiren,sgi,kosen,rufu</itunes:keywords>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Around the kitchen table with Part 2, Chapter 2, The Lotus Sutra</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>A Buddhist Podcast - Chap 2, Lotus Sutra</title>
                    <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2006 23:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/index.php?post_id=70662#</guid>
                    <link>http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/ABP9_-_Lotus_Sutra_Ch2_Part_1.mp3</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/695153"/>
                    <description>Questions, questions! Tonights lecture is on the first page of Gongyo, the first part of Chapter 2 of the Lotus Sutra, "At that time...". This was enjoyable to put together. 
We close the show with great music from Matthew Ebel, "I know you're there", from the Podsafe Music Network. If you like it, visit music.podshow.com. Podsafe Music Network is a great source of new music. Have a great week!</description>
                    <enclosure length="55014546" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/ABP9_-_Lotus_Sutra_Ch2_Part_1.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>57:18</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Questions, questions! Tonights lecture is on the first page of Gongyo, the first part of Chapter 2 of the Lotus Sutra, "At that time...". This was enjoyable to put together. 
We close the show with great music from Matthew Ebel, "I know you're...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>A Buddhist Podcast - Q&amp;A and Chapter 1 of the Lotus Sutra</title>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2006 07:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/index.php?post_id=65553#</guid>
                    <link>http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/ABP8_-_Chapter_1_Lotus_Sutra.mp3</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/695152"/>
                    <description>Tonight we have changed the format slightly and have a Q&amp;A on some Buddhist basics, an experience and as a short lecture on Chapter 1 of the Lotus Sutra.
We finish the show with great music from Geoff Smith, "Not on the radio", from the Podshow. If you like it, visit music.podshow.com. Podsafe Music Network is a great source of new music.
Have a wonderful week!</description>
                    <enclosure length="52795172" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/ABP8_-_Chapter_1_Lotus_Sutra.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>54:59</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Tonight we have changed the format slightly and have a Q&amp;A on some Buddhist basics, an experience and as a short lecture on Chapter 1 of the Lotus Sutra.
We finish the show with great music from Geoff Smith, "Not on the radio", from the Podshow. If...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>A Buddhist Podcast</title>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2006 00:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/index.php?post_id=60033#</guid>
                    <link>http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/ABP7_-_Introduction_to_the_Lotus_Sutra.mp3</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/695151"/>
                    <description>A Buddhist Podcast - Introduction to the Lotus Sutra. This is an introductory lecture to the essence of the Buddha's teaching, the Lotus Sutra.</description>
                    <enclosure length="46603290" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/ABP7_-_Introduction_to_the_Lotus_Sutra.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>48:32</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Introduction to the Lotus Sutra</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>A Buddhist Podcast - Repaying Debts of Gratitude</title>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2006 00:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/index.php?post_id=50281#</guid>
                    <link>http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/ABP_4_-_Repaying_Debts_of_Gratitude.mp3</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/695150"/>
                    <description>-undefined-</description>
                    <enclosure length="30353495" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/ABP_4_-_Repaying_Debts_of_Gratitude.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>31:37</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>-undefined-</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>New Years Gosho</title>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2006 20:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/index.php?post_id=44727#</guid>
                    <link>http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/new_years_gosho</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/695149"/>
                    <description>Finally, after 13 misfires, 14th time lucky, overcoming seven kinds of Sansho Shima, the one with the New Years Gosho is out and up there! Happy New Year to everyone!</description>
                    <enclosure length="40996139" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/ABP_4_-_The_New_Years_Gosho.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>42:42</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Finally, after 13 misfires, 14th time lucky, overcoming seven kinds of Sansho Shima, the one with the New Years Gosho is out and up there! Happy New Year to everyone!</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>A Buddhist Podcast : The Action Man Lecture</title>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 04 Dec 2005 21:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/index.php?post_id=38272#</guid>
                    <link>http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/The_lecture_with_the_Action_Man.mp3</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/695148"/>
                    <description>Finally here the lecture I gave in Hospital which was recorded and played to the members the next night with an action man taking the microphone</description>
                    <enclosure length="48193215" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/The_lecture_with_the_Action_Man.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>50:12</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Finally here the lecture I gave in Hospital which was recorded and played to the members the next night with an action man taking the microphone</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>A Buddhist Podcast</title>
                    <pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2005 12:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">http://abuddhistpodcast.libsyn.com/index.php?post_id=36562#</guid>
                    <link>http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/The_Essentials_for_Attaining_for_Buddhahood.mp3</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/695147"/>
                    <description>Here is my notes on the Gosho, The Essentials for Attaining Buddhahood&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;a href="http://www.podshow.com/"&gt;  Podshow PDN &lt;/a&gt;  {podshow-d58633bd2f685d0c214a809169dc3271}</description>
                    <enclosure length="25807128" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/abuddhistpodcast/The_Essentials_for_Attaining_for_Buddhahood.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>26:52</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Here is my notes on the Gosho, The Essentials for Attaining Buddhahood
  Podshow PDN   {podshow-d58633bd2f685d0c214a809169dc3271}</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
            </channel>
        </rss>
    </httpclient:body>
</httpclient:response>