<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<httpclient:response xmlns:httpclient="http://exist-db.org/xquery/httpclient" statusCode="200">
    <httpclient:headers>
        <httpclient:header name="Content-Type" value="text/xml"/>
        <httpclient:header name="Last-Modified" value="Fri, 27 Aug 2010 09:48:37 GMT"/>
        <httpclient:header name="Accept-Ranges" value="bytes"/>
        <httpclient:header name="ETag" value="&#34;97a4565cd45cb1:0&#34;"/>
        <httpclient:header name="Server" value="Microsoft-IIS/7.0"/>
        <httpclient:header name="X-Powered-By" value="ASP.NET"/>
        <httpclient:header name="Date" value="Wed, 20 Aug 2014 08:53:15 GMT"/>
        <httpclient:header name="Content-Length" value="10963"/>
    </httpclient:headers>
    <httpclient:body mimetype="text/xml" type="xml">
        <rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" version="2.0">
            <channel>
                <title>Live At The Stand Comedy Club</title>
                <link>http://www.thestand.co.uk/podcast.aspx</link>
                <language>en-us</language>
                <copyright>℗ &amp; © 2010 The Stand Comedy Club</copyright>
                <itunes:subtitle>The Stand Comedy Club Podcasts</itunes:subtitle>
                <itunes:author>The Stand Comedy Club</itunes:author>
                <itunes:summary>Podcasts from The Stand Comedy Club featuring up and coming talent and big names on the comedy scene.</itunes:summary>
                <description>Podcasts from The Stand Comedy Club featuring up and coming talent and big names on the comedy scene. We've teamed up with Audible to give you FREE access to digital audiobooks from their expansive collection featuring live recordings by Frankie Boyle, Michael McIntyre, Lee Mack, Russell Brand and many more. Visit http://www.audible.co.uk/thestand to get them now!</description>
                <itunes:owner>
                    <itunes:name>The Stand Comedy Club</itunes:name>
                    <itunes:email>admin@thestand.co.uk</itunes:email>
                </itunes:owner>
                <itunes:image href="http://www.thestand.co.uk/images/acts100/standpodcast_large.jpg"/>
                <itunes:category text="Comedy"/>
                <itunes:category text="Arts"/>
                <itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>
                <item>
                    <title>Live at The Stand Comedy Club: Podcast 1</title>
                    <itunes:author>The Stand Comedy Club</itunes:author>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Featuring Tommy Tiernan, Andrew Maxwell, Webdy Wason, Benjamin Crellin and Patrick Moahan</itunes:subtitle>
                    <itunes:summary>Here it is at last! The very first podcast from the Stand Comedy Club.  This week, our host Julia Sutherland brings us some of the best bits recorded at The Magners Festival Club in Glasgow. There's amazing stand up and some revealing backstage chats with Tommy Tiernan, Andrew Maxwell, Wendy Wason, Benjamin Crellin and Patrick Monahan. It is a must listen for comedy fans everywhere. Don't forget to subscribe to the feed for future episodes.   Coming up on the next podcast - Fred MacAulay, Brendon Burns, Lucy Porter and Richard Herring!</itunes:summary>
                    <enclosure url="http://109.109.252.218/podcast/podcast1.mp3" length="25554314" type="audio/mpeg"/>
                    <guid>http://109.109.252.218/podcast/podcast1.mp3</guid>
                    <pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2010 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                    <itunes:duration>26:34</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords>The Stand, Comedy Club, Comedy, Tommy Tiernan, Andrew Maxwell, Webdy Wason, Benjamin Crellin and Patrick Moahan</itunes:keywords>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Live at The Stand Comedy Club: Podcast 2</title>
                    <itunes:author>The Stand Comedy Club</itunes:author>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Featuring Richard Herring, Brendon Burns, Miles Jupp, Fred MacAulay and Lucy Porter</itunes:subtitle>
                    <itunes:summary>Here's another great podcast from the Stand Comedy Club. This week, our host Richard Melvin brings us some more choice cuts from Richard Herring, Brendon Burns, Miles Jupp, Fred MacAulay and Lucy Porter, in converstaion and on stage at The Magners Festival Club in Glasgow. Coming up on the next podcast Robin Ince, Dara O'Briain, Kevin Bridges and Shappi Khorsandi.</itunes:summary>
                    <enclosure url="http://109.109.252.218/podcast/podcast2.mp3" length="17537861" type="audio/mpeg"/>
                    <guid>http://109.109.252.218/podcast/podcast2.mp3</guid>
                    <pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2010 03:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
                    <itunes:duration>18:13</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords>The Stand, Comedy Club, Comedy, Richard Herring, Brendon Burns, Miles Jupp, Fred MacAulay, Lucy Porter</itunes:keywords>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Live at The Stand Comedy Club: Podcast 3</title>
                    <itunes:author>The Stand Comedy Club</itunes:author>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Featuring Dara O'Briain, Shappi Korsandi, Robin Ince, Hannibal Burres and Davey See</itunes:subtitle>
                    <itunes:summary>Here is podcast number 3. This week our host, Richard Melvin introduces stand up and back stage chats with Dara O'Briain, Shappi Korsandi, Robin Ince, Saturday Night Live's Hannibal Burres and local boy Davey See.</itunes:summary>
                    <enclosure url="http://109.109.252.218/podcast/podcast3.mp3" length="21078016" type="audio/mpeg"/>
                    <guid>http://109.109.252.218/podcast/podcast3.mp3</guid>
                    <pubDate>Sat, 03 Apr 2010 03:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
                    <itunes:duration>21:54</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords>The Stand, Comedy Club, Comedy, Dara O'Briain, Shappi Korsandi, Robin Ince, Hannibal Burres, Davey See</itunes:keywords>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Live at The Stand Comedy Club: Podcast 4</title>
                    <itunes:author>The Stand Comedy Club</itunes:author>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Featuring Todd Barry, Hailey Boyle, Marc Marron, Rachel Feinstein, Jenna Friedman and Brian Scott McFadden.</itunes:subtitle>
                    <itunes:summary>Here is podcast number 4, The American Special.  This week our host, Richard Melvin introduces stand up and back stage chats with Todd Barry, Hailey Boyle, Marc Marron, Rachel Feinstein, Jenna Friedman and Brian Scott McFadden. Coming up next week, Lee Mack, Kevin Bridges, Craig Campbell and Mark Nelson.</itunes:summary>
                    <enclosure url="http://109.109.252.218/podcast/podcast4.mp3" length="19928613" type="audio/mpeg"/>
                    <guid>http://109.109.252.218/podcast/podcast4.mp3</guid>
                    <pubDate>Tue, 13 Apr 2010 03:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
                    <itunes:duration>20:42</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords>The Stand, Comedy Club, Comedy, Todd Barry, Hailey Boyle, Marc Marron, Rachel Feinstein, Jenna Friedman and Brian Scott McFadden.</itunes:keywords>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Live at The Stand Comedy Club: Podcast 5</title>
                    <itunes:author>The Stand Comedy Club</itunes:author>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Featuring Mark Nelson, Chris Forbes, Lee Mack, Kevin Bridges, Craig Campbell, Mike Wozniak and Simon Evans.</itunes:subtitle>
                    <itunes:summary>Podcast 5 includes more highlights from The Glasgow Comedy Festival, including Mark Nelson, Chris Forbes, Lee Mack, Kevin Bridges, Craig Campbell, Mike Wozniak and Simon Evans. Listen to the podcast to find out about how you can get some exclusive offers on tickets. This is the last podcast for a while but we will be back in August with a brand new series.</itunes:summary>
                    <enclosure url="http://109.109.252.218/podcast/podcast5.mp3" length="23959607" type="audio/mpeg"/>
                    <guid>http://109.109.252.218/podcast/podcast5.mp3</guid>
                    <pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2010 13:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
                    <itunes:duration>20:42</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords>The Stand, Comedy Club, Comedy, Mark Nelson, Chris Forbes, Lee Mack, Kevin Bridges, Craig Campbell, Mike Wozniak and Simon Evans</itunes:keywords>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Live at The Stand Comedy Club: Frankie Boyle and Stewart Lee</title>
                    <itunes:author>The Stand Comedy Club</itunes:author>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Featuring Frankie Boyle, Stewart Lee, Andy Zaltzman, John Moloney, Ava Vidal and Kevin Eldon.</itunes:subtitle>
                    <itunes:summary>Frankie Boyle, Stewart Lee, Andy Zaltzman, John Moloney, Ava Vidal and Kevin Eldon feature on the brand new Live At The Stand Comedy Club Podcast. There's loads of stand up comedy and a couple of backstage chats.  You can hear Frankie Boyle talking about his new TV show Tramadol Nights,  his thoughts on causing controversy and Mock The Week.</itunes:summary>
                    <enclosure url="http://109.109.252.218/podcast/podcast6.mp3" length="234165059" type="audio/mpeg"/>
                    <guid>http://109.109.252.218/podcast/podcast6.mp3</guid>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 09 Aug 2010 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                    <itunes:duration>23:41</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords>The Stand, Comedy Club, Comedy, Frankie Boyle, Stewart Lee, Andy Zaltzman, John Moloney, Ava Vidal, Kevin Eldon, Fringe, Festival 2010, Edinburgh Festival, Edinburgh Fringe, Mock the week, Tramadol Nights</itunes:keywords>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Live at The Stand Comedy Club: Sarah Millican and Phil Nichol</title>
                    <itunes:author>The Stand Comedy Club</itunes:author>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Featuring Sarah Millican, Phil Nichol, Lucy Porter, Pete Johansson and Vladimir McTavish.</itunes:subtitle>
                    <itunes:summary>Sarah Millican, Phil Nichol, Lucy Porter, Pete Johansson and Vladimir McTavish chat and perform for The Stand Comedy Club podcast.</itunes:summary>
                    <enclosure url="http://109.109.252.218/podcast/podcast7.mp3" length="27820611" type="audio/mpeg"/>
                    <guid>http://109.109.252.218/podcast/podcast7.mp3</guid>
                    <pubDate>Thu, 12 Aug 2010 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                    <itunes:duration>19:12</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords>The Stand, Comedy Club, Comedy, Sarah Millican, Phil Nichol, Lucy Porter, Pete Johansson, Vladimir McTavish, Fringe, Festival 2010, Edinburgh Festival, Edinburgh Fringe</itunes:keywords>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Live at The Stand Comedy Club: Josie Long, Caroline Rhea and Paul Sinha</title>
                    <itunes:author>The Stand Comedy Club</itunes:author>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Featuring Caroline Rhea, Josie Long and Keith Farnan chat to Bruce Devlin, with stand up from Carey Marx, Ian Coppinger and Paul Sinha.</itunes:subtitle>
                    <itunes:summary>Featuring Caroline Rhea, Josie Long and Keith Farnan chat to Bruce Devlin, with stand up from Carey Marx, Ian Coppinger and Paul Sinha.</itunes:summary>
                    <enclosure url="http://109.109.252.218/podcast/podcast8.mp3" length="25174381" type="audio/mpeg"/>
                    <guid>http://109.109.252.218/podcast/podcast8.mp3</guid>
                    <pubDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2010 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                    <itunes:duration>17:22</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords>The Stand, Comedy Club, Comedy, Caroline Rhea, Josie Long, Keith Farnan, Bruce Devlin, Carey Marx, Ian Coppinger, Paul Sinha, Festival 2010, Edinburgh Festival, Edinburgh Fringe</itunes:keywords>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Live at The Stand Comedy Club: Ardal O'Hanlon and Jim Jeffries</title>
                    <itunes:author>The Stand Comedy Club</itunes:author>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Featuring Jim Jeffries, Ardal O'Hanlon, Michael Fabbri and Tiffany Stevenson</itunes:subtitle>
                    <itunes:summary>Stand up comedy from Stand favourites Tiffany Stevenson and Michael Fabbri, more highlights from The Late Club featuring Ardal O'Hanlon, Costaki and David Whitney plus a very revealing interview with Jim Jeffries.</itunes:summary>
                    <enclosure url="http://109.109.252.218/podcast/podcast10.mp3" length="24736807" type="audio/mpeg"/>
                    <guid>http://109.109.252.218/podcast/podcast10.mp3</guid>
                    <pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2010 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                    <itunes:duration>17:14</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>Yes</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords>The Stand, Comedy Club, Comedy, Jim Jeffries, Ardal O'Hanlon, Michael Fabbri, Tiffany Stevenson Festival 2010, Edinburgh Festival, Edinburgh Fringe</itunes:keywords>
                </item>
            </channel>
        </rss>
    </httpclient:body>
</httpclient:response>