<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<httpclient:response xmlns:httpclient="http://exist-db.org/xquery/httpclient" statusCode="200">
    <httpclient:headers>
        <httpclient:header name="Server" value="Apache/2.2.22 (Ubuntu)"/>
        <httpclient:header name="X-Libsyn-Host" value="web-engine3.libsyn.com"/>
        <httpclient:header name="Vary" value="Accept-Encoding"/>
        <httpclient:header name="Content-Type" value="application/rss+xml"/>
        <httpclient:header name="last-modified" value="Tue, 19 Aug 2014 16:42:43 GMT"/>
        <httpclient:header name="Content-Length" value="133115"/>
        <httpclient:header name="Accept-Ranges" value="bytes"/>
        <httpclient:header name="Date" value="Wed, 20 Aug 2014 09:22:47 GMT"/>
        <httpclient:header name="X-Varnish" value="2177998339 2171639312"/>
        <httpclient:header name="Age" value="60539"/>
        <httpclient:header name="Via" value="1.1 varnish"/>
        <httpclient:header name="Connection" value="close"/>
        <httpclient:header name="X-Cache" value="HIT"/>
    </httpclient:headers>
    <httpclient:body mimetype="application/rss+xml" type="xml">
        <rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:cc="http://web.resource.org/cc/" version="2.0">
            <channel>
                <atom:link href="http://altucher.stansberry.libsynpro.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
                <title>The James Altucher Show</title>
                <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2014 16:37:39 +0000</pubDate>
                <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2014 16:42:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
                <generator>Libsyn WebEngine 2.0</generator>
                <link>http://www.stansberryradio.com</link>
                <language>en</language>
                <copyright>Stansberry Radio Network</copyright>
                <docs>http://www.stansberryradio.com</docs>
                <managingEditor>feedback@stansberryradio.com (feedback@stansberryradio.com)</managingEditor>
                <description>Altucher Show Description</description>
                <image>
                    <url>http://assets.libsyn.com/content/6641608.jpg</url>
                    <title>The James Altucher Show</title>
                    <link>http://www.stansberryradio.com</link>
                </image>
                <itunes:author>James Altucher: Interviews w/ Mark Cuban, Tim Ferriss, Arianna Huffington, Seth Godin, Tucker Max on Entrepreneurship, Investing, Health</itunes:author>
                <itunes:keywords>altucher,choose,help,investing,radio,self,stansberry,yourself</itunes:keywords>
                <itunes:category text="Business">
                    <itunes:category text="Investing"/>
                </itunes:category>
                <itunes:category text="Business">
                    <itunes:category text="Careers"/>
                </itunes:category>
                <itunes:category text="Health">
                    <itunes:category text="Self-Help"/>
                </itunes:category>
                <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/6641608.jpg"/>
                <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                <itunes:owner>
                    <itunes:name>James Altucher: Interviews w/ Mark Cuban, Tim Ferriss, Arianna Huffington, Seth Godin, Tucker Max on Entrepreneurship, Investing, Health</itunes:name>
                    <itunes:email>dnewman@stansberryresearch.com</itunes:email>
                </itunes:owner>
                <itunes:summary>James Altucher is a successful entrepreneur, investor, board member, and the writer of 11 books including the recent WSJ Bestseller, "Choose Yourself!" (foreword by Dick Costolo, CEO of Twitter).
 
He has started and sold several companies for eight figure exits. He's on the board of a billion revenue company, has written for The Financial Times, The New York Observer, and over a dozen popular websites for the past 15 years. He's run several hedge funds, venture capital funds, and is a successful angel investor in technology, energy, and biotech.
 
He has also lost all his money, made it back, lost it, made it back several times and openly discusses how he did it in his columns and books.</itunes:summary>
                <itunes:subtitle>The James Altucher Show</itunes:subtitle>
                <item>
                    <title>Ep. 37 Wendy Simmons: What's Really Going On in North Korea?</title>
                    <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2014 16:37:39 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">3f3dd544acb36f6427deb168488433ed</guid>
                    <link>http://traffic.libsyn.com/altucher/ALR_EP._37_WENDYSIMMONS.mp3</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/3019858"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;The stories and headlines that we hear and see about North Korea could be enough to keep anyone from traveling to the country.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Or even the simple fact that Americans are generally NOT welcomed would be a clear warning to never travel there.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;But for our guest this week, that only enticed her more.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This week, Wendy Simmons, professional photographer and worldwide traveler of over 85 countries, joins The James Altucher Show to share what is really going on in North Korea.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From the moment she entered the country to the day she left, she was assigned a handler to escort her every move.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;With a "military-first" policy and the basic idea that nobody has free will... It's hard to believe that anybody would venture willingly into such a country.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here you will hear Wendy's first-hand experiences and the truth of what she has encountered.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Forget most of what you think you know... because in this interview, everything about the world's most militarized society is revealed in a new light.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="27333280" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/altucher/ALR_EP._37_WENDYSIMMONS.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:05:00</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>The stories and headlines that we hear and see about North Korea could be enough to keep anyone from traveling to the country.Or even the simple fact that Americans are generally NOT welcomed would be a clear warning to never travel there.But for our...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Ep. 36 Ramit Sethi: I Will Teach You to Be Rich</title>
                    <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2014 17:37:28 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">f4223485453016e780a304105123adc4</guid>
                    <link>http://traffic.libsyn.com/altucher/JAS_RamitSethiInterview.mp3</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/3013757"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are tired of living in the dark, being lied to, and sick of wasting your time&amp;hellip; then this is the show you have been waiting for... &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ramit Sethi, author of I Will Teach You to Be Rich, joins The James Altucher Show, to share his personal success story and how he has made a living out of doing what he loves most... inspiring others to find their passion.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The workforce is being bombarded by recent college graduates that are materially ambitious yet financially clueless... &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Millions of jobs applications are filled out every day, but once you fill out that online application, what's next?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Are you being proactive? Do you have control of your future? Have you even considered what other actions and responsibilities you should be doing in the meantime?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;HINT: There are MANY things that you should be doing.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ramit's book, I Will Teach You to Be Rich, has proven to be a practical and detailed approach on personal finance, banking, saving, budgeting, and investing. And today, you get to hear straight from the source what basic skills you need to acquire in order to be successful.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are looking for wealth-building ideas to pursue your entrepreneurial idea, Ramit has all the answers that you are seeking.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="30227102" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/altucher/JAS_RamitSethiInterview.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:11:55</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>If you are tired of living in the dark, being lied to, and sick of wasting your time&amp;hellip; then this is the show you have been waiting for... Ramit Sethi, author of I Will Teach You to Be Rich, joins The James Altucher Show, to share his personal...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Ep. 35 Biz Markie: The Best and Worst Interview You'll Ever Hear</title>
                    <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2014 13:26:23 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">067eae0ad656f1d252ee275d9563b5b9</guid>
                    <link>http://traffic.libsyn.com/altucher/BizMarkie_JAS-FINAL.mp3</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/3001593"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;James says it's his worst interview ever and that he has never felt more awkward or embarrassed.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We think it could be one of the best yet!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We decided to play off of the awkwardness and embarrassing moments in the interview and bring to you something we know you haven't heard anywhere else.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Enter, Biz Markie, hip-hop legend and James' hero.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are familiar with the hit song "Just a Friend" then you already know at least one of his many hits.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From making it as one of the top names in hip-hop to "choosing himself" and losing 150 pounds... Biz shares it all!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Most of people don't know about the many careers that Biz Markie has been able to master. He has gone from rapping to DJ-ing to acting to managing a business.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;But what is really remarkable about him is his attitude... doing what he loves and not worrying about making millions. Money should just be a side effect of doing what you are truly passionate about.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For Biz, that is his many business ventures... He chose himself by having multiple sources of income to support all of his interests.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This interview gives listeners insight into his whole career inside and out. Was he a one-hit guy? Did he resent other rappers that went on to make millions later on? How did he reinvent himself to succeed in other careers?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;How hard do you actually have to work and how many years of practice does it take?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you ever wondered how the hip-hop industry works, and what it takes to make it in a highly competitive field, then this is the show for you.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;With all of his success and opportunities that he has had over the years, James asks Biz if he has any regrets. His answer is truly one to admire and one that a lot of individuals would not be able to say.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="25815799" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/altucher/BizMarkie_JAS-FINAL.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:01:23</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>James says it's his worst interview ever and that he has never felt more awkward or embarrassed.We think it could be one of the best yet!We decided to play off of the awkwardness and embarrassing moments in the interview and bring to you something we...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Ep. 34 James Altucher's Life Story</title>
                    <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2014 16:46:07 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">7f18a53f63a3540aa819bfcba49554ba</guid>
                    <link>http://traffic.libsyn.com/altucher/JAS_Claudia_July24_Final.mp3</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/2997859"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Each week, we get to hear little snippets of James Altucher's life, but we never get the full story.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Today that changes. Today, Claudia turns the tables on James and interviews HIM. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you know James, you have heard him say that he has lost and made millions back and at times mention that he felt as if he was going to die.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So Claudia jumps right into the questions that so many of us want to know more about. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;"Why were you going to die?"&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;"People lose money every day... how many millions did you lose?"&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;"How did you lose it? How did you make it back again?" &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;James reveals all the mistakes that led to his darkest moments... times where he thought he would never see the light again.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Divorced, no job, completely broke, millions have been lost. When you feel that your children would be better off with your life-insurance policy instead of you... how do you come back from something like that?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And... James reveals a HUGE secret that nobody else knows... not even Claudia.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;He has always been open and honest with his listeners and followers of his blog, twitter, and Facebook. But today EVERYTHING is revealed... absolutely nothing is off the table.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;He was able to completely turn his life around... something that most individuals in the same type of situations would not be fortunate enough to do.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;His success, triumph, and passion are truly admirable and could be inspiration to use toward your own life.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It is the ultimate "choose yourself" episode... &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Enjoy.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="31058890" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/altucher/JAS_Claudia_July24_Final.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:13:52</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Each week, we get to hear little snippets of James Altucher's life, but we never get the full story.Today that changes. Today, Claudia turns the tables on James and interviews HIM. If you know James, you have heard him say that he has lost and made...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Ep. 33 Noah Kagan: What It's Like to Lose $100 Million at Facebook</title>
                    <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2014 16:57:29 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">076d383d64bbdad3fcfeb3fbc59c11d4</guid>
                    <link>http://traffic.libsyn.com/altucher/Ep33_NoahKagen-JAS-FINAL.mp3</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/2988619"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Noah Kagan, an American Internet entrepreneur and founder of AppSumo, joins The James Altucher Show.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Noah gets asked the same question every time he gives an interview... "Why were you fired from Facebook?"&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;But today... he shares it all with James and you get to hear the real story.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Noah shares two secrets that he hasn't ever told in an interview before.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;He was fired as one of the first employees of Facebook and he left probably $100,000,000 behind if he had stayed.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;He tells James exactly what happened. Why he was fired. What he did afterwards. And... what he's doing now (its genius).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Then... the interview veers in a different direction that changes James' life and maybe it will change yours as well. Noah tells James that one of the first steps to success is to get over your fears.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Noah presents James with a challenge. It may sound simple, but he encourages all of the listeners to go out and try it as well.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;IT'S UNCOMFORTABLE.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Going outside the comfort zone will put you in THE ZONE. THE ZONE is much bigger than the comfort zone. And James has found that he wants to live in THE ZONE even though it's scarier.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You'll see that life is full of rejection, but what you learn from the experience is what will change your life for the better.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="38038458" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/altucher/Ep33_NoahKagen-JAS-FINAL.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:30:25</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Noah Kagan, an American Internet entrepreneur and founder of AppSumo, joins The James Altucher Show.Noah gets asked the same question every time he gives an interview... "Why were you fired from Facebook?"But today... he shares it all with James and...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Ep. 32 Tim Ryan: The Congressman Who Meditates</title>
                    <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2014 17:07:25 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">fc1cde50acd4361d890cbfd2c56b4567</guid>
                    <link>http://traffic.libsyn.com/altucher/Ep32_TimRyan-JAS-FINAL.mp3</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/2981591"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Tim Ryan, U.S representative for the 13th district of Ohio and author of A Mindful Nation, joins The James Altucher Show.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When you think of politics and Congress, meditation is not usually something that jumps out in your mind.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;But today, that is precisely the case. Tim joins The James Altucher Show to talk about how cutting stress&amp;hellip; Being mindful and aware of others is the number one way to create a less chaotic nation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Just like James, Tim has created a daily practice for himself to exercise his idea muscle and figure out alternative routes to everyday problems.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tim presents listeners with a simple strategy that when applied and practiced can help with any problems that you may have... &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We live in a world where there is a pill for any problem. Do we want to live in a society where our children, politicians, teachers, family, and friends are heavily medicated?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Or are there more effective and natural ways to heal our bodies and minds?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;James and Tim go through several techniques that everyone can use to better their lives with minimal amount of effort.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="21566881" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/altucher/Ep32_TimRyan-JAS-FINAL.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>51:15</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Tim Ryan, U.S representative for the 13th district of Ohio and author of A Mindful Nation, joins The James Altucher Show.When you think of politics and Congress, meditation is not usually something that jumps out in your mind.But today, that is...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Ep. 31 Jim Norton: The Art of Comedy</title>
                    <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2014 17:41:46 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">c61929361e7368020f0f0ce12c2921db</guid>
                    <link>http://traffic.libsyn.com/altucher/JimNorton-JAS-FINAL.mp3</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/2969976"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Today, James interviews his close friend and author of Happy Endings: The Tales of a Meaty-Breasted Zilch, Jim Norton.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You may know Jim from his various appearances on shows or even his own stand-up routines. But what you don't know is the process behind all his achievements.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is where you meet the real Jim Norton. You'll learn how he overcame the darkest part of his life and decided to rise above it all and "choose himself."&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Just like James, Jim found it difficult to perform in front of an audience, but he shares his strategy for connecting and building a quick rapport with a crowd.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;He gives several other tactics that have helped him overcome the anxiety and doubt that builds during his shows. His examples could be approaches that help you cure your own stage fright.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Something that James and Jim both believe in is honesty. An audience responds to honesty and it's what will always work in your favor.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Not only will it free you from guilt and stress, it will protect you if the truth is ever questioned in the future. To have a true connection and respectability with your fans, you need to hide nothing from them.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Get ready to see a side of comedy that is not revealed very often...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Enjoy!&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="22604035" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/altucher/JimNorton-JAS-FINAL.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>53:43</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Today, James interviews his close friend and author of Happy Endings: The Tales of a Meaty-Breasted Zilch, Jim Norton.You may know Jim from his various appearances on shows or even his own stand-up routines. But what you don't know is the process...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Ep.30 Iron Chef Judy Joo: How She Quit Wall Street To Choose Herself</title>
                    <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2014 18:39:58 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">8a737488fa430d99a14a3db62bd238e0</guid>
                    <link>http://traffic.libsyn.com/altucher/Ep30_JudyJoo-JAS-FINAL.mp3</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/2961359"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;In today&amp;rsquo;s interview Judy Joo tells us how she went from being a high-paid Wall Street analyst to a low-paid chef.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="18621451" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/altucher/Ep30_JudyJoo-JAS-FINAL.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>44:15</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>In today&amp;rsquo;s interview Judy Joo tells us how she went from being a high-paid Wall Street analyst to a low-paid chef.</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Ep. 29 Adam Braun: How To Quit Your Job And Do What You Love</title>
                    <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jul 2014 00:16:56 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">f94e49e0ca1aafd748d15efed89a0c9b</guid>
                    <link>http://traffic.libsyn.com/altucher/Ep.29AdamBraun_JAS-FINAL_copy.mp3</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/2953962"/>
                    <description>&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;This week, Adam Braun, New York Times bestselling author and the founder of the charity Pencils of Promise, joins The James Altucher Show.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;Today you will hear how Adam found his purpose in life and what near-disaster made him realize he was meant to live doing what he loved.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;"When you are pushed to your limit and you are faced with your own mortality, it's the expectation, almost knowledge that you have something more to live for." This is how Adam describes the moment that changed his life forever.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;You probably haven't had a near death experience, but today you will learn that there is more than one way to find your purpose in life &amp;ndash; Adam describes three.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;Adam has backpacked around the world, risked his life, and gained knowledge that led him to start an extraordinary charitable organization. This leads James to ask him... "Was it worth it to go to college, given that a lot of the impactful things that happened to you happened outside the classroom?"&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;You won't want to miss Adams response. You'll also find out where he says he learned the most.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;This is the show that gives you the knowledge and tools that will lead you to a successful and significant life... and make it a story worth telling.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;Enjoy!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="25699339" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/altucher/Ep.29AdamBraun_JAS-FINAL_copy.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:01:11</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>This week, Adam Braun, New York Times bestselling author and the founder of the charity Pencils of Promise, joins The James Altucher Show.&amp;nbsp;
Today you will hear how Adam found his purpose in life and what near-disaster made him realize he was...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Ep. 28 Kamal Ravikant: How to Become an Angel Investor with Only $1000</title>
                    <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2014 18:27:43 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">cedbf5a4019c261120d198cb39d7c04f</guid>
                    <link>http://traffic.libsyn.com/altucher/JA-_Kamal_Ravikant.mp3</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/2939067"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;This week, Kamal Ravikant, a serial entrepreneur and author of Live Your Truth, joins The James Altucher Show to talk about the secret to his success.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Today's interview will reveal a side to Kamal that many people have not seen before. He shares his past... from his time in the military to the time he was bed-ridden. There are many life lessons and hardships that he has risen above... and it's here that you get the exclusive details.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;His experiences will remind listeners that everything can change in the blink of an eye. No matter how good or bad a situation is, it will change.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Part of Kamal's success is his skillful investing techniques, and now you will hear what he specifically looks for when picking these enterprises.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;James asks Kamal to share the trends in the technology sector he is excited about (that nobody else knows about yet). Find out why he is excited about what he calls "the new Internet." He describes it as having no government, no private company, no middle man; it will be communication without central authority.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And you won't want to miss this... James and Kamal talk about what could be a tipping point in the BitCoin community. It just takes one country... Find out why they are looking closely at Argentina.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Then, James asks Kamal to talk about the success he has seen from his books. You'll hear the real secret to Kamal's success. He explains, "The key is really simple: Create something of value that's more about giving to others than to yourself and then put it where people are."&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Just like James, Kamal believes in being completely honest and transparent with your audience so that they can have the opportunity to relate to you and your writing.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Get ready because this is the interview that gives you great insight from a truly unique entrepreneur.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="27134409" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/altucher/JA-_Kamal_Ravikant.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:04:36</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>This week, Kamal Ravikant, a serial entrepreneur and author of Live Your Truth, joins The James Altucher Show to talk about the secret to his success.Today's interview will reveal a side to Kamal that many people have not seen before. He shares his...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Ep. 27 Seth Godin: Guts and Glory</title>
                    <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2014 13:33:57 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">5ea58a545693b609eabf355f5d6e9e5e</guid>
                    <link>http://traffic.libsyn.com/altucher/Ep27_SethGodin-JAS-FINAL.mp3</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/2925471"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;This week, Seth Godin, founder and CEO of Squidoo.com joins The James Altucher Show to talk about some of the ideas behind his many bestsellers. He'll also share how he got started on his entrepreneurial path.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;James starts the interview by asking Seth to introduce a side of himself that many people might not know about.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You'll hear how his summer as a camp instructor was where he really discovered his passion for helping people. This time of his life also is where many of the themes of his books originated.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Discover which two books were most influential to James while he was starting his internet business... they could be the inspiration that you have been looking for, as well.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Then, James asks Seth to talk about what the first real big push into success was for him. It was a highly successful company that you have probably never heard of.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You'll find out which company it was and why Yahoo was so impressed they decided to buy it.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Just like James, Seth believes in the power of storytelling. You'll hear him break down how his newest book All Marketers Are Liars embodies the importance of storytelling and the role it plays in the marketing of everything.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It's a fantastic interview, where Seth really opens up, shares his path to success, and discusses what he would have done differently if he were given the chance.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Enjoy!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="12412761" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/altucher/Ep27_SethGodin-JAS-FINAL.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>29:29</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>This week, Seth Godin, founder and CEO of Squidoo.com joins The James Altucher Show to talk about some of the ideas behind his many bestsellers. He'll also share how he got started on his entrepreneurial path.James starts the interview by asking Seth...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Ep. 26 The Power of No</title>
                    <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2014 18:57:38 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">c111cde4caf587a49f8b086504aeb73a</guid>
                    <link>http://traffic.libsyn.com/altucher/JASJamesClaudiaPodcast_EDIT.mp3</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/2913221"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Today's show is a little different. Aaron is out so James asked his wife, Claudia, to join as his co-host to talk about their new book, The Power of No.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;How many times have you heard yourself saying "yes" to the wrong things &amp;ndash; overwhelming requests, bad relationships, time-consuming obligations? How often have you wished you could summon the power to turn them down?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;James and Claudia talk about how this book is a practical guide that helps you take back that power &amp;ndash; and shows that a well-placed "no" can not only save you time and trouble... it can save your life.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Drawing on their own stories as well as feedback from their readers and students, James and Claudia clearly show that you have the right to say no to:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;bull;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Anything that is hurting you&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;bull;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Standards that no longer serve you&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;bull;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; People who drain you of your creativity and expression&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;bull;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Beliefs that are not true to the real you&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;"It's one thing to say no," the authors explain, "it's another thing to have the 'Power of No.' When you do, you will have a stronger sense of what is good for you and the people around you, and you will have a deeper understanding of who you are. And, ultimately, you'll be free to say a truly powerful 'Yes' in your life &amp;ndash; one that opens the door to opportunities, abundance, and love."&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is like a chance to sit down with the authors and get the inside scoop.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you Pre-order NOW, before July 15, 2014, you can get THREE FREE GIFTS&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Bonus Audio Chapter: "The Opportunity Cost of NO"&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Bonus Audio Chapter: "What to Do When Someone Says NO &amp;ndash; To YOU"&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;3.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Free PDF Copy of The Choose Yourself Stories&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Click here to get the details on how you can pre-order.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We hope you use The Power of No and the bonus materials to live your best "Yes!" life.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Enjoy!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="35231953" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/altucher/JASJamesClaudiaPodcast_EDIT.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:23:53</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Today's show is a little different. Aaron is out so James asked his wife, Claudia, to join as his co-host to talk about their new book, The Power of No.How many times have you heard yourself saying "yes" to the wrong things &amp;ndash; overwhelming...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Ep. 25 Adam Carolla: The Next President of the USA</title>
                    <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2014 14:44:48 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">f5a1e710b300db06a2266088d89c8e62</guid>
                    <link>http://traffic.libsyn.com/altucher/JAS_AdamCarolla-FINAL.mp3</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/2900895"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;This week, Adam Carolla, American comedian and host of The Adam Carolla Show, joins The James Altucher Show.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You probably know Adam best from his show on Comedy Central, The Man Show. But what you might not know is how the show actually originated.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Today, Adam reveals the secret to the show that may shock many listeners.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Like James, Adam chose a more unconventional path in life.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;He was a college dropout who tried every job in the book. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;But with perseverance, he was able to go around the gatekeepers of the industry that he wanted to pursue. You'll hear all the struggles and hurdles that got Adam to where he is today.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A humbling side of Adam is revealed as he shares the story of his first consistent paying job where the little things meant so much to him. Things as simple as sitting in air conditioning and getting paid to interview people... He says he just could not fathom the idea of it.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Even when his ideas were shut down, he found incentive to move forward and continue building his idea muscle... &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here, you'll learn that you have to break out of your comfort zone to really succeed.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Plus, you won't want to miss this, Adam discusses his newest book President Me: The America That's in My Head. It's your chance to sit down and have a one-on-one with the author himself.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;James and Adam discuss the general entitlement that people seem to have across America, as mentioned in his book.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And for anyone seeking advice or wisdom on starting a podcasting career... listen up, because Adam has several priceless suggestions.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You'll also hear all about what Adam calls his "patent troll," opening up about a recent lawsuit his podcast is facing...&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="17403152" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/altucher/JAS_AdamCarolla-FINAL.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>41:19</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>This week, Adam Carolla, American comedian and host of The Adam Carolla Show, joins The James Altucher Show.You probably know Adam best from his show on Comedy Central, The Man Show. But what you might not know is how the show actually...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Ep. 24 Mark Cuban â€“ Enough Said</title>
                    <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2014 18:06:50 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">ec920d9f1367b7adfdaf3ccda879c99f</guid>
                    <link>http://traffic.libsyn.com/altucher/JAS_MarkCuban-FINAL.mp3</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/2888987"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;e is all over the media... but this is an interview you won't get anywhere else!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Having started out with no money, living with six guys in a three-bedroom apartment, while sleeping on the floor, it's kind of hard to believe that this person would be able to retire by age 30.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;But this isn't just any person, it's Mark Cuban... and that is exactly what he did. His first passion in life was getting rich, and today you get the real story about his success.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It was more than just aspiration &amp;ndash; Mark says it was about putting in the time and the desire to be self-employed and an entrepreneur that really drove his passion.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What started as the motivation to simply survive his monthly bills turned into a life he could not have imagined.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From his first college bar to MicroSolutions (the first company that he sold), you'll get the inside scoop on how his business ventures started and then soared to epic proportions.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Plus, Mark goes into detail about his recent case with the SEC, and talks about the influence that the case had on the creation of Cyber Dust.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It will surely make you think twice about sending your next text, email, tweet, or any communication over the internet.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="23089471" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/altucher/JAS_MarkCuban-FINAL.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>54:53</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>e is all over the media... but this is an interview you won't get anywhere else!Having started out with no money, living with six guys in a three-bedroom apartment, while sleeping on the floor, it's kind of hard to believe that this person would be...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Ep. 23 How To Go From $0-$40,000 a Month Writing From Home</title>
                    <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2014 15:14:08 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">ff4f62108d5c81a598eecbc688faef6c</guid>
                    <link>http://traffic.libsyn.com/altucher/Ep23_SteveScott-JAS-FINAL.mp3</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/2876161"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Divorce, success, failure, struggle... are these excuses or stepping stones?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Today's guest has been through many situations similar to our host, James Altucher.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Like James, Steve Scott has made his passions a reality by going around the gatekeepers of industries and finding a way to "choose himself."&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Steve has written a variety of books that deliver step-by-step strategies you can immediately implement to improve your life and business strategies.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You'll quickly learn that what separates Steve from many others is his unique ability to break down barriers and explain complex topics in a no-nonsense, straight forward way.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You would think that having a failed marriage, losing his house, and moving back in with his parents would have slowed his success and willpower. However, for Steve, that is simply not the case... in fact, it has only pushed his drive and focus even further.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is your shortcut in life... There is no holding back in this interview. Steve shares all the secrets and shortcuts that have brought him success.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This month alone he is already set to make $40,000... all from the comfort of his home and at his own leisurely schedule.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There are two strategies that Steve follows, and he explains why there is no need for any others... It could be your new business philosophy.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Enjoy!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="26757033" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/altucher/Ep23_SteveScott-JAS-FINAL.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:03:38</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Divorce, success, failure, struggle... are these excuses or stepping stones?Today's guest has been through many situations similar to our host, James Altucher.Like James, Steve Scott has made his passions a reality by going around the gatekeepers of...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Ep. 22 Tim Ferriss: Possibilities and Experimentation</title>
                    <pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2014 17:55:56 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">4fe0dcf7ec36f624522d8fc4106d9e9e</guid>
                    <link>http://traffic.libsyn.com/altucher/JAShow_TimFerrissInterview_Final-.mp3</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/2864466"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;This week James hosts his good friend and best-selling author of The 4-Hour Workweek, Tim Ferriss.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Before every interview, James spends hours reviewing his guest's work so he can come up with something different and something very special.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This interview proved to be the most difficult in regard to preparation, so far. Not because Tim Ferriss doesn't have anything interesting to talk about (quite the opposite), but because James didn't want to ask him the same old questions he gets asked on every interview. "Can you really only work 4 hours a week?" "Did you really do the things you wrote about?" "Is it actually possible to get the results that you did?" Blah, Blah, Blah.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tim Ferriss has done many different, interesting things besides writing his "4 hour series," and James explores many of those passions on this podcast.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And don't worry, this isn't "The 4 Hour Podcast." But almost.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="45012821" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/altucher/JAShow_TimFerrissInterview_Final-.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:47:03</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>This week James hosts his good friend and best-selling author of The 4-Hour Workweek, Tim Ferriss.Before every interview, James spends hours reviewing his guest's work so he can come up with something different and something very special.This...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Ep. 21 College is a Scam</title>
                    <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2014 19:56:38 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">fcf87a84af85a3c9beee17c4eca7d107</guid>
                    <link>http://traffic.libsyn.com/altucher/JAShow_CollegeEpisode_WithCommercial.mp3</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/2850813"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;We are doing something a little different this week. There isn't a guest, but there will be a heated debate between James and Aaron.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It's a sensitive topic for many individuals, so get ready...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kids that are graduating high school right now are beginning to apply for college. Unfortunately, they could be making one of the biggest mistakes of their lives.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hundreds of dollars of student debt, little to no job opportunities &amp;ndash; these are the realities of today's college graduate.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;James takes some of the most popular arguments for why kids should go to college and turns them on their head.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It's the American religion that kids should go to college... but is it necessary?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What are the reasons for going to college? Is it to network and meet people?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Couldn't you do the same by taking a year off and traveling? Not only would you get to see the world, meet people from all walks of life, but you would be gaining knowledge and experiences that could NEVER be taught in a classroom.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Will you make more money if you go to college?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Do you want to be a writer? Why not write a book for free and self-publish?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There are many ways around almost every gate-keeper out there... Why not get a head start on your fellow "classmates" and skip the debt process?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sure you learn certain things in college, but the real question is, "what are you NOT learning?"...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Whether you are a student or the parent of a student, listening to this episode is a must...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And even if you are neither, these children are the future of the country and they will affect the direction this country goes.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It's a fantastic show that will certainly have you rethinking your goals in life.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="35564737" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/altucher/JAShow_CollegeEpisode_WithCommercial.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:24:33</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>We are doing something a little different this week. There isn't a guest, but there will be a heated debate between James and Aaron.It's a sensitive topic for many individuals, so get ready...Kids that are graduating high school right now are...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Ep. 20 Stephen Dubner: How to Think Like a Freak</title>
                    <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2014 15:52:35 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">8fbb9bfc770a52cf6dd26e5a822e9b6b</guid>
                    <link>http://traffic.libsyn.com/altucher/Ep._20_JA-StephenDubnerw-commercial.mp3</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/2840445"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;This week, James asked one of his favorite guests, Stephen Dubner, to join the show and talk about his newest book, Think Like a Freak.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Just like his previous bestseller, Freakonomics, you'll hear James and Stephen talk about how his new book also infuses the power of storytelling... If you don't already know the secret purpose, you'll hear it here!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Stephen's newest book gives practical advice on how to think outside of the box and how to solve problems from an economic perspective.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;He explains to our listeners that "in order for a piece of writing to be successful, you have to be really good at both logic and rhetoric." &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What Stephen has to share will certainly have your idea-muscle breaking a sweat... &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;His recipe for greatness is revealed. and you'll get incredibly valuable behind-the-scenes knowledge.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Get ready, because once again, James has found another completely unconventional guest to deliver priceless knowledge and information that you just can't get anywhere else!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It's rare to come across an individual that sees the world so differently than anyone else.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is where you will learn how to think a bit more productively, more creatively, more rationally, and most importantly, a bit unusual... &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Do you have what it takes to Think Like a Freak?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="25427249" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/altucher/Ep._20_JA-StephenDubnerw-commercial.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:00:32</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>This week, James asked one of his favorite guests, Stephen Dubner, to join the show and talk about his newest book, Think Like a Freak.Just like his previous bestseller, Freakonomics, you'll hear James and Stephen talk about how his new book also...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Ep. 19 Austin Kleon: How To Be A Creative Genius</title>
                    <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2014 12:40:16 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">7a828898ade294ee93d8b554847960ec</guid>
                    <link>http://traffic.libsyn.com/altucher/EP19_JAShow_AustinKleon.mp3</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/2828271"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;This week, Austin Kleon, New York Times bestselling author, joins The James Altucher Show.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;James and Austin start the show with a discussion on embracing influence, which is the main theme in his book, Steal Like An Artist.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This will truly open up your creativity and tap into your artistic side.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Austin believes that you should open yourself up to influence and accept a mash up of what you let into your life.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;James and Austin both express the importance of following your interests and generating ideas... They tell you how you can be unique by just reinventing ideas of others.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;They encourage you to "choose yourself" and get rid of any hurdles that are keeping you from success.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And... It's a question that many of us have asked... "How do I find purpose in life?" &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It's different for everyone, but Austin tells you how to look at the world to figure that out.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Throughout the day, is there time that you are not using efficiently? Find out how to utilize those moments you might have been overlooking. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It's a fantastic show that you won't want to miss out on.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Enjoy!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="22313811" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/altucher/EP19_JAShow_AustinKleon.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>53:02</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>This week, Austin Kleon, New York Times bestselling author, joins The James Altucher Show.James and Austin start the show with a discussion on embracing influence, which is the main theme in his book, Steal Like An Artist.This will truly open up your...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Ep. 18 Ryan Holiday: Turning Trials into Triumph</title>
                    <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2014 17:52:29 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">527e861e3f72ad116e94b54cf070e456</guid>
                    <link>http://traffic.libsyn.com/altucher/JA-Ep18_1-2.mp3</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/2815492"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Feeling stuck, frustrated, or faced with unbearable situations?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Do you find it difficult to live in the present moment?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If any of those apply to you, then this is the show to listen to!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ryan Holiday joins The James Altucher Show to talk about his brand-new book, The Obstacle Is the Way: The Timeless Art of Turning Trials into Triumph.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You'll hear how you can build resilience in your life to help protect yourself from any difficulties that may cross your path.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is a discipline in perception that needs to be put in place... and James and Ryan walk you through the process.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;His book depicts several examples of individuals that were faced with impossible situations and were able to thrive past any limitations they thought would have held them back.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A lot of us are stuck, stymied, and frustrated &amp;ndash; working to make the best of the financial crisis or unemployment or personal problems. But it needn't be this way. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is a formula for success that has been followed by the icons of history &amp;ndash; from John D. Rockefeller to Amelia Earhart to Ulysses S. Grant to Steve Jobs &amp;ndash; a formula that let them turn obstacles into opportunities. The Obstacle Is The Way contains that formula and will be your manual for facing adversity and turning it into the triumphs we all seek.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you can't handle the minor obstacles, how are you going to handle the major dilemmas?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is your chance to get an inside look from the author himself... There is a formula to turn negative situations into positive ones and James and Ryan reveal the secret.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;James asks Ryan, why this book and why now?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;"I believe that you write the book that you have to write. This is that book for me. I first discovered the Stoic exercise of turning obstacles upside down when I was 19 years old. Since then, it has been seared into my brain regardless of what I've done, and I've always tried to think about my problems and opportunities in life through that frame. It has helped me become successful, just as it helped countless people before me. The Obstacle Is The Way reveals that framework for the first time &amp;ndash; and shows you how to turn your trials and tribulations into opportunities."&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="17818739" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/altucher/JA-Ep18_1-2.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>42:25</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Feeling stuck, frustrated, or faced with unbearable situations?Do you find it difficult to live in the present moment?If any of those apply to you, then this is the show to listen to!Ryan Holiday joins The James Altucher Show to talk about his...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Ep. 17 Chris Brogan â€“ Are YOU a Freak?</title>
                    <pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2014 16:43:56 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">882a264e8492acaafdd98c1e2ad9bc12</guid>
                    <link>http://traffic.libsyn.com/altucher/Ep17_JAShow_ChrisBroganInterview.mp3</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/2801798"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Willpower is pointless!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Do you agree? If you do then you will love this interview with Publisher and CEO of Owner Magazine, Chris Brogan.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;James brings Chris on as a guest to talk about his new book, The Freaks Shall Inherit the Earth: Entrepreneurship for Weirdos, Misfits, and World Dominators.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He breaks down what willpower really is... just our brains' programming language.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Just like James does in his upcoming book, The Power of No, Chris discusses how to use discipline with our willpower and to learn that smarter no's lead to better yesses...&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;How do you avoid getting stuck in "plan-ville?" How will you launch these great ideas that have inspired you?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;James and Chris talk about how to turn your passions into businesses...&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Are you still playing it safe? Scared to take that plunge and trust your ideas?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is an excellent "Choose Yourself" episode that gives you that nudge of reassurance that you need to go after whatever it is that you are hesitant about.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Enjoy!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="21665620" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/altucher/Ep17_JAShow_ChrisBroganInterview.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>51:30</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>&amp;nbsp;
Willpower is pointless!
&amp;nbsp;
Do you agree? If you do then you will love this interview with Publisher and CEO of Owner Magazine, Chris Brogan.
&amp;nbsp;
James brings Chris on as a guest to talk about his new book, The Freaks Shall Inherit...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Ep. 16 Mastering Online Dating!</title>
                    <pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2014 16:08:19 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">5260d43aaef64ca4cd9ab7255a57c196</guid>
                    <link>http://traffic.libsyn.com/altucher/Ep16_JAShow.mp3</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/2790158"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;How can you make yourself stand out in a crowd?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Are you catching the right person's attention?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Well, here is the show where you can figure that out. Our guest this week is Paul Oyer, author of Everything I Ever Needed to Know about Economics I Learned from Online Dating.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Like our host James, Paul is an interesting guy who has found success by thinking outside the box.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Paul shares his discoveries about the online dating world that he found to stem from economics.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After more than 20 years of marriage, Paul found himself swimming in the deep sea of the online dating scene...&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sure he was out of the game for some time &amp;ndash; older than the last time he was single &amp;ndash; but he did have an edge on the dating market... his economist's point of view.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He talks about his experiences in the online dating world that helped him learn how to stand out. It's all about signaling...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Paul explains how he came to realize that the sites available out there are no different from the markets that he had spent a lifetime studying.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You'll hear how you can relate these ideas to your everyday life.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Enjoy!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="25492873" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/altucher/Ep16_JAShow.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:00:35</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>How can you make yourself stand out in a crowd?
&amp;nbsp;
Are you catching the right person's attention?
&amp;nbsp;
Well, here is the show where you can figure that out. Our guest this week is Paul Oyer, author of Everything I Ever Needed to Know about...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Ep. 15 The Man Who Gave Away 50 Million Dollars and Moved Into a Trailer Park</title>
                    <pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2014 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">ae018daea059549ffbcf871c6bf89d21</guid>
                    <link>http://traffic.libsyn.com/altucher/Ep15_JAShowTomShadyakInterview.mp3</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/2775545"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Tom Shadyac, one of the most prolific comedy directors in Hollywood, joins The James Altucher Show.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="27140531" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/altucher/Ep15_JAShowTomShadyakInterview.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:04:31</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Tom Shadyac, one of the most prolific comedy directors in Hollywood, joins The James Altucher Show.</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Ep. 14 Gabrielle Bernstein: Miracles</title>
                    <pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2014 16:09:21 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">3a9a528651acc45dfeafac69bf133a38</guid>
                    <link>http://traffic.libsyn.com/altucher/Ep14_JAShow.mp3</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/2771675"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;This week, Gabrielle Bernstein, New York Times bestselling author, joins The James Altucher Show to give us an exclusive look into her new book Miracles Now, which is being released today!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;James starts the show off by asking Gabrielle how she started her media empire. She takes us back to the very beginning and her first career in public relations promoting night clubs.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Believe it or not, by the time Gabrielle was 25 years old, she was already in a dark place and had hit rock bottom. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;She was in the party scene, stressed, overwhelmed, and over-worked.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You'll hear how she overcame all and was able to resurrect her life.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;James and Gabrielle talk about those moments in life when you do feel most stressed and she offers up some tools that you can use to eliminate those frustrations. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;They talk about how to look at your moments of panic, depression, and emotional thoughts with a new perspective. It is up to you to reach for positive thoughts and solutions.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Gabrielle's new book, Miracles Now, presents you with the life-changing techniques that will melt away fear, channel your inner strength, and bring you inner peace.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here is your chance to get the inside scoop from the author herself!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Enjoy.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="24016805" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/altucher/Ep14_JAShow.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>57:06</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>This week, Gabrielle Bernstein, New York Times bestselling author, joins The James Altucher Show to give us an exclusive look into her new book Miracles Now, which is being released today!James starts the show off by asking Gabrielle how she started...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Ep. 13 Arianna Huffington: The New Way To Thrive</title>
                    <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2014 19:47:55 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">4b9b190487d6351b461ddacb0e110792</guid>
                    <link>http://traffic.libsyn.com/altucher/Ep._13_JA-AriannaHuffington.mp3</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/2766053"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;This week, Arianna Huffington, president, and Editor in Chief of the Huffington Post Media Group, joins The James Altucher Show to talk about her new book, Thrive. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Are you stressed over work, relationships, or your environment?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Is stress causing you to miss out on certain activities or events?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Are you losing your connection with what really matters? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In today's show, James and Arianna go through it all and much more... &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;They talk about what it really means to be successful in today's world and the stress that is caused from the constant strives for perfection.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You will hear Arianna break down the baby steps that helped her make her transformation to a more successful and less stressful life.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It could be something as simple as adding 30 minutes of sleep to your schedule... It's what she calls the miracle drug!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Find out why she no longer multi-tasks... It could be a change that you need to make in order to "choose yourself."&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Something that we need to do is bring joy back to our daily life... James and Arianna tell us how we can make that possible.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is a shortcut to happiness, and you heard it here first.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It's a powerful and eye-opening episode... &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Enjoy!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="14227879" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/altucher/Ep._13_JA-AriannaHuffington.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>33:52</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>This week, Arianna Huffington, president, and Editor in Chief of the Huffington Post Media Group, joins The James Altucher Show to talk about her new book, Thrive. Are you stressed over work, relationships, or your environment?Is stress causing you to...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Ep. 12 "How To Be 10% Happier"</title>
                    <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2014 13:45:39 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">5aedf233cef16c15746173af15454078</guid>
                    <link>http://traffic.libsyn.com/altucher/Ep12_JAShow.mp3</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/2753259"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;This week, Dan Harris, co-anchor of ABC News' weekend edition of "Good Morning America," joins The James Altucher Show to talk about his new book, 10% Happier.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Do you have 5 minutes to dedicate to your health?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In that little bit of time, you could lower your blood pressure, relieve stress, and even rewire your brain. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Some people might cringe at the thought of the first topic that we cover... meditation. But maybe they don't understand exactly what can be considered as meditation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In today's show, you'll hear just how useful this tool can be and how easily it can be incorporated into your daily life routine. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Everybody has time to better themselves... it's just a matter of "choosing yourself" and making it a habit.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Then, Dan Harris breaks down all barriers and shares it all.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You'll hear about how he suffered panic attacks as a result from his drug addiction and how his experiences had led to the creation of his book, 10% Happier.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dan shares with our listeners the secrets that he has stumbled upon that have led to his success in life.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;They talk about the "Don't be a jerk" theory and the true power of compassion in the business world.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You will learn how to be successful, happy, improve your focus, build stronger relationships, and how to live in the moment.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Enjoy!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="25814651" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/altucher/Ep12_JAShow.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:01:21</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>This week, Dan Harris, co-anchor of ABC News' weekend edition of "Good Morning America," joins The James Altucher Show to talk about his new book, 10% Happier.Do you have 5 minutes to dedicate to your health?In that little bit of time, you could lower...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Ep. 11 "Who Will Be the Next President of the United States?"</title>
                    <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2014 17:18:41 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">4710f40f8f92c5e87073d78e7fabe9bf</guid>
                    <link>http://traffic.libsyn.com/altucher/Ep11_JAShow.mp3</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/2750153"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Ken Kurson, editor of The New York Observer, political consultant, journalist, and author, joins The James Altucher Show&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;"You've created a 'Choose Yourself Career.'" Nobody could have just given you the career you've had. You've had to go and hunt for that career. You had to kill for that career. You made it up yourself as you went along.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This week, Ken Kurson, editor of The New York Observer, political consultant, journalist, and author, joins The James Altucher Show to talk about who will be the next President of the United States, the future of the media, and Ken's million-dollar deal that's still out there for the right entrepreneur to grab and run with.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;"Green was my one great idea in my life." There really is room, in my opinion, for a legitimate inheritor to the Greenmantle." &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;James and Ken then jump right into what it was like to work with America's Mayor, Rudy Guilliani. You'll get a firsthand look at what it's like running for President of the United States and what it takes to win.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;James asks Ken who he thinks the 2016 Republican and Democratic front runners are right now. You might be very surprised by his picks.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;They talk about getting rid of our two-party system because, as James says, "It doesn't seem to work at all. The candidates are very similar. I mean, in very rare cases, can I tell a difference in policy, actually, between Obama and Bush. It just seems like the two-party system and the lack of democracy, as you mentioned, is just a total failure."&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;But Ken disagrees&amp;hellip; "Yeah, I don't agree. I think the two-party system is a disaster except for all the other systems that have tried democracy which is an inversion of the old democracy is terrible except for all the other systems."&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And so James offers up a brand-new, high-tech system that he believes could really help.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Plus, James asks Ken "So what's next in the media industry?" &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I think you'll be very surprised by Ken's answer... &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;"I don't think Twitter is the end of news. I believe we're kind of in a golden age of attention span. There's never been a time where people would watch 13 hours of beautifully written television in a row; the same show. I think it's really the beginning."&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope you enjoy.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="19514387" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/altucher/Ep11_JAShow.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>46:24</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Ken Kurson, editor of The New York Observer, political consultant, journalist, and author, joins The James Altucher Show"You've created a 'Choose Yourself Career.'" Nobody could have just given you the career you've had. You've had to go and hunt for...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Ep. 10 "How to Be a Super-Human"</title>
                    <pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2014 12:51:25 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">08b3f0b911a4220621a0a6c967d86f8f</guid>
                    <link>http://traffic.libsyn.com/altucher/Ep10_JAShow.mp3</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/2740952"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;This week, Steven Kotler, an American bestselling author, journalist, and entrepreneur joins The James Altucher Show to talk about his new book The Rise of Superman: Decoding the Science of Ultimate Human Performance.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;They break down the term "flow," an optimal state of consciousness in which we perform and feel our best, and Steven shares his fascination with the term.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;His book focuses on extreme athletes who partake in phenomenal situations that are impossible to train for and experience "flow" that bridges their ability gap.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Steven calls them "flow" hackers... and discusses how he has used them as case studies to figure out how they trigger and harness their euphoric state.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You will learn how to activate your own state of flow and unleash your creativity.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Time will stand still allowing opportunities and possibilities that you never even imagined to open up.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It's a great "Choose Yourself" tool to master.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="30678458" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/altucher/Ep10_JAShow.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:12:57</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>This week, Steven Kotler, an American bestselling author, journalist, and entrepreneur joins The James Altucher Show to talk about his new book The Rise of Superman: Decoding the Science of Ultimate Human Performance.They break down the term "flow,"...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Ep. 9 Is Self-Publishing the Next Gold Rush?</title>
                    <pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2014 13:54:34 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">ad05c2b847ea587642633b346e18e817</guid>
                    <link>http://traffic.libsyn.com/altucher/Ep9_JAShow.mp3</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/2728908"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;This week, Hugh Howey, author of the New York Times bestseller Wool, joins The James Altucher Show.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you have ever wanted to write a book or any piece of literature... this is the show for you.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hugh explains how self-publishing is breaking down the walls to the literary world. This is creating more genres that people actually want to read rather than what general publishers assume the public wants to read.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You'll hear him break down his creative process and the steps that he took to self-publish his books.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Just by cutting out a few activities a day made it possible for him to accomplish his writing goals.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It will prove that you are the only one standing in the way of your success.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Taking a day off will only snowball... you have to stick with it.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You have to "Choose Yourself!"&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="31197697" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/altucher/Ep9_JAShow.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:14:10</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>This week, Hugh Howey, author of the New York Times bestseller Wool, joins The James Altucher Show.If you have ever wanted to write a book or any piece of literature... this is the show for you.Hugh explains how self-publishing is breaking down the...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Ep. 8 Anxiety: How to Deal with It</title>
                    <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2014 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">69df8d7168f87349d4c0fb13b2394e6d</guid>
                    <link>http://traffic.libsyn.com/altucher/Ep8_JAShow_FINAL.mp3</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/2716099"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;On this week's show, James and Aaron discuss the Stansberry Society Conference that was held this past weekend in Miami.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;James shares with Aaron the nervousness that he felt about speaking at the conference and how he was able to overcome that anxiety. It's something useful to anyone that has to do public speaking.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Then James interviews Charlie Hoehn, author of Play It Away: A Workaholic's Cure for Anxiety.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is truly no holding back for Charlie... &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;How do you pull yourself out of an emotional slump?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;He shares with James and our listeners the lowest points he has experienced in life, and the one book that changed it all.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Then, they talk about something that all of us have done as kids but maybe have forgotten the importance of... How to play and let yourself have guilt-free fun.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;James and Charlie discuss the many ways they take time for themselves to play, generate ideas, and how it jump starts different parts of their brain.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You will hear how planning time for yourself can cure many things... &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Plus, find out how Charlie was able to have his book edited for free... and turn out 10 times better than if he had gone through a traditional publisher.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So we hope you are paying attention because here is your chance to have a better life, make more money, have more fun, and accomplish your dreams by ignoring conventional wisdom.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And... Don't miss this! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We debut our first-ever "Ask Altucher" segment... &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Enjoy!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="27999529" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/altucher/Ep8_JAShow_FINAL.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:06:34</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>On this week's show, James and Aaron discuss the Stansberry Society Conference that was held this past weekend in Miami.James shares with Aaron the nervousness that he felt about speaking at the conference and how he was able to overcome that anxiety....</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Ep. 7 Matthew Berry: How to Create Your Fantasy Life</title>
                    <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2014 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">a83319600c0af5448ed394409c5b71c8</guid>
                    <link>http://altucher.stansberry.libsynpro.com/ep-7-matthew-berry-how-to-create-your-fantasy-life</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/2699611"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;This week, Matthew Berry, Senior Fantasy Sports Analyst at ESPN, joins the show to talk about his &lt;em&gt;New York Times&lt;/em&gt; bestseller, &lt;em&gt;Fantasy Life&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The world of fantasy sports is huge, and still growing, Matthew gives us an inside look to this niche subculture that has become a national pastime. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You will hear him talk about his success as a writer and the different career paths he has experienced along the way.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And... there is no holding back!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Divorce, hate mail, business deals gone bad, disappointing celebrity idols... Matthew shares it all.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Find out his secret to happiness.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Plus, don't miss out on the special promo code to use at rotopass.com.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Enjoy!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="47321303" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/altucher/JA-MattBerry2.20.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:52:40</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>This week, Matthew Berry, Senior Fantasy Sports Analyst at ESPN, joins the show to talk about his New York Times bestseller, Fantasy Life.The world of fantasy sports is huge, and still growing, Matthew gives us an inside look to this niche subculture...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Ep. 6 Dr. Wayne Dyer: A Test to See If You Are Ordinary</title>
                    <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2014 18:21:01 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">b0192ba96ba9d64e7a123b4f345571d6</guid>
                    <link>http://altucher.stansberry.libsynpro.com/ep-6-dr-wayne-dyer-a-test-to-see-if-you-are-ordinary</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/2693927"/>
                    <description>&lt;p style="margin: 0px; font-size: 13px; font-family: Verdana;"&gt;It's a question many of us are too afraid to answer..&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 11px; font-family: Verdana;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 11px; font-size: 13px; font-family: Verdana;"&gt;"Is this as good as it gets?"&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; font-size: 13px; font-family: Verdana;"&gt;Perhaps you feel that way from time to time. You get stuck in an unfulfilling job. You get stuck with a mortgage you can barely pay, in a house that didn't make you any happier than your previous home. You get stuck in a negative relationship. And you wonder if things will ever get better.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; font-size: 13px; font-family: Verdana;"&gt;James Altucher knows the feeling well. And in the latest episode of his radio show, he shows you exactly how to get "un-stuck" by making your negative life experiences work &lt;em&gt;for &lt;/em&gt;you instead of against you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; font-size: 13px; font-family: Verdana;"&gt;The type of unconventional ideas you'll hear on his show made James a millionaire... and many of his guests have done the same.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; font-size: 13px; font-family: Verdana;"&gt;This week's guest is no exception..&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; font-size: 13px; font-family: Verdana;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;Dr. Wayne Dyer has seen plenty of obstacles in his life... but his attitude and belief in the power of self-reliance have earned him the title "father of motivation" by his fans.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; font-size: 13px; font-family: Verdana;"&gt;A hard worker since his first paper route at age 9, Dr. Dyer says, "There's never been a moment when I was unemployed, ever."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; font-size: 13px; font-family: Verdana;"&gt;He was an orphan, served in the military, taught at a prestigious university, had eight children of his own, and made a comfortable life for himself in Hawaii.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; font-size: 13px; font-family: Verdana;"&gt;To say he is influential is an understatement.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 11px; font-family: Verdana;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; font-size: 13px; font-family: Verdana;"&gt;His first book, &lt;em&gt;Your Erroneous Zones&lt;/em&gt;, was not only a &lt;em&gt;New York Times&lt;/em&gt; bestseller, but it sold more than 100 million copies in 47 languages... and was even smuggled to readers living behind the Iron Curtain of the 1980's.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 11px; font-family: Verdana;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; font-size: 13px; font-family: Verdana;"&gt;He is one of the most prolific writers of our time. In fact, he has authored 40 books.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 11px; font-family: Verdana;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; font-size: 13px; font-family: Verdana;"&gt;But like we mentioned earlier, some people really struggle with the feeling that their life is ordinary and unimportant...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 11px; font-family: Verdana;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; font-size: 13px; font-family: Verdana;"&gt;James and Dr. Dyer explain why getting "un-stuck" is so important.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 11px; font-family: Verdana;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; font-size: 13px; font-family: Verdana;"&gt;Dr. Dyer explains "If you're feeling stuck, your stuckness is going to have a physical impact on you... You're gonna get sick if you stay stuck."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 11px; font-family: Verdana;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; font-size: 13px; font-family: Verdana;"&gt;More importantly, he shows you exactly how to get un-stuck, and live the life you were meant to lead.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 11px; font-family: Verdana;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; font-size: 13px; font-family: Verdana;"&gt;The tips and ideas Dr. Dyer discusses in the show are wide ranging.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 11px; font-family: Verdana;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; font-size: 13px; font-family: Verdana;"&gt;From how to side-step fights with your wife... to avoiding the most common regret of the dying... Dr. Dyer's advice is well worth listening to.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 11px; font-family: Verdana;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; font-size: 13px; font-family: Verdana;"&gt;We&amp;rsquo;ll be the first to admit this was an intense show.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 11px; font-family: Verdana;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; font-size: 13px; font-family: Verdana;"&gt;But Dr. Dyer is one of the most inspirational speakers in the world... And when combined with James' fascinating, original take on the world, the result is riveting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 11px; font-family: Verdana;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; font-size: 13px; font-family: Verdana;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 11px; font-family: Verdana;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; font-size: 13px; font-family: Verdana;"&gt;Enjoy!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="23582865" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/altucher/Ep6_JAShow_Wayne_Dyer.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>56:05</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>It's a question many of us are too afraid to answer..
&amp;nbsp;
"Is this as good as it gets?"
Perhaps you feel that way from time to time. You get stuck in an unfulfilling job. You get stuck with a mortgage you can barely pay, in a house that didn't...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Ep. 5 Lewis Howes: The Millionaire Who Couldn't Read</title>
                    <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2014 17:40:03 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">1e39c1e871f385281e66dea18d306b19</guid>
                    <link>http://altucher.stansberry.libsynpro.com/ep-5-lewis-howes-the-millionaire-who-couldnt-read</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/2690996"/>
                    <description>&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 11px; font-size: 13px; font-family: Verdana;"&gt;You've heard the stories about college dropouts who go on to become billionaires... like Bill Gates, Steve Jobs, and Mark Zuckerburg...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 11px; font-size: 13px; font-family: Verdana;"&gt;And you might even know that 20% of America's millionaires never stepped foot on a college campus.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 11px; font-size: 13px; font-family: Verdana;"&gt;But how many guys have you heard of who read at a second grade level... yet go on to be millionaires?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 11px; font-size: 13px; font-family: Verdana;"&gt;My guess is none... but you're about to meet one.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 11px; font-size: 13px; font-family: Verdana;"&gt;His name is Lewis Howes, and he's this week's guest on the James Altucher Show, a radio show we recently helped to launch.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 11px; font-size: 13px; font-family: Verdana;"&gt;Lewis Howes' story is nothing short of amazing...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 11px; font-size: 13px; font-family: Verdana;"&gt;At age 10, he was 6'3". He described himself as a "gangly, skinny, ugly, acne kid, who couldn't read or write or do anything."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 11px; font-size: 13px; font-family: Verdana;"&gt;In the eighth grade, he could only read at a second-grade level. He cheated on every test in high school because he says that's the only way he could pass.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 11px; font-size: 13px; font-family: Verdana;"&gt;But Lewis' life changed dramatically after talking his way into college. He wanted to become a football player... and despite a series of major setbacks and injuries, he became a &lt;em&gt;two-time All-American&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 11px; font-size: 13px; font-family: Verdana;"&gt;Thing is... when it came time to leave college, the NFL didn't want him. He had no other skills. He was broke and depressed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 11px; font-size: 13px; font-family: Verdana;"&gt;By now, you might be wondering how listening to a former semi-pro football player can help you become more successful and wealthy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 11px; font-size: 13px; font-family: Verdana;"&gt;Turns out, a lot more than you'd think... Howes figured out an ingenious way to make a fortune. At one time, he was making an incredible $60,000 per hour.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 11px; font-size: 13px; font-family: Verdana;"&gt;This week, you'll hear the amazing story of Lewis Howes, who now travels the globe teaching people exactly how they can achieve their dreams.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 11px; font-size: 13px; font-family: Verdana;"&gt;Schools can't prep you for success anymore.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 11px; font-size: 13px; font-family: Verdana;"&gt;Today's millionaires prove that if schooling and traditional employment does not work for you, then you must figure out how to connect with people on a different level.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 11px; font-size: 13px; font-family: Verdana;"&gt;And Lewis teaches you exactly what you need to do to get there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 11px; font-size: 13px; font-family: Verdana;"&gt;He reveals the secret thing that people should &lt;span style="text-decoration: underline;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;never, ever&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; do when they're trying to get ahead. I was shocked because it's usually the first thing people think they SHOULD do!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 11px; font-size: 13px; font-family: Verdana;"&gt;He also reveals the question that he always asks during networking sessions. Lewis explains, "That simple question opened the door" to his future as a millionaire.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px 0px 11px; font-size: 13px; font-family: Verdana;"&gt;Like James Altucher, Lewis Howes is a quirky, interesting guy, who's become a huge success by thinking outside the box.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="30687777" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/altucher/JA-LewisHowe2.19.14.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:13:04</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>You've heard the stories about college dropouts who go on to become billionaires... like Bill Gates, Steve Jobs, and Mark Zuckerburg...
And you might even know that 20% of America's millionaires never stepped foot on a college campus.
But how many...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Ep. 4 Ylon Schwartz: A Poker Champion's Secret Revealed</title>
                    <pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2014 18:11:01 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">aa3ca2841c40e37e70e7497c63cc6edd</guid>
                    <link>http://altucher.stansberry.libsynpro.com/ep-4-ylon-schwartz-a-poker-champions-secret-revealed</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/2679299"/>
                    <description>&lt;p style="margin: 0px; font-size: 13px; font-family: Verdana;"&gt;On this week's show, James and Aaron Brabham chat with Ylon Schwartz: poker champion, chess master, and gamer extraordinaire.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; font-size: 13px; font-family: Verdana;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; font-size: 13px; font-family: Verdana;"&gt;He is without a doubt one of the most intriguing characters you're ever likely to encounter...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; font-size: 13px; font-family: Verdana;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; font-size: 13px; font-family: Verdana;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;College Dropout Who Has Never Had a Real Job Wins $8 Million in Cash at the Poker Table...&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; font-size: 13px; font-family: Verdana;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; font-size: 13px; font-family: Verdana;"&gt;If you watched the 2008 World Series of Poker, you may remember Ylon Schwartz and his trademark curly locks...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; font-size: 13px; font-family: Verdana;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; font-size: 13px; font-family: Verdana;"&gt;The day before the championship, Ylon was drowning in debt and in trouble with the law back in his hometown of New York City. From rock bottom, he redirected years of frustrations about money and women, channeling it towards winning the game...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; font-size: 13px; font-family: Verdana;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; font-size: 13px; font-family: Verdana;"&gt;... and walked out of the Las Vegas Rio Casino with a cool $3.7 million in his pocket.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; font-size: 13px; font-family: Verdana;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; font-size: 13px; font-family: Verdana;"&gt;In fact, Ylon has won an estimated $8 million in cash, just from playing poker. Not bad for a college dropout who has never held a job.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; font-size: 13px; font-family: Verdana;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0px; font-size: 13px; font-family: Verdana;"&gt;Today, he's one of the most widely recognized and well-respected poker players in the world.&lt;span style="font-size: 11px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="29084886" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/altucher/JAShow_Ep4.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:09:10</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>On this week's show, James and Aaron Brabham chat with Ylon Schwartz: poker champion, chess master, and gamer extraordinaire.
&amp;nbsp;
He is without a doubt one of the most intriguing characters you're ever likely to encounter...
&amp;nbsp;
College...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Ep. 3 A.J. Jacobs: A Biblical Experiment</title>
                    <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2014 17:02:44 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">5eda5a8662afbc2635805435e06589b2</guid>
                    <link>http://traffic.libsyn.com/altucher/Ep._3_AJ_Jacobs.mp3</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/2668071"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;!--[if gte mso 9]&gt;&lt;xml&gt;
 &lt;o:OfficeDocumentSettings&gt;
  &lt;o:AllowPNG/&gt;
 &lt;/o:OfficeDocumentSettings&gt;
&lt;/xml&gt;&lt;![endif]--&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal" style="margin-bottom: .0001pt; line-height: normal;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10.0pt; mso-bidi-font-size: 11.0pt; font-family: 'Verdana','sans-serif';"&gt;On this week's show, James' special guest is A.J. Jacobs, a journalist, lecturer, self-described human guinea pig and author of four &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.amazon.com/A.-J.-Jacobs/e/B000APL8HO"&gt;&lt;i style="mso-bidi-font-style: normal;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10.0pt; mso-bidi-font-size: 11.0pt; font-family: 'Verdana','sans-serif';"&gt;New York Times&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10.0pt; mso-bidi-font-size: 11.0pt; font-family: 'Verdana','sans-serif';"&gt; bestsellers&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10.0pt; mso-bidi-font-size: 11.0pt; font-family: 'Verdana','sans-serif';"&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal" style="margin-bottom: .0001pt; line-height: normal;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10.0pt; mso-bidi-font-size: 11.0pt; font-family: 'Verdana','sans-serif';"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal" style="margin-bottom: .0001pt; line-height: normal;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10.0pt; mso-bidi-font-size: 11.0pt; font-family: 'Verdana','sans-serif';"&gt;In this episode, he shares life-changing tips about how to improve your business, become healthier, and live better. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal" style="margin-bottom: .0001pt; line-height: normal;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10.0pt; mso-bidi-font-size: 11.0pt; font-family: 'Verdana','sans-serif';"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal" style="margin-bottom: .0001pt; line-height: normal;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10.0pt; mso-bidi-font-size: 11.0pt; font-family: 'Verdana','sans-serif';"&gt;You see, A.J. has spent years conducting the wackiest "experiments" we've ever heard of to see what he could learn. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal" style="margin-bottom: .0001pt; line-height: normal;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10.0pt; mso-bidi-font-size: 11.0pt; font-family: 'Verdana','sans-serif';"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal" style="margin-bottom: .0001pt; line-height: normal;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10.0pt; mso-bidi-font-size: 11.0pt; font-family: 'Verdana','sans-serif';"&gt;You won't believe the crazy things he has done!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal" style="margin-bottom: .0001pt; line-height: normal;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10.0pt; mso-bidi-font-size: 11.0pt; font-family: 'Verdana','sans-serif';"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal" style="margin-bottom: .0001pt; line-height: normal;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10.0pt; mso-bidi-font-size: 11.0pt; font-family: 'Verdana','sans-serif';"&gt;James and A.J. discuss how to generate great ideas... and the importance of exercising the "idea muscle" in your brain. The very act of generating 40 different ideas literally made A.J. millions of dollars. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal" style="margin-bottom: .0001pt; line-height: normal;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10.0pt; mso-bidi-font-size: 11.0pt; font-family: 'Verdana','sans-serif';"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal" style="margin-bottom: .0001pt; line-height: normal;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10.0pt; mso-bidi-font-size: 11.0pt; font-family: 'Verdana','sans-serif';"&gt;Other things you'll learn when you listen to this show include:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal" style="margin-bottom: .0001pt; line-height: normal;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10.0pt; mso-bidi-font-size: 11.0pt; font-family: 'Verdana','sans-serif';"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal" style="margin-bottom: .0001pt; line-height: normal;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10.0pt; mso-bidi-font-size: 11.0pt; font-family: 'Verdana','sans-serif';"&gt;** One simple exercise that will make you feel more confident and optimistic. George Washington used this tip to create an aura of authority... &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal" style="margin-bottom: .0001pt; line-height: normal;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10.0pt; mso-bidi-font-size: 11.0pt; font-family: 'Verdana','sans-serif';"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal" style="margin-bottom: .0001pt; line-height: normal;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10.0pt; mso-bidi-font-size: 11.0pt; font-family: 'Verdana','sans-serif';"&gt;** How to reframe the boring parts of your job as something creative. If you aren't satisfied living in a cubicle, you need to hear this... &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal" style="margin-bottom: .0001pt; line-height: normal;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10.0pt; mso-bidi-font-size: 11.0pt; font-family: 'Verdana','sans-serif';"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal" style="margin-bottom: .0001pt; line-height: normal;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10.0pt; mso-bidi-font-size: 11.0pt; font-family: 'Verdana','sans-serif';"&gt;**What you should do within the first three seconds of meeting someone to overcome shyness... &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal" style="margin-bottom: .0001pt; line-height: normal;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10.0pt; mso-bidi-font-size: 11.0pt; font-family: 'Verdana','sans-serif';"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal" style="margin-bottom: .0001pt; line-height: normal;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10.0pt; mso-bidi-font-size: 11.0pt; font-family: 'Verdana','sans-serif';"&gt;** Why overthinking is a problem... and how you can stop your brain from ruling your life... &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal" style="margin-bottom: .0001pt; line-height: normal;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10.0pt; mso-bidi-font-size: 11.0pt; font-family: 'Verdana','sans-serif';"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal" style="margin-bottom: .0001pt; line-height: normal;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10.0pt; mso-bidi-font-size: 11.0pt; font-family: 'Verdana','sans-serif';"&gt;** A.J.'s proven technique for using Facebook to fix almost any problem... &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal" style="margin-bottom: .0001pt; line-height: normal;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10.0pt; mso-bidi-font-size: 11.0pt; font-family: 'Verdana','sans-serif';"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal" style="margin-bottom: .0001pt; line-height: normal;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10.0pt; mso-bidi-font-size: 11.0pt; font-family: 'Verdana','sans-serif';"&gt;** How he's using genetic testing, of all things, to grow his business... &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal" style="margin-bottom: .0001pt; line-height: normal;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10.0pt; mso-bidi-font-size: 11.0pt; font-family: 'Verdana','sans-serif';"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal" style="margin-bottom: .0001pt; line-height: normal;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10.0pt; mso-bidi-font-size: 11.0pt; font-family: 'Verdana','sans-serif';"&gt;Like James Altucher, A.J. Jacobs is a quirky, interesting guy, who has become a huge success by thinking outside the box. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="23463469" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/altucher/Ep._3_AJ_Jacobs.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>55:52</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>On this week's show, James' special guest is A.J. Jacobs, a journalist, lecturer, self-described human guinea pig and author of four New York Times bestsellers.
&amp;nbsp;
In this episode, he shares life-changing tips about how to improve your business,...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Ep. 2 Gary Vaynerchuk: Millionaire by Age 35</title>
                    <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2014 18:22:18 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">77e6d124ed8832edf1b6d1a720e144fc</guid>
                    <link>http://traffic.libsyn.com/altucher/Ep2_JAShow.mp3</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/2657210"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;!--[if gte mso 9]&gt;&lt;xml&gt;
 &lt;o:OfficeDocumentSettings&gt;
  &lt;o:AllowPNG/&gt;
 &lt;/o:OfficeDocumentSettings&gt;
&lt;/xml&gt;&lt;![endif]--&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal" style="margin-bottom: .0001pt; line-height: normal;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10.0pt; mso-bidi-font-size: 11.0pt; font-family: 'Verdana','sans-serif';"&gt;On this week's show, which you can now access free of charge, James covered several interesting, unique, and useful topics... which I guarantee you won't hear anywhere else.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal" style="margin-bottom: .0001pt; line-height: normal;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10.0pt; mso-bidi-font-size: 11.0pt; font-family: 'Verdana','sans-serif';"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal" style="margin-bottom: .0001pt; line-height: normal;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10.0pt; mso-bidi-font-size: 11.0pt; font-family: 'Verdana','sans-serif';"&gt;For example... &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal" style="margin-bottom: .0001pt; line-height: normal;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10.0pt; mso-bidi-font-size: 11.0pt; font-family: 'Verdana','sans-serif';"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal" style="margin-bottom: .0001pt; line-height: normal;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10.0pt; mso-bidi-font-size: 11.0pt; font-family: 'Verdana','sans-serif';"&gt;*He shares his idea of the absolute best place to meet women... and how to avoid feeling embarrassed if she says no to your invitation. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal" style="margin-bottom: .0001pt; line-height: normal;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10.0pt; mso-bidi-font-size: 11.0pt; font-family: 'Verdana','sans-serif';"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal" style="margin-bottom: .0001pt; line-height: normal;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10.0pt; mso-bidi-font-size: 11.0pt; font-family: 'Verdana','sans-serif';"&gt;*He discusses the 2 reasons traditional jobs are a scam... why he tries to avoid working in the workplace... and the ways you can avoid having a regular ho-hum job... &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal" style="margin-bottom: .0001pt; line-height: normal;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10.0pt; mso-bidi-font-size: 11.0pt; font-family: 'Verdana','sans-serif';"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal" style="margin-bottom: .0001pt; line-height: normal;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10.0pt; mso-bidi-font-size: 11.0pt; font-family: 'Verdana','sans-serif';"&gt;*And he explains why there has been such a dramatic change in the way we interact with total strangers... how that impacts the way we sell our goods... and how to use this change to your benefit... &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal" style="margin-bottom: .0001pt; line-height: normal;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10.0pt; mso-bidi-font-size: 11.0pt; font-family: 'Verdana','sans-serif';"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal" style="margin-bottom: .0001pt; line-height: normal;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10.0pt; mso-bidi-font-size: 11.0pt; font-family: 'Verdana','sans-serif';"&gt;Altucher has an interesting take on this subject and you won't want to miss it!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal" style="margin-bottom: .0001pt; line-height: normal;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10.0pt; mso-bidi-font-size: 11.0pt; font-family: 'Verdana','sans-serif';"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal" style="margin-bottom: .0001pt; line-height: normal;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10.0pt; mso-bidi-font-size: 11.0pt; font-family: 'Verdana','sans-serif';"&gt;Then James brings on his special guest... &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal" style="margin-bottom: .0001pt; line-height: normal;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10.0pt; mso-bidi-font-size: 11.0pt; font-family: 'Verdana','sans-serif';"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal" style="margin-bottom: .0001pt; line-height: normal;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10.0pt; mso-bidi-font-size: 11.0pt; font-family: 'Verdana','sans-serif';"&gt;James' good friend Gary Vaynerchuk, author of a &lt;i style="mso-bidi-font-style: normal;"&gt;New York Times&lt;/i&gt; best-selling book: &lt;b style="mso-bidi-font-weight: normal;"&gt;&lt;i style="mso-bidi-font-style: normal;"&gt;&lt;span style="background: yellow; mso-highlight: yellow;"&gt;&lt;span style="background-color: #ffffff;"&gt;Jab, Jab, Jab, Right &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal" style="margin-bottom: .0001pt; line-height: normal;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: 'Verdana','sans-serif'; background-color: #ffffff;"&gt;&lt;b style="mso-bidi-font-weight: normal;"&gt;&lt;i style="mso-bidi-font-style: normal;"&gt;&lt;span style="background-image: none; background-repeat: repeat; background-attachment: scroll; background-position: 0% 0%; background-clip: border-box; background-origin: padding-box; background-size: auto auto;"&gt;Hook&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span style="background-image: none; background-repeat: repeat; background-attachment: scroll; background-position: 0% 0%; background-clip: border-box; background-origin: padding-box; background-size: auto auto;"&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal" style="margin-bottom: .0001pt; line-height: normal;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10pt; font-family: 'Verdana','sans-serif'; background-color: #ffffff;"&gt;&lt;span style="background-image: none; background-repeat: repeat; background-attachment: scroll; background-position: 0% 0%; background-clip: border-box; background-origin: padding-box; background-size: auto auto;"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="23407739" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/altucher/Ep2_JAShow.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>55:39</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>On this week's show, which you can now access free of charge, James covered several interesting, unique, and useful topics... which I guarantee you won't hear anywhere else.
&amp;nbsp;
For example... 
&amp;nbsp;
*He shares his idea of the absolute best place...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Ep. 1 Tucker Max: Buckle Up, We've Launched</title>
                    <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2014 19:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">6912e784085cd201cf76af633e56fd0e</guid>
                    <link>http://traffic.libsyn.com/altucher/Ep1JAShow.mp3</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/2644922"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal" style="margin-bottom: .0001pt; line-height: normal;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10.0pt; mso-bidi-font-size: 11.0pt; font-family: 'Verdana','sans-serif'; mso-bidi-font-family: Cambria;"&gt;On James' very first show, he covers several really interesting, unique, and useful stories, which I guarantee you won't hear anywhere else.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal" style="margin-bottom: .0001pt; line-height: normal;"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;!--[if gte mso 9]&gt;&lt;xml&gt;
 &lt;o:OfficeDocumentSettings&gt;
  &lt;o:TargetScreenSize&gt;800x600&lt;/o:TargetScreenSize&gt;
 &lt;/o:OfficeDocumentSettings&gt;
&lt;/xml&gt;&lt;![endif]--&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal" style="margin-bottom: .0001pt; line-height: normal;"&gt;&lt;!--[if gte mso 9]&gt;&lt;xml&gt;
 &lt;w:WordDocument&gt;
  &lt;w:View&gt;Normal&lt;/w:View&gt;
  &lt;w:Zoom&gt;0&lt;/w:Zoom&gt;
  &lt;w:TrackMoves/&gt;
  &lt;w:TrackFormatting/&gt;
  &lt;w:PunctuationKerning/&gt;
  &lt;w:ValidateAgainstSchemas/&gt;
  &lt;w:SaveIfXMLInvalid&gt;false&lt;/w:SaveIfXMLInvalid&gt;
  &lt;w:IgnoreMixedContent&gt;false&lt;/w:IgnoreMixedContent&gt;
  &lt;w:AlwaysShowPlaceholderText&gt;false&lt;/w:AlwaysShowPlaceholderText&gt;
  &lt;w:DoNotPromoteQF/&gt;
  &lt;w:LidThemeOther&gt;EN-US&lt;/w:LidThemeOther&gt;
  &lt;w:LidThemeAsian&gt;X-NONE&lt;/w:LidThemeAsian&gt;
  &lt;w:LidThemeComplexScript&gt;X-NONE&lt;/w:LidThemeComplexScript&gt;
  &lt;w:Compatibility&gt;
   &lt;w:BreakWrappedTables/&gt;
   &lt;w:SnapToGridInCell/&gt;
   &lt;w:WrapTextWithPunct/&gt;
   &lt;w:UseAsianBreakRules/&gt;
   &lt;w:DontGrowAutofit/&gt;
   &lt;w:SplitPgBreakAndParaMark/&gt;
   &lt;w:EnableOpenTypeKerning/&gt;
   &lt;w:DontFlipMirrorIndents/&gt;
   &lt;w:OverrideTableStyleHps/&gt;
  &lt;/w:Compatibility&gt;
  &lt;w:BrowserLevel&gt;MicrosoftInternetExplorer4&lt;/w:BrowserLevel&gt;
  &lt;m:mathPr&gt;
   &lt;m:mathFont m:val="Cambria Math"/&gt;
   &lt;m:brkBin m:val="before"/&gt;
   &lt;m:brkBinSub m:val="&amp;#45;-"/&gt;
   &lt;m:smallFrac m:val="off"/&gt;
   &lt;m:dispDef/&gt;
   &lt;m:lMargin m:val="0"/&gt;
   &lt;m:rMargin m:val="0"/&gt;
   &lt;m:defJc m:val="centerGroup"/&gt;
   &lt;m:wrapIndent m:val="1440"/&gt;
   &lt;m:intLim m:val="subSup"/&gt;
   &lt;m:naryLim m:val="undOvr"/&gt;
  &lt;/m:mathPr&gt;&lt;/w:WordDocument&gt;
&lt;/xml&gt;&lt;![endif]--&gt;&lt;!--[if gte mso 9]&gt;&lt;xml&gt;
 &lt;w:LatentStyles DefLockedState="false" DefUnhideWhenUsed="true"
  DefSemiHidden="true" DefQFormat="false" DefPriority="99"
  LatentStyleCount="267"&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="0" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" QFormat="true" Name="Normal"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="9" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" QFormat="true" Name="heading 1"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="9" QFormat="true" Name="heading 2"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="9" QFormat="true" Name="heading 3"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="9" QFormat="true" Name="heading 4"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="9" QFormat="true" Name="heading 5"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="9" QFormat="true" Name="heading 6"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="9" QFormat="true" Name="heading 7"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="9" QFormat="true" Name="heading 8"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="9" QFormat="true" Name="heading 9"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="39" Name="toc 1"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="39" Name="toc 2"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="39" Name="toc 3"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="39" Name="toc 4"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="39" Name="toc 5"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="39" Name="toc 6"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="39" Name="toc 7"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="39" Name="toc 8"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="39" Name="toc 9"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="35" QFormat="true" Name="caption"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="10" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" QFormat="true" Name="Title"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="1" Name="Default Paragraph Font"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="11" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" QFormat="true" Name="Subtitle"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="22" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" QFormat="true" Name="Strong"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="20" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" QFormat="true" Name="Emphasis"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="59" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" Name="Table Grid"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" UnhideWhenUsed="false" Name="Placeholder Text"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="1" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" QFormat="true" Name="No Spacing"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="60" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" Name="Light Shading"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="61" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" Name="Light List"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="62" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" Name="Light Grid"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="63" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" Name="Medium Shading 1"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="64" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" Name="Medium Shading 2"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="65" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" Name="Medium List 1"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="66" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" Name="Medium List 2"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="67" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" Name="Medium Grid 1"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="68" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" Name="Medium Grid 2"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="69" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" Name="Medium Grid 3"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="70" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" Name="Dark List"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="71" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" Name="Colorful Shading"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="72" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" Name="Colorful List"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="73" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" Name="Colorful Grid"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="60" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" Name="Light Shading Accent 1"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="61" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" Name="Light List Accent 1"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="62" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" Name="Light Grid Accent 1"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="63" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" Name="Medium Shading 1 Accent 1"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="64" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" Name="Medium Shading 2 Accent 1"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="65" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" Name="Medium List 1 Accent 1"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" UnhideWhenUsed="false" Name="Revision"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="34" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" QFormat="true" Name="List Paragraph"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="29" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" QFormat="true" Name="Quote"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="30" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" QFormat="true" Name="Intense Quote"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="66" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" Name="Medium List 2 Accent 1"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="67" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" Name="Medium Grid 1 Accent 1"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="68" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" Name="Medium Grid 2 Accent 1"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="69" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" Name="Medium Grid 3 Accent 1"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="70" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" Name="Dark List Accent 1"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="71" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" Name="Colorful Shading Accent 1"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="72" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" Name="Colorful List Accent 1"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="73" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" Name="Colorful Grid Accent 1"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="60" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" Name="Light Shading Accent 2"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="61" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" Name="Light List Accent 2"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="62" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" Name="Light Grid Accent 2"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="63" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" Name="Medium Shading 1 Accent 2"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="64" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" Name="Medium Shading 2 Accent 2"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="65" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" Name="Medium List 1 Accent 2"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="66" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" Name="Medium List 2 Accent 2"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="67" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" Name="Medium Grid 1 Accent 2"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="68" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" Name="Medium Grid 2 Accent 2"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="69" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" Name="Medium Grid 3 Accent 2"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="70" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" Name="Dark List Accent 2"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="71" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" Name="Colorful Shading Accent 2"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="72" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" Name="Colorful List Accent 2"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="73" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" Name="Colorful Grid Accent 2"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="60" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" Name="Light Shading Accent 3"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="61" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" Name="Light List Accent 3"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="62" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" Name="Light Grid Accent 3"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="63" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" Name="Medium Shading 1 Accent 3"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="64" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" Name="Medium Shading 2 Accent 3"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="65" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" Name="Medium List 1 Accent 3"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="66" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" Name="Medium List 2 Accent 3"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="67" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" Name="Medium Grid 1 Accent 3"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="68" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" Name="Medium Grid 2 Accent 3"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="69" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" Name="Medium Grid 3 Accent 3"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="70" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" Name="Dark List Accent 3"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="71" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" Name="Colorful Shading Accent 3"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="72" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" Name="Colorful List Accent 3"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="73" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" Name="Colorful Grid Accent 3"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="60" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" Name="Light Shading Accent 4"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="61" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" Name="Light List Accent 4"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="62" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" Name="Light Grid Accent 4"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="63" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" Name="Medium Shading 1 Accent 4"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="64" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" Name="Medium Shading 2 Accent 4"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="65" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" Name="Medium List 1 Accent 4"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="66" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" Name="Medium List 2 Accent 4"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="67" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" Name="Medium Grid 1 Accent 4"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="68" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" Name="Medium Grid 2 Accent 4"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="69" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" Name="Medium Grid 3 Accent 4"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="70" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" Name="Dark List Accent 4"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="71" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" Name="Colorful Shading Accent 4"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="72" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" Name="Colorful List Accent 4"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="73" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" Name="Colorful Grid Accent 4"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="60" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" Name="Light Shading Accent 5"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="61" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" Name="Light List Accent 5"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="62" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" Name="Light Grid Accent 5"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="63" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" Name="Medium Shading 1 Accent 5"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="64" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" Name="Medium Shading 2 Accent 5"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="65" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" Name="Medium List 1 Accent 5"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="66" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" Name="Medium List 2 Accent 5"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="67" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" Name="Medium Grid 1 Accent 5"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="68" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" Name="Medium Grid 2 Accent 5"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="69" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" Name="Medium Grid 3 Accent 5"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="70" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" Name="Dark List Accent 5"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="71" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" Name="Colorful Shading Accent 5"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="72" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" Name="Colorful List Accent 5"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="73" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" Name="Colorful Grid Accent 5"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="60" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" Name="Light Shading Accent 6"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="61" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" Name="Light List Accent 6"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="62" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" Name="Light Grid Accent 6"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="63" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" Name="Medium Shading 1 Accent 6"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="64" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" Name="Medium Shading 2 Accent 6"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="65" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" Name="Medium List 1 Accent 6"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="66" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" Name="Medium List 2 Accent 6"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="67" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" Name="Medium Grid 1 Accent 6"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="68" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" Name="Medium Grid 2 Accent 6"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="69" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" Name="Medium Grid 3 Accent 6"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="70" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" Name="Dark List Accent 6"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="71" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" Name="Colorful Shading Accent 6"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="72" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" Name="Colorful List Accent 6"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="73" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" Name="Colorful Grid Accent 6"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="19" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" QFormat="true" Name="Subtle Emphasis"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="21" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" QFormat="true" Name="Intense Emphasis"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="31" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" QFormat="true" Name="Subtle Reference"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="32" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" QFormat="true" Name="Intense Reference"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="33" SemiHidden="false"
   UnhideWhenUsed="false" QFormat="true" Name="Book Title"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="37" Name="Bibliography"/&gt;
  &lt;w:LsdException Locked="false" Priority="39" QFormat="true" Name="TOC Heading"/&gt;
 &lt;/w:LatentStyles&gt;
&lt;/xml&gt;&lt;![endif]--&gt;&lt;!--[if gte mso 10]&gt;
&lt;style&gt;
 /* Style Definitions */
 table.MsoNormalTable
	{mso-style-name:"Table Normal";
	mso-tstyle-rowband-size:0;
	mso-tstyle-colband-size:0;
	mso-style-noshow:yes;
	mso-style-priority:99;
	mso-style-parent:"";
	mso-padding-alt:0in 5.4pt 0in 5.4pt;
	mso-para-margin:0in;
	mso-para-margin-bottom:.0001pt;
	mso-pagination:widow-orphan;
	font-size:10.0pt;
	font-family:"Calibri","sans-serif";}
&lt;/style&gt;
&lt;![endif]--&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10.0pt; mso-bidi-font-size: 11.0pt; font-family: 'Verdana','sans-serif'; mso-bidi-font-family: Cambria;"&gt;Then James brings on his special guest for Show #1... &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal" style="margin-bottom: .0001pt; line-height: normal;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10.0pt; mso-bidi-font-size: 11.0pt; font-family: 'Verdana','sans-serif'; mso-bidi-font-family: Cambria;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal" style="margin-bottom: .0001pt; line-height: normal;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10.0pt; mso-bidi-font-size: 11.0pt; font-family: 'Verdana','sans-serif'; mso-bidi-font-family: Cambria;"&gt;Maybe you've heard of Tucker Max. Maybe not.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal" style="margin-bottom: .0001pt; line-height: normal;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10.0pt; mso-bidi-font-size: 11.0pt; font-family: 'Verdana','sans-serif'; mso-bidi-font-family: Cambria;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal" style="margin-bottom: .0001pt; line-height: normal;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10.0pt; mso-bidi-font-size: 11.0pt; font-family: 'Verdana','sans-serif'; mso-bidi-font-family: Cambria;"&gt;Tucker is an entertaining guy, who figured out a way to basically reinvent the entire book-publishing industry. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="22355999" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/altucher/Ep1JAShow.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>53:13</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>On James' very first show, he covers several really interesting, unique, and useful stories, which I guarantee you won't hear anywhere else.

Then James brings on his special guest for Show #1... 
&amp;nbsp;
Maybe you've heard of Tucker Max. Maybe...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Robert Greene: How to Become a Master of What You Love</title>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2014 19:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">08091c21d0d17e89164a42f63edf209d</guid>
                    <link>http://traffic.libsyn.com/altucher/Ep116_SARadioClipWithMusic.mp3</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/2629555"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal" style="margin-bottom: .0001pt; line-height: normal;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10.0pt; mso-bidi-font-size: 11.0pt; font-family: 'Verdana','sans-serif';"&gt;Robert Greene, best-selling author of &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.amazon.com/gp/product/014312417X/ref=as_li_ss_tl?ie=UTF8&amp;amp;camp=1789&amp;amp;creative=390957&amp;amp;creativeASIN=014312417X&amp;amp;linkCode=as2&amp;amp;tag=stansradio-20" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10.0pt; mso-bidi-font-size: 11.0pt; font-family: 'Verdana','sans-serif';"&gt;Mastery&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 10.0pt; mso-bidi-font-size: 11.0pt; font-family: 'Verdana','sans-serif';"&gt;, joins &lt;i style="mso-bidi-font-style: normal;"&gt;The James Altucher Show.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="14496354" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/altucher/Ep116_SARadioClipWithMusic.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>34:26</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Robert Greene, best-selling author of Mastery, joins The James Altucher Show.</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Greg Zuckerman: The Future of Fracking</title>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2014 14:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">c8964ea0e40c6e9321c102684e8b647b</guid>
                    <link>http://traffic.libsyn.com/altucher/Ep113_SARadioClipWithMusic.mp3</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/2629073"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;This week, James Altucher interviews Greg Zuckerman, author of &lt;i&gt;The Frackers&lt;/i&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="15767182" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/altucher/Ep113_SARadioClipWithMusic.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>37:28</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>This week, James Altucher interviews Greg Zuckerman, author of The Frackers.</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>James Altucher &amp; Marc EckÅ: Secrets to Success</title>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2014 13:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">167f3eaeb957b16714871fce337edf73</guid>
                    <link>http://traffic.libsyn.com/altucher/Ep102_SARadioClipWithMusic.mp3</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/2629024"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;This week, we have James Altucher interviews with Marc EckÅ, author of the new best-seller, &lt;a href="http://www.amazon.com/gp/product/1451685300/ref=as_li_ss_tl?ie=UTF8&amp;amp;camp=1789&amp;amp;creative=390957&amp;amp;creativeASIN=1451685300&amp;amp;linkCode=as2&amp;amp;tag=stansradio-20"&gt;&lt;i&gt;Unlabel: Selling You Without Selling Out&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;i&gt;.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="22450514" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/altucher/Ep102_SARadioClipWithMusic.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>53:21</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>This week, we have James Altucher interviews with Marc EckÅ, author of the new best-seller, Unlabel: Selling You Without Selling Out.</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>James Altucher and Ryan Holiday: Letâ€™s Make the News Up</title>
                    <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2014 20:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">8da3307551a1e7383e9894be52a075cb</guid>
                    <link>http://traffic.libsyn.com/altucher/Ep86_SARadioClipWithMusic.mp3</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/2625665"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;This week, James Altucher interviews the bestselling author of &lt;a href="http://www.amazon.com/gp/product/1591846285/ref=as_li_ss_tl?ie=UTF8&amp;amp;camp=1789&amp;amp;creative=390957&amp;amp;creativeASIN=1591846285&amp;amp;linkCode=as2&amp;amp;tag=stansradio-20"&gt;&lt;i&gt;Trust Me I&amp;rsquo;m Lying: Confessions of a Media Manipulator&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;i&gt;,&lt;/i&gt; Ryan Holiday.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;James and Ryan talk about what makes a book a best-seller, and how to market yourself and your work. Ryan tells us what it means to be a media manipulator. In a world where blogs control and distort the news, his job was to control blogs &amp;ndash; as much as any one person can. And he does this better than anyone else...&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="23865442" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/altucher/Ep86_SARadioClipWithMusic.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>56:47</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>This week, James Altucher interviews the bestselling author of Trust Me I&amp;rsquo;m Lying: Confessions of a Media Manipulator, Ryan Holiday.
James and Ryan talk about what makes a book a best-seller, and how to market yourself and your work. Ryan tells...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Taking Back America</title>
                    <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2014 18:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">04cab338abe2718eac0034b0b546eee3</guid>
                    <link>http://traffic.libsyn.com/altucher/Ep82_SARadioClipWithMusic.mp3</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/2625570"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;James, the editor of the widely read letter, &lt;i&gt;The Altucher Confidential&lt;/i&gt;, and author of the new blockbuster hit, &lt;a href="http://www.amazon.com/gp/product/1490313370/ref=as_li_ss_tl?ie=UTF8&amp;amp;camp=1789&amp;amp;creative=390957&amp;amp;creativeASIN=1490313370&amp;amp;linkCode=as2&amp;amp;tag=stansradio-20"&gt;&lt;i&gt;Choose Yourself&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;,&lt;i&gt; &lt;/i&gt;talks with Glenn &amp;ldquo;Kane&amp;rdquo; Jacobs.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="26155635" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/altucher/Ep82_SARadioClipWithMusic.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:02:14</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>James, the editor of the widely read letter, The Altucher Confidential, and author of the new blockbuster hit, Choose Yourself, talks with Glenn &amp;ldquo;Kane&amp;rdquo; Jacobs.</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>James Altucher Live and Unplugged</title>
                    <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2014 16:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">c9792e4c3bdf49b6e5f9258790095bb6</guid>
                    <link>http://traffic.libsyn.com/altucher/Ep190-SAInvestorRadioClipWithMusic.mp3</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/2625254"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;James Altucher talks about his new best-selling book, &lt;i style="mso-bidi-font-style: normal;"&gt;Choose Yourself&lt;/i&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="9322081" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/altucher/Ep190-SAInvestorRadioClipWithMusic.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>22:10</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>James Altucher talks about his new best-selling book, Choose Yourself.</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>The Best Guest Ever</title>
                    <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2014 15:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">951f06b536817eddd923feff00a66911</guid>
                    <link>http://traffic.libsyn.com/altucher/Ep67_SARadioClipWithMusic.mp3</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/2625162"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;James Altucher proves to be one of our best guests as he and Porter Stansberry break down the markets.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="16304608" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/altucher/Ep67_SARadioClipWithMusic.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>38:47</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>James Altucher proves to be one of our best guests as he and Porter Stansberry break down the markets.</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Why College Is a Waste of Money</title>
                    <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2014 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">8635627060a60ef0b56fb7fdf3eb1730</guid>
                    <link>http://traffic.libsyn.com/altucher/Ep34_SARadio_ClipWithMusic.mp3</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/2622876"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0in 0in 10pt;" class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: small;" size="3"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: Calibri;" face="Calibri"&gt;On James Altucher&amp;rsquo;s first visit to Stansberry Radio, recorded back on August 9, 2012, he sets the stage for what&amp;rsquo;s to come.&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0in 0in 10pt; mso-pagination: none; mso-layout-grid-align: none;" class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: small;" size="3"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: Calibri;" face="Calibri"&gt;For the very first time to give our audience a look into why we consider &lt;span style="mso-bidi-font-family: Cambria;"&gt;James one of the most interesting people we know.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: 'Georgia','serif'; mso-bidi-font-family: Cambria;"&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0in 0in 10pt;" class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: small;" size="3"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: Calibri;" face="Calibri"&gt;In this first show, he talks about why he believes college is a real waste of money.&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="margin: 0in 0in 10pt;" class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: small;" size="3"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: Calibri;" face="Calibri"&gt;His analysis will get you re-thinking what you though you knew.&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="10287568" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/altucher/Ep34_SARadio_ClipWithMusic.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>24:26</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>On James Altucher&amp;rsquo;s first visit to Stansberry Radio, recorded back on August 9, 2012, he sets the stage for what&amp;rsquo;s to come.

For the very first time to give our audience a look into why we consider James one of the most interesting people...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
            </channel>
        </rss>
    </httpclient:body>
</httpclient:response>