<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<httpclient:response xmlns:httpclient="http://exist-db.org/xquery/httpclient" statusCode="200">
    <httpclient:headers>
        <httpclient:header name="Server" value="Apache/2.2.22 (Ubuntu)"/>
        <httpclient:header name="X-Libsyn-Host" value="web-engine3.libsyn.com"/>
        <httpclient:header name="Vary" value="Accept-Encoding"/>
        <httpclient:header name="Content-Type" value="application/rss+xml"/>
        <httpclient:header name="last-modified" value="Thu, 14 Aug 2014 20:29:42 GMT"/>
        <httpclient:header name="Content-Length" value="86784"/>
        <httpclient:header name="Accept-Ranges" value="bytes"/>
        <httpclient:header name="Date" value="Wed, 20 Aug 2014 09:18:39 GMT"/>
        <httpclient:header name="X-Varnish" value="2975478566 2927339096"/>
        <httpclient:header name="Age" value="478677"/>
        <httpclient:header name="Via" value="1.1 varnish"/>
        <httpclient:header name="Connection" value="close"/>
        <httpclient:header name="X-Cache" value="HIT"/>
    </httpclient:headers>
    <httpclient:body mimetype="application/rss+xml" type="xml">
        <rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:cc="http://web.resource.org/cc/" version="2.0">
            <channel>
                <atom:link href="http://advisorsoption.optionsinsider.libsynpro.com/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
                <title>The Advisors Option</title>
                <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2014 20:03:38 +0000</pubDate>
                <lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2014 20:29:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
                <generator>Libsyn WebEngine 2.0</generator>
                <link>http://www.theoptionsinsider.com/RADIO</link>
                <language>en</language>
                <copyright>© 2014 The Options Insider Incorporated</copyright>
                <docs>http://www.theoptionsinsider.com/RADIO</docs>
                <managingEditor>info@theoptionsinsider.com (info@theoptionsinsider.com)</managingEditor>
                <description>Simple diversification is no longer enough to shield the assets under your management. Registered investment advisors, financial planners and asset managers need a new weapon in their war on risk. Welcome to The Advisors Option  - the only program designed to arm busy advisors with the information necessary to properly manage risk in this volatile environment. From options education, trading strategies and tips to options industry news and interviews with leading advisors, you will find it all on The Advisors Option. </description>
                <image>
                    <url>http://assets.libsyn.com/content/4308415.jpg</url>
                    <title>The Advisors Option</title>
                    <link>http://www.theoptionsinsider.com/RADIO</link>
                </image>
                <itunes:author>The Options Insider Radio Network</itunes:author>
                <itunes:keywords>advisor,asset,calls,education,financial,generation,income,manager,option,options,planner,planning,portfolio,protection,puts,trading</itunes:keywords>
                <itunes:category text="Business">
                    <itunes:category text="Investing"/>
                </itunes:category>
                <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/4308415.jpg"/>
                <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
                <itunes:owner>
                    <itunes:name>The Options Insider Inc.</itunes:name>
                    <itunes:email>info@TheOptionsInsider.com</itunes:email>
                </itunes:owner>
                <itunes:summary>Simple diversification is no longer enough to shield the assets under your management. Registered investment advisors, financial planners and asset managers need a new weapon in their war on risk. Welcome to The Advisors Option  - the only program designed to arm busy advisors with the information necessary to properly manage risk in this volatile environment. From options education and trading strategies to practical tips, industry news and interviews with leading advisors, you will find it all on The Advisors Option.</itunes:summary>
                <itunes:subtitle>The Premier Options Program for Financial Advisors, Planners and Asset Managers</itunes:subtitle>
                <item>
                    <title>Advisors Option 21: Options for Protecting Profits</title>
                    <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2014 20:03:38 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">3310f21cca12b309023407fcf0575355</guid>
                    <link>http://traffic.libsyn.com/advisorsoption/AdvisorsOption21.mp3</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/7459588"/>
                    <description>&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;Advisors Option 21: Options for Protecting Profits&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;Options 101: Many clients are sitting on gains in their portfolios right now and are rightfully concerned about protecting them. Selling the assets with gains is a sure bet but eliminates future upside potential. This is an ideal use case for options.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;Basic hedging strategies:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li class="MsoNormal"&gt;Protective put: the basic defensive play.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="MsoNormal"&gt;Put spread: ideal for protecting gains due to limited outlay.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="MsoNormal"&gt;Collar: the holy grail of options positions for advisors.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="MsoNormal"&gt;Ratio spreads/back spreads: ratios are tempting but can add risk to a portfolio. Back spreads may be more appropriate for some experienced.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="MsoNormal"&gt;Hedging an individual asset is relatively straightforward:&amp;nbsp;simply implement the hedging strategy in the product you want to protect.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="MsoNormal"&gt;Hedging a broad portfolio is a little more difficult&amp;nbsp;and requires determining the beta of the portfolio and the appropriate number of shares of the index product to hedge as result. Any tools or platform recommendations to assist with this process?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;Listener Mail: Listener questions and comments&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li class="MsoNormal"&gt;Question from Tyler Madison:&amp;nbsp;I&amp;rsquo;m studying to become a CFA in Virginia. Your program has been tremendously helpful in preparing me for any options components of the exam. It has also armed me with potential options strategies to use for my clients. Thank you for this great content. You could really charge for this. If I may I&amp;rsquo;d like to ask a question about open interest. &amp;nbsp;I see this mentioned quite frequently by options analysts. What impact does open interest play in the options market - does an option with high open interest behave differently than an option with low open interest? Is this something I should pay attention to when trading options for my clients or is this not important? Thanks again for all of your insight - Tyler.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="MsoNormal"&gt;Question from J. Schaw, Ontario:&amp;nbsp;can the advisors options hosts recommend any good listed products that generate options income? I like the strategies you discuss on the show but simply don&amp;rsquo;t have time to manage all the strikes and such for my people. Available in Canada is obviously a big plus for me.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="60736433" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/advisorsoption/AdvisorsOption21.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:03:11</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Advisors Option 21: Options for Protecting Profits
Options 101: Many clients are sitting on gains in their portfolios right now and are rightfully concerned about protecting them. Selling the assets with gains is a sure bet but eliminates future...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Advisors Option 20: Volatility and Options</title>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2014 18:59:55 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">181df41cb6601a7e98ca3111bc1ba372</guid>
                    <link>http://traffic.libsyn.com/advisorsoption/AdvisorsOption20.mp3</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/7336161"/>
                    <description>&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;Advisors Option 20: Volatility and Options&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;In this episode, Mark and Randy are joined by Joe Cusick, Vice President of Wealth and Asset Management at MoneyBlock.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;Options 101: &amp;ldquo;Low VIX&amp;rdquo; is all over the financial media these days. Which makes it an excellent time to review the relationship between volatility &amp;amp; options. Haven&amp;rsquo;t discussed volatility on the program since Feb 2013 and the VIX products since October 2013 so we&amp;rsquo;ll review the following topics:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li class="MsoNormal"&gt;What is implied volatility?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="MsoNormal"&gt;Difference between realized and implied volatility?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="MsoNormal"&gt;How does high and low implied volatility impact options pricing?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="MsoNormal"&gt;If you trade options for your clients do you want high or low volatility?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="MsoNormal"&gt;What does it mean to have a &amp;ldquo;low VIX&amp;rdquo;? Is this level of implied volatility actually low?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="MsoNormal"&gt;Should advisors use VIX options to hedge their client&amp;rsquo;s portfolios?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;The Buzz: Credit unions help advisers expand use of options:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;Listener Mail: Listener questions and comments&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li class="MsoNormal"&gt;Question from Charlie Durant -&amp;nbsp;love the advisors show. Can you guys recommend a good tool or platform that will help me roll covered calls on my spy and individual equity positions more effectively? Right now I&amp;rsquo;m pretty much running a spreadsheet for my clients and then manually trading in and out of each position. Seems like there should be a better or easier way.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="MsoNormal"&gt;Question from Firestar -&amp;nbsp;can I&amp;nbsp;use VIX options in my IRA accounts or are futures options banned due to leverage?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="58737746" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/advisorsoption/AdvisorsOption20.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:01:06</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Advisors Option 20: Volatility and Options
In this episode, Mark and Randy are joined by Joe Cusick, Vice President of Wealth and Asset Management at MoneyBlock.
&amp;nbsp;
Options 101: &amp;ldquo;Low VIX&amp;rdquo; is all over the financial media these days....</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Advisors Option 19: Pension Problems and PUT Writes</title>
                    <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2014 18:20:58 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">cb118245c4d7f5428f35443160c9386c</guid>
                    <link>http://traffic.libsyn.com/advisorsoption/AdvisorsOption19.mp3</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/7228224"/>
                    <description>&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;Advisors Option 19: Pension Problems and PUT Writes&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;The Buzz: News out of China: OIC, Shanghai Stock Exchange content licensing agreement. Pensions seek bond diversification. Report: UK pensions miss out on returns. Chuck likes index funds. Retail investors not afraid of equity markets. Low VIX: what does it mean for volatility?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;Listener Mail: Your comments and questions&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Symbol;mso-fareast-font-family:Symbol;mso-bidi-font-family:
Symbol"&gt;&amp;middot;&lt;span style="font-size: 7pt; font-family: 'Times New Roman';"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;Question from Neil Staffenberg: thank you for this program. It is very informative. I&amp;rsquo;ve heard you mention SMAs on this program in the past. I&amp;rsquo;m not familiar with this term. Can you explain what you are referring to and the significance it has for the advisor community.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Symbol;mso-fareast-font-family:Symbol;mso-bidi-font-family:
Symbol"&gt;&amp;middot;&lt;span style="font-size: 7pt; font-family: 'Times New Roman';"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;Question from Avow: what do the hosts think of recent claims from advisor-centric firms like Charles Schwab that the market is rigged against individual investors? Should i be instructing my advisor to move me to cash? Is purchasing a put sufficient protection to my broad portfolio or are the options market rigged against me as well?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Symbol;mso-fareast-font-family:Symbol;mso-bidi-font-family:
Symbol"&gt;&amp;middot;&lt;span style="font-size: 7pt; font-family: 'Times New Roman';"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;Question from Tim Nichols, Fredericksburg, VA - can you provide an overview of the CBOE put write index. The BXM has been discussed widely but i haven&amp;rsquo;t come across much discussion or analysis on this sister product. From all the research I&amp;rsquo;ve encountered the product appears to perform quite well. It seems that structured products that include automation are the preferred tools for many financial advisors and planners. Would the panel recommend the put write index as a viable alternative for advisors looking to add options to their portfolio without the hassle of writing the options themselves?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li class="MsoListParagraphCxSpLast" style="text-indent: -.25in; mso-list: l0 level1 lfo1;"&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="60021726" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/advisorsoption/AdvisorsOption19.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:02:26</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Advisors Option 19: Pension Problems and PUT Writes
The Buzz: News out of China: OIC, Shanghai Stock Exchange content licensing agreement. Pensions seek bond diversification. Report: UK pensions miss out on returns. Chuck likes index funds. Retail...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Advisors Option 18: Listener Mail Extravaganza</title>
                    <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2014 13:53:11 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">21e936de93061a568cba9af45354fccf</guid>
                    <link>http://traffic.libsyn.com/advisorsoption/AdvisorsOptionReboot18.mp3</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/7205677"/>
                    <description>&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;Advisors Option 18: Listener Mail Extravaganza&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;The Buzz: An overview of the upcoming Options Industry Conference. What topics are discussed at the conference? Who attends? Is there any benefit for advisors?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;Listener Mail Extravaganza: The Advisors Options mail bag is filling up, so we are going to tackle as many as possible this episode:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li class="MsoNormal"&gt;Question from Neal Santos -&amp;nbsp;I am in the market for a new advisor and your program has awakened me to the benefits of using options. What sort of licensing should I look for in an advisor to make sure he is qualified to handle options investments? Is there a specific options exam offered by the exchanges or perhaps OCC that I should look for? Thanks for the show.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="MsoNormal"&gt;Question from J. Andrews, Philadelphia, PA - I have multiple clients with retirement assets in broad based equity portfolios. I have already done the correlation work and calculated how many SPX and SPY puts it would require to both fully and partially hedge the positions. My initial thought is to utilize SPX contracts as the larger size will reduce the number of contracts and reduce the overall commissions. But I have serious concerns regarding slippage in the SPX. I fear that over the long-term the dramatic difference in the bid-ask spread of the two products will result in lower returns for my clients in the SPX. One or two bad fills is all it would take to wipe out several years&amp;rsquo; worth of commission savings. Are these fears warranted?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="MsoNormal"&gt;Question from Darren - Hi, does OIC have any option alert services? Thanks and I truly enjoy the program.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="MsoNormal"&gt;Question from Andrea Tillwell - I would be interested in crafting a custom overlay to my retirement portfolio. Does Swan offer a bespoke service to individual investors or only to institutions?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="MsoNormal"&gt;Question from Hudson Trader - I am starting a new RIA with a focus on covered calls. What firms do the best job handling options focused funds - tools, understanding, etc?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="MsoNormal"&gt;Question from A_Firm -&amp;nbsp;My clients are pushing for more commodity and volatility exposure in their portfolios. I am comfortable with options but have not traded many futures, so I am looking at ETF options, particularly SLV, GLD, VXX, USO and UNG. What is your view on these products from an options perspective? Do they offer suitable depth and liquidity for clients looking for commodity exposure?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="MsoNormal"&gt;Question from TBard -&amp;nbsp;You have discussed leveraged ETFs in the past but have not touched on structured products. This to me is the more interesting of the two product categories for a busy advisor or asset manager. Many of my peers use fee-based products that replicate protective put strategies. I have several clients in funds linked the BXM and am taking a long look at PUT. Since you&amp;rsquo;ve complained about lack of options tools and awareness on the part of major BDs in the past perhaps these products are the necessary half step. The goldilocks porridge of options products for advisors.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="54614583" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/advisorsoption/AdvisorsOptionReboot18.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>56:48</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Advisors Option 18: Listener Mail Extravaganza
The Buzz: An overview of the upcoming Options Industry Conference. What topics are discussed at the conference? Who attends? Is there any benefit for advisors?
&amp;nbsp;
Listener Mail Extravaganza: The...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Advisors Options 17: Stock Replacement Using American-Style Calls</title>
                    <pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2014 17:04:24 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">5847f8f8de45e675844fe34d3aa578fa</guid>
                    <link>http://traffic.libsyn.com/advisorsoption/AdvisorsOption17.mp3</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/7104810"/>
                    <description>&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;Advisors Options 17: Stock Replacement Using American-Style Calls&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;The Buzz: Overview/highlights for advisors from the RMC. Are advisors genuinely interesting in volatility products such as ETN, VIX ETPs, etc.? The one-year anniversary of mini options is upcoming, what's the feedback from this product? What is the panels take on the most recent Goldman-Sachs study?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;Listener Mail: Stock Replacement Using American-Style Calls&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;Question from Greg S. -&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; I am looking for some advice from an experienced options professional regarding stock replacement using American-style calls. Really the question comes down to- for a higher dividend yielding stock, should I be buying a LEAP or rolling out approximately every three months after exercising very close to expiration and capturing each dividend? &amp;nbsp;I get that the dividend lowers the price I pay the longer dated the options are, but does not reflect as much as if the options were available as European-style. It seems that if the dividend yield is high enough, the American style cannot fully compensate the option holder for the missed dividends as the value cannot drop below intrinsic value. Does this call for the shorter term options to capture each dividend? The caveat seems to be that the roll out should cost more extrinsic value on ex-dividend. Since I have a buy-and-hold objective, euro-style or warrants would be ideal to avoid transaction costs, but again, not available. So far, I have been rolling an ITM call option position on a relatively high dividend yielding (5-7%) stock I have wanted concentrated exposure in as part of my overall portfolio but limited risk. &amp;nbsp;It makes regular scheduled quarterly dividend payments and the timing of the annual increases is known to occur in Q1 each year. Well just yesterday (day before ex-div for my stock), I figured I would skip the dividend capture and roll out the May contract to the August one cheaper than I could today because today it trades ex-dividend. &amp;nbsp;I confirmed this using the CBOE calculator, holding price constant. &amp;nbsp;It showed the time value paid to roll should have been more today due to trading without the dividend vs. yesterday. &amp;nbsp;Though just eyeing the bid x ask spread it didn't appear to do so by much and implied volatility looked to be the same."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="55596962" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/advisorsoption/AdvisorsOption17.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>57:50</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords/>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Advisors Options 17: Stock Replacement Using American-Style Calls
The Buzz: Overview/highlights for advisors from the RMC. Are advisors genuinely interesting in volatility products such as ETN, VIX ETPs, etc.? The one-year anniversary of mini options...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Advisors Option: Straddles &amp; Strangles</title>
                    <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2014 18:22:09 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">2345b7d5f3a5f355a682f43c2a8a5a52</guid>
                    <link>http://traffic.libsyn.com/advisorsoption/AdvisorsOptionSS.mp3</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/6894032"/>
                    <description>&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"&gt;Advisors Option: Straddles &amp;amp; Strangles&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"&gt;Options 101: Straddles &amp;amp; Strangles&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul style="margin-top: 0in;" type="disc"&gt;
&lt;li class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"&gt;Straddle: Buy/sell a call and put on the same strike.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"&gt;Long straddles. But be careful of high decay. Flip that around and you have a short straddle.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"&gt;Strangles allow you to benefit from significant underlying with smaller premium outlay compares to straddles. High decay still exist. Flip that around and you have a short strangle.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"&gt;Covered Straddles and Strangles.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal" style="margin-left: .5in;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"&gt;Listener Mail: What do you want to know?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul style="margin-top: 0in;" type="disc"&gt;
&lt;li class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"&gt;Question from Avid Gardener - &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"&gt;I am looking for ways to use options to establish very low cost, or hopefully free, bullish positions on stocks and ETFs. Is this possible or are my expectations unrealistic? Any specific strategies you could recommend would be greatly appreciated.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"&gt;Question from Istafan - &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"&gt;I am thinking of becoming an RIA or CFA. What should I expect on the exams from an options perspective? Any tips for an aspiring advisor? Thanks for your informative program. It has inspired me to pursue this as a career path with an emphasis on options.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"&gt;Question from INY06 - &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 11.0pt;"&gt;Quick question for Randy - Just what is reinsurance?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="56450942" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/advisorsoption/AdvisorsOptionSS.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>58:04</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords>wealth,investments,risk,options,futures,derivatives,strangles,straddles</itunes:keywords>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Advisors Option: Straddles &amp;amp; Strangles
&amp;nbsp;
Options 101: Straddles &amp;amp; Strangles

Straddle: Buy/sell a call and put on the same strike.
Long straddles. But be careful of high decay. Flip that around and you have a short...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Advisors Option: Mini Options</title>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2014 15:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">938111617e0867556b1293a6a8d8d449</guid>
                    <link>http://traffic.libsyn.com/advisorsoption/AdvisorsOption15.mp3</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/6740154"/>
                    <description>&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration: underline;"&gt;Advisors Option: Mini Options&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Options 101:&lt;/b&gt; Mini Options&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul style="margin-top: 0in;" type="disc"&gt;
&lt;li class="MsoNormal"&gt;What are mini options? &lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="MsoNormal"&gt;Which underlying stocks? The SEC approved mini options on five underlying securities: Apple Inc. (AAPL), Amazon Inc. (AMZN), Google Inc. (GOOG), SPDR S&amp;amp;P 500 (SPY) exchange-trade fund, and SPDR Gold Shares (GLD) exchange-traded fund.&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="MsoNormal"&gt;What is the use case? &lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="MsoNormal"&gt;Why would you not want to use mini options?&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Tricks of the Trade:&lt;/b&gt; The Right Skill Set&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;Today we will discuss the options skill set that a good advisor should bring to the table: how to hedge. It&amp;rsquo;s a critical skill, particularly in this market environment. Every advisor should understand buying puts. How to write calls:&amp;nbsp;Generate income on an equity portfolio. Put it together:&amp;nbsp;How to construct a collar. Understanding how high and low volatility impacts options prices. Writing puts instead of using limit buy orders for stocks. Understand basic vertical spreads.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Listener Mail:&lt;/b&gt; Keep those questions coming in&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul style="margin-top: 0in;" type="disc"&gt;
&lt;li class="MsoNormal"&gt;Question from C. Davis, Portland, ME -&amp;nbsp;Did you guys hear the episode of NPRs Marketplace where the financial advisor slammed options as "riskier than penny stocks?" What do you think?&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="MsoNormal"&gt;Question from Dog Fan -&amp;nbsp;How much should I reasonably expect to pay for a financial advisor who can do all of the things you discussed? Is there a set percentage or rule of thumb that I should go by? I imagine all of these skills would result in hefty fees.&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="85492013" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/advisorsoption/AdvisorsOption15.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>59:19</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords>calls,wealth,strategy,risk,options,puts,income,vix,advisor,futures,derivatives,volatility,collars</itunes:keywords>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Advisors Option: Mini Options
Options 101: Mini Options

What are mini options? 
Which underlying stocks? The SEC approved mini options on five underlying securities: Apple Inc. (AAPL), Amazon Inc. (AMZN), Google Inc. (GOOG), SPDR S&amp;amp;P 500 (SPY)...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Advisors Option: Year in Review</title>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2013 19:49:04 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">7dceeba7efe1cd893a3d40c65c335461</guid>
                    <link>http://traffic.libsyn.com/advisorsoption/Advisors_Option__The_Year_in_Review.mp3</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/6600553"/>
                    <description>&lt;p class="p1"&gt;&lt;span class="s1"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Advisors Option: Year in Review&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="p1"&gt;&lt;span class="s2"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Options 101: &lt;/b&gt;A Year in Review&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li class="li1"&gt;&lt;span class="s2"&gt;Options in Lieu of the Underlying&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="li1"&gt;&lt;span class="s2"&gt;Stock Replacement Strategy&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="li1"&gt;&lt;span class="s2"&gt;Stock Repair Strategy&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="li1"&gt;&lt;span class="s2"&gt;"Wheel of Fun"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p class="p1"&gt;&lt;span class="s2"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Listener Mail:&lt;/b&gt; So, what do you want to know?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li class="li1"&gt;&lt;span class="s2"&gt;&lt;i&gt;Question from Charles A.&lt;/i&gt; - I have heard it said that you should never exercise an option early. Is that accurate? Are there no scenarios when it would be appropriate? What is the point of paying for a right that you never intend to utilize?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="li1"&gt;&lt;span class="s2"&gt;&lt;i&gt;Question from Mr. Underhill &lt;/i&gt;- In your opinion, what is the sweet stop between paying too much time premium for a position versus paying too much time decay for a position?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="li1"&gt;&lt;span class="s2"&gt;Question from Tom G. - My advisor uses leveraged short SPY ETFs to hedge my portfolio. Your thoughts versus using puts?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="li1"&gt;&lt;span class="s2"&gt;&lt;i&gt;Question from "Joe Bagadonuts" &lt;/i&gt;- Hey Longo! Is that Italian? Cause I got a cousin, Vinny Longo from Bensonhurst. This is Joe Bagadonuts from Boca Raton. I go naked short on puts sitting here in my NY Jet boxers, and I've made a ton of moolah on them GOOG thingies. What you guys think of them mini doo-dads? Are those minis like the little cannoli I get at Publix Market here on SW 18th St? I love those little things! My wife won't let me eat the big Italian Arthur Avenue Dolce anymore, so thank the Lord for the minis!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="89867891" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/advisorsoption/Advisors_Option__The_Year_in_Review.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:02:19</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords>investing,wealth,management,financial,trading,advisors,risk,options</itunes:keywords>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Advisors Option: Year in Review
Options 101: A Year in Review

Options in Lieu of the Underlying
Stock Replacement Strategy
Stock Repair Strategy
"Wheel of Fun"

Listener Mail: So, what do you want to know?


Question from Charles A. - I have heard it...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>The Advisor’s Option: Stock Replacement Strategy</title>
                    <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2013 19:49:10 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">262f70b6c9c6ba98bfebbbb634eace16</guid>
                    <link>http://traffic.libsyn.com/advisorsoption/TheAdvisorsOptionReplacement.mp3</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/6500867"/>
                    <description>&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration: underline;"&gt;The Advisor&amp;rsquo;s Option: Stock Replacement Strategy&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Options 101:&lt;/b&gt; The Stock Replacement Strategy&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul style="margin-top: 0in;" type="disc"&gt;
&lt;li class="MsoNormal"&gt;Using options in lieu of stock.&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="MsoNormal"&gt;What is stock replacement? What are the advantages of stock replacement over just owning stock?&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="MsoNormal"&gt;What are some scenarios where you might want to consider a stock replacement strategy?&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="MsoNormal"&gt;Jazz up your covered call by using a stock replacement to save money and improve returns.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Listener Mail: &lt;/b&gt;What do you want to know?&lt;b&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul style="margin-top: 0in;" type="disc"&gt;
&lt;li class="MsoNormal"&gt;Question from Sal S, Fort Worth, TX - Most of the firms where I house my client account are pretty worthless when it comes to options. Rather than go through the hassle and paperwork of buying a put, what do you think about using an ETF like VXX to generate a volatility hedge for my portfolio?&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="MsoNormal"&gt;Question from Avantage - Do I need to fully understand the Black-Scholes formula to trade options?&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="MsoNormal"&gt;Question from Nick Thomas - How long do I have after the close of trading on expiration Friday to decide whether to exercise my clients call options? Also, do you have any good rules of thumb when deciding whether or not to exercise?&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="49427250" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/advisorsoption/TheAdvisorsOptionReplacement.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>51:24</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords>trading,risk,options,vix,advisor,volatility,weath</itunes:keywords>
                    <itunes:subtitle>The Advisor&amp;rsquo;s Option: Stock Replacement Strategy
Options 101: The Stock Replacement Strategy

Using options in lieu of stock.
What is stock replacement? What are the advantages of stock replacement over just owning stock?
What are some scenarios...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Advisors Option: The World of VIX</title>
                    <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2013 21:42:24 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">b42a4d3c717f97566ecb08e9a0c2783c</guid>
                    <link>http://traffic.libsyn.com/advisorsoption/AdvisorOptionVIX.mp3</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/6351656"/>
                    <description>&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration: underline;"&gt;Advisors Option: The World of VIX&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Options 101:&lt;/b&gt; Using VIX options/futures and volatility products as hedges. &lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal" style="margin-left: .25in; text-indent: -.25in; mso-list: l1 level1 lfo1;"&gt;&lt;!--[if !supportLists]--&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: Symbol; mso-fareast-font-family: Symbol; mso-bidi-font-family: Symbol;"&gt;&amp;middot;&lt;span style="font-size: 7pt; font-family: 'Times New Roman';"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;!--[endif]--&gt;What is the VIX? How is the VIX calculated?&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal" style="margin-left: .25in; text-indent: -.25in; mso-list: l1 level1 lfo1;"&gt;&lt;!--[if !supportLists]--&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: Symbol; mso-fareast-font-family: Symbol; mso-bidi-font-family: Symbol;"&gt;&amp;middot;&lt;span style="font-size: 7pt; font-family: 'Times New Roman';"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;!--[endif]--&gt;How are VIX options priced?&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal" style="margin-left: .25in; text-indent: -.25in; mso-list: l1 level1 lfo1;"&gt;&lt;!--[if !supportLists]--&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: Symbol; mso-fareast-font-family: Symbol; mso-bidi-font-family: Symbol;"&gt;&amp;middot;&lt;span style="font-size: 7pt; font-family: 'Times New Roman';"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;!--[endif]--&gt;How do the greeks work with VIX options?&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal" style="margin-left: .25in; text-indent: -.25in; mso-list: l1 level1 lfo1;"&gt;&lt;!--[if !supportLists]--&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: Symbol; mso-fareast-font-family: Symbol; mso-bidi-font-family: Symbol;"&gt;&amp;middot;&lt;span style="font-size: 7pt; font-family: 'Times New Roman';"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;!--[endif]--&gt;VIX is not a perfect hedge that offers pure inverse correlation to the S&amp;amp;P.&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal" style="margin-left: .25in; text-indent: -.25in; mso-list: l1 level1 lfo1;"&gt;&lt;!--[if !supportLists]--&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: Symbol; mso-fareast-font-family: Symbol; mso-bidi-font-family: Symbol;"&gt;&amp;middot;&lt;span style="font-size: 7pt; font-family: 'Times New Roman';"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;!--[endif]--&gt;Beware of the VIX settlement process and some of the other issues traders encounter during it. VIX settlement was 10/16 this month.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal" style="margin-left: .25in; text-indent: -.25in; mso-list: l1 level1 lfo1;"&gt;&lt;span style="text-indent: -0.25in; font-family: Symbol;"&gt;&amp;middot;&lt;span style="font-size: 7pt; font-family: 'Times New Roman';"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="text-indent: -0.25in;"&gt;There is an entire universe of VIX-related products out there including VXX, TVIX, etc.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Listener Mail:&lt;/b&gt;&amp;nbsp; It&amp;rsquo;s like Dear Abby, but for options&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul style="margin-top: 0in;" type="disc"&gt;
&lt;li class="MsoNormal"&gt;Question from Neal Tillman, CFA - We are at all-time highs in the market right now. Most of my clients account are long equity. My average account is sitting on gains of $60K-$100K for the year. I do not want to lose those gains if the market corrects, but I also do not want to sell these positions and miss out on future rallies in the broad market. For the sake of this discussion let&amp;rsquo;s assume I am sitting on a $1M portfolio with heavy exposure to SPY. How would I insure this portfolio to protect a $100K gain using SPY options? How much would it cost me to protect that $100K gain through the end of the year? Your insight on this issue would be most appreciated. &lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="MsoNormal"&gt;Question from Alamo -&amp;nbsp;If I buy puts to protect a stock that I already own in my account, does that count as a sale for tax purposes? Is that a taxable event?&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="58609119" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/advisorsoption/AdvisorOptionVIX.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:00:58</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords>wealth,trading,risk,options,vix,advisor,hedging,derivatives,vxx</itunes:keywords>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Advisors Option: The World of VIX
Options 101: Using VIX options/futures and volatility products as hedges. 
&amp;middot;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; What is the VIX? How is the VIX...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Advisors Option: Stock Repair</title>
                    <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2013 22:36:37 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">330865602137f1888776bcd5f023a87c</guid>
                    <link>http://traffic.libsyn.com/advisorsoption/AdvisorsOptionStockRepair.mp3</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/6195584"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;!--[if gte mso 9]&gt;&lt;xml&gt;
 &lt;o:OfficeDocumentSettings&gt;
  &lt;o:AllowPNG/&gt;
 &lt;/o:OfficeDocumentSettings&gt;
&lt;/xml&gt;&lt;![endif]--&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;b style="mso-bidi-font-weight: normal;"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration: underline;"&gt;Advisors Option: Stock Repair&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;b style="mso-bidi-font-weight: normal;"&gt;Options 101:&lt;/b&gt; The Stock Repair Strategy&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;Have a downturn in your account? Options can help make that money back. Stock repair strategies are a popular way for many advisors to regain some or all of the losses in a clients&amp;rsquo; portfolio. &lt;span style="mso-spacerun: yes;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;When should you use a stock repair strategy? How does it differ from just holding the stock? You can trade calls on a ratio for additional income, etc.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;b style="mso-bidi-font-weight: normal;"&gt;The Buzz:&lt;/b&gt; Clients are ready to listen to advisers on alternative investments:&amp;nbsp;Natixis survey finds mass majority open to adviser recommendations, up dramatically from past two years - &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.investmentnews.com/article/20130917/FREE/130919907"&gt;http://www.investmentnews.com/article/20130917/FREE/130919907#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;b style="mso-bidi-font-weight: normal;"&gt;Mail Bag:&lt;/b&gt; In which we tell it like it is&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul style="margin-top: 0in;" type="disc"&gt;
&lt;li class="MsoNormal" style="mso-list: l0 level1 lfo1;"&gt;Question from Gabe Shahir - The majority of my clients have large concentrations of assets in 401K plans. These plans are usually very limited from an asset selection perspective (very broad mutual funds, large cap, small cap, etc). With such a prolonged rally in the stock market many of my clients are looking for ways to protect the gains in their 401Ks. Short of divesting the positions and going into cash, the typical 401K does not offer much in the way of hedging opportunities. How can I use options to protect my clients?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="MsoNormal" style="mso-list: l0 level1 lfo1;"&gt;Question from Alex Tophas -&amp;nbsp;I often utilize leveraged short S&amp;amp;P ETFs to hedge my equity accounts. Is this a preferable options to buying puts - pun intended - for most advisors, since they do not need to master a new asset class to protect their clients?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="53532772" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/advisorsoption/AdvisorsOptionStockRepair.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>55:41</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords>investing,wealth,stock,trading,repair,risk,futures,derivatives,volatility</itunes:keywords>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Advisors Option: Stock Repair
Options 101: The Stock Repair Strategy
Have a downturn in your account? Options can help make that money back. Stock repair strategies are a popular way for many advisors to regain some or all of the losses in a...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Advisors Option: Spreads with Wings</title>
                    <pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2013 16:14:31 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">aeafb7938b100ff8a2b0fae8f758b81d</guid>
                    <link>http://traffic.libsyn.com/advisorsoption/AdvisorsOptionWings.mp3</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/6054536"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;!--[if gte mso 9]&gt;&lt;xml&gt;
 &lt;o:OfficeDocumentSettings&gt;
  &lt;o:AllowPNG/&gt;
 &lt;/o:OfficeDocumentSettings&gt;
&lt;/xml&gt;&lt;![endif]--&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;b style="mso-bidi-font-weight: normal;"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration: underline;"&gt;Advisors Option: Spreads with Wings&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;b style="mso-bidi-font-weight: normal;"&gt;Options 101:&lt;/b&gt; We have discusses collars and verticals on this show in the past, and now it&amp;rsquo;s time to explore some of the more elaborate option spreads that many advisors/asset managers may be familiar with - particularly spreads with wings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;What is a butterfly? When would an advisor want to use a butterfly spread?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;What is an iron condor? How does it differ from a butterfly? When would an advisor want to?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;What is an iron butterfly? How does an iron fly differ from an iron condor and a standard fly?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;b style="mso-bidi-font-weight: normal;"&gt;Listener Mail:&lt;/b&gt; So, what do you want to know?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;Question from Tom S. - How do dividends impact option prices? Let&amp;rsquo;s say my clients own a put on a stock and it declares a substantial dividend. Do they collect all of the profit from the stock drop in the price of the put, or is there some sort of change made to the strike price to reflect the new value of the stock?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;Question from TheNewt - If I own a call on a stock and it declares a special dividend, do I collect the dividend?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;Question from Mike Z., Tampa, FL - I would like to gain some volatility exposure in my portfolio. Which volatility products should I recommend to my financial advisor at our next meeting?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;b style="mso-bidi-font-weight: normal;"&gt;Industry Buzz:&lt;/b&gt; Attention Chicagoland Financial Planners, Insurance Agents, Certified Public Accountants, and financial services practitioners! Early bird registration for the Financial Planning Association of Illinois Fall Forum ends in a few days. Don't miss our awesome Hyatt Oak Brook event September 19th. For more information click on the link below and look for Fall Forum 2013!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="72221695" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/advisorsoption/AdvisorsOptionWings.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>50:06</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords>investing,wealth,trading,condor,iron,risk,butterfly,options,advisor,spreads,derivatives</itunes:keywords>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Advisors Option: Spreads with Wings
Options 101: We have discusses collars and verticals on this show in the past, and now it&amp;rsquo;s time to explore some of the more elaborate option spreads that many advisors/asset managers may be familiar with -...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Advisors Option: The Wheel of Fun</title>
                    <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2013 21:20:42 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">5bf0f7dcfab9e5eb4f92a112add5a136</guid>
                    <link>http://traffic.libsyn.com/advisorsoption/AdvisorsOptionWOF.mp3</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/5922032"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;!--[if gte mso 9]&gt;&lt;xml&gt;
 &lt;o:OfficeDocumentSettings&gt;
  &lt;o:AllowPNG/&gt;
 &lt;/o:OfficeDocumentSettings&gt;
&lt;/xml&gt;&lt;![endif]--&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration: underline;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Advisors Option: The Wheel of Fun&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Options 101:&lt;/strong&gt; Alternate methods for entering and exiting stock positions using options - aka "The Wheel of Fun."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Caveat 1:&amp;nbsp;Short puts are excellent tools for income generation, but most advisors and clients should limit themselves to only writing puts at prices, and on underlyings, that they don't mind owning.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Caveat 2: The income generation portion of these trades are extremely volatility-dependent. This strategy is not suitable for all trading/volatility environments. Don't force an income trade when the volatility is too low. You're simply incurring risk without enough reward to offset it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Listener Mail:&amp;nbsp; &lt;/strong&gt;Help us help you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Question from Walter T., Tampa, FL - Why are retirement accounts restricted to only buying options and writing covered positions?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Question from NorthForkSpur -&amp;nbsp;What do the hosts think of advisors using futures options for exposure to non-correlated assets like commodities? Is this the right path? Should most stick with ETF options instead?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Question from Alejandro Vega, CFP, Los Angeles, CA - I enjoyed your episode on collars. They can certainly provide great benefit to my clients. But I'm confused as to the difference between a collar and a risk reversal. They seem to be the same trade. Are these just two different terms for the same thing?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Buzz: &lt;/strong&gt;S&amp;amp;P 500 &amp;ldquo;Persistence Scorecard" result are out - Most managers still fail to beat the market. Two great reasons to add options to you client portfolios. Correlation is kicking into high gear.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="55704064" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/advisorsoption/AdvisorsOptionWOF.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>57:56</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords>calls,investing,wealth,management,trading,risk,options,puts,advisor,cfp,cpa,cfa</itunes:keywords>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Advisors Option: The Wheel of Fun
Options 101: Alternate methods for entering and exiting stock positions using options - aka "The Wheel of Fun."

Caveat 1:&amp;nbsp;Short puts are excellent tools for income generation, but most advisors and clients...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Advisors Option: The Problems with Annuities and Structured Products.</title>
                    <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2013 19:13:22 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">794ed83fe69d8dd9a6bed1f402e0c38d</guid>
                    <link>http://traffic.libsyn.com/advisorsoption/AdvisorsOption7.mp3</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/5821115"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;!--[if gte mso 9]&gt;&lt;xml&gt;
 &lt;w:WordDocument&gt;
  &lt;w:View&gt;Normal&lt;/w:View&gt;
  &lt;w:Zoom&gt;0&lt;/w:Zoom&gt;
  &lt;w:TrackMoves/&gt;
  &lt;w:TrackFormatting/&gt;
  &lt;w:PunctuationKerning/&gt;
  &lt;w:ValidateAgainstSchemas/&gt;
  &lt;w:SaveIfXMLInvalid&gt;false&lt;/w:SaveIfXMLInvalid&gt;
  &lt;w:IgnoreMixedContent&gt;false&lt;/w:IgnoreMixedContent&gt;
  &lt;w:AlwaysShowPlaceholderText&gt;false&lt;/w:AlwaysShowPlaceholderText&gt;
  &lt;w:DoNotPromoteQF/&gt;
  &lt;w:LidThemeOther&gt;EN-US&lt;/w:LidThemeOther&gt;
  &lt;w:LidThemeAsian&gt;X-NONE&lt;/w:LidThemeAsian&gt;
  &lt;w:LidThemeComplexScript&gt;X-NONE&lt;/w:LidThemeComplexScript&gt;
  &lt;w:Compatibility&gt;
   &lt;w:BreakWrappedTables/&gt;
   &lt;w:SnapToGridInCell/&gt;
   &lt;w:WrapTextWithPunct/&gt;
   &lt;w:UseAsianBreakRules/&gt;
   &lt;w:DontGrowAutofit/&gt;
   &lt;w:SplitPgBreakAndParaMark/&gt;
   &lt;w:DontVertAlignCellWithSp/&gt;
   &lt;w:DontBreakConstrainedForcedTables/&gt;
   &lt;w:DontVertAlignInTxbx/&gt;
   &lt;w:Word11KerningPairs/&gt;
   &lt;w:CachedColBalance/&gt;
  &lt;/w:Compatibility&gt;
  &lt;w:BrowserLevel&gt;MicrosoftInternetExplorer4&lt;/w:BrowserLevel&gt;
  &lt;m:mathPr&gt;
   &lt;m:mathFont m:val="Cambria Math"/&gt;
   &lt;m:brkBin m:val="before"/&gt;
   &lt;m:brkBinSub m:val="&amp;#45;-"/&gt;
   &lt;m:smallFrac m:val="off"/&gt;
   &lt;m:dispDef/&gt;
   &lt;m:lMargin m:val="0"/&gt;
   &lt;m:rMargin m:val="0"/&gt;
   &lt;m:defJc m:val="centerGroup"/&gt;
   &lt;m:wrapIndent m:val="1440"/&gt;
   &lt;m:intLim m:val="subSup"/&gt;
   &lt;m:naryLim m:val="undOvr"/&gt;
  &lt;/m:mathPr&gt;&lt;/w:WordDocument&gt;
&lt;/xml&gt;&lt;![endif]--&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration: underline;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Advisors Option: The Problems with Annuities and Structured Products.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tricks of the Trade:&lt;/strong&gt; The problems with Annuities and Structured Products.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;Many advisors gravitate toward structured products instead of using options/derivatives in client accounts, but structured products frequently present problems:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul style="margin-top: 0in;" type="disc"&gt;
&lt;li class="MsoNormal" style="mso-list: l0 level1 lfo2;"&gt;Accuracy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="MsoNormal" style="mso-list: l0 level1 lfo2;"&gt;Options Exposure&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="MsoNormal" style="mso-list: l0 level1 lfo2;"&gt;Time Management&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="MsoNormal" style="mso-list: l0 level1 lfo2;"&gt;Expense&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="MsoNormal" style="mso-list: l0 level1 lfo2;"&gt;Evaluate your product.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Listener Mail:&lt;/strong&gt; How may we be of service?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul style="margin-top: 0in;" type="disc"&gt;
&lt;li class="MsoNormal" style="mso-list: l1 level1 lfo1;"&gt;Question from Charles Sullivan - Is the primary stumbling block for options use by advisors the fact that the leading names in the advisor space (Charles Schwab, Morningstar, etc.) seem to have no interest in these products?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="MsoNormal" style="mso-list: l1 level1 lfo1;"&gt;Question from Thomas Folk, CFP - Most of my clients invest through retirement accounts. Can I trade options in these accounts? If so, what strategies can I pursue?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="MsoNormal" style="mso-list: l1 level1 lfo1;"&gt;Question from Nathan Phillips - I have several clients with odd lot positions in Apple. I've toyed with using options in the past, but it never made sense given the size of the positions. But the launch of the new mini Apple products has piqued my curiosity. Are these products the same as regular options only with a reduced notional value? Are the any nuances or hidden issues I should be aware of before I consider using these for my clients? Thank for this program; I learn something new every episode.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="61528858" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/advisorsoption/AdvisorsOption7.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:03:57</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords>calls,wealth,trading,products,advisors,options,puts,vix,structured,annuities,volatility,oic</itunes:keywords>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Advisors Option: The Problems with Annuities and Structured Products.
Tricks of the Trade: The problems with Annuities and Structured Products.
Many advisors gravitate toward structured products instead of using options/derivatives in client accounts,...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Advisors Option: Listeners Take Over</title>
                    <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2013 20:44:47 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">4c1c19b061b7a516a43f2d00e26ad0d4</guid>
                    <link>http://traffic.libsyn.com/advisorsoption/AdvisorsOption6.mp3</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/5749740"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;!--[if gte mso 9]&gt;&lt;xml&gt;
 &lt;o:OfficeDocumentSettings&gt;
  &lt;o:AllowPNG/&gt;
 &lt;/o:OfficeDocumentSettings&gt;
&lt;/xml&gt;&lt;![endif]--&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;Advisor&amp;rsquo;s Option: Listeners Take Over&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Listener Mail: &lt;/strong&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s all mail, all episode long.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;Question from Jackson_CFA: What do the hosts think of annuities as a tool for diversification and income generation for risk-averse clients?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;Question from Alexander Sarsgard, Portland, OR: Just adding puts to your client's portfolios is expensive. What is your favorite methodology for reducing the cost of protection when structuring client portfolios?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;Question from Tim Dinahar, Houston, TX: Do I really need to understand the greeks when writing/buying options for my clients? Or is everything I really need to know encapsulated in the option's price? Thank you very much for this insightful program. I don't think anyone else has tackled the advisor space like this.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;Question from Anthony Deshanti, Stracuse, NY: How can I approach the topic of options with my clients when mainstream outlets like New York Times are slamming options as risky and dangerous - http://www.nytimes.com/2013/05/25/business/growth-in-options-trading-helps-brokers-but-not-small-investors.html?ref=nathanielpopper&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;Question from JBerg: What time frame do you use when constructing collars/risk overlays? Six months is my preferred time frame to buy put/sell call.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;Question from Alejandro Vega, San Antonio, TX: I don't use options in my client accounts. If I want leveraged exposure to underlyings I simply turn to leveraged ETFs. What do you think of using these instruments in lieu of options in client portfolios? Am I missing something by not using options?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;Question from Mr_Nick: Can I as an individual investor buy into Randy's fund? What is the ticker?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;Question from Jim Schulman, Mobile, AL: Adding options to client accounts would generate significant fees to accommodate opening and closing the positions, rolling to new strikes, etc. Do you find your clients are receptive to these instruments even with the added costs?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="53665541" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/advisorsoption/AdvisorsOption6.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>55:49</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords>investing,wealth,trading,forex,options,advisor,futures,deriviatives</itunes:keywords>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Advisor&amp;rsquo;s Option: Listeners Take Over
Listener Mail: It&amp;rsquo;s all mail, all episode long.
Question from Jackson_CFA: What do the hosts think of annuities as a tool for diversification and income generation for risk-averse clients?
Question...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>The Advisors Option 5: Asset Allocation</title>
                    <pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2013 20:34:15 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">fdd6360eb643d3261eae1a90b959c168</guid>
                    <link>http://traffic.libsyn.com/advisorsoption/AdvisorOption5.mp3</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/5640406"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;!--[if gte mso 9]&gt;&lt;xml&gt;
 &lt;o:OfficeDocumentSettings&gt;
  &lt;o:AllowPNG/&gt;
 &lt;/o:OfficeDocumentSettings&gt;
&lt;/xml&gt;&lt;![endif]--&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration: underline;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Advisors Option 5: Asset Allocation&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;Tricks of the Trade: The myth/lie of asset allocation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul style="margin-top: 0in;" type="disc"&gt;
&lt;li class="MsoNormal" style="mso-list: l1 level1 lfo1;"&gt;It used to be 20 different underlyings to be fully diversified. Now with increasing correlation, it is closer to 40.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="MsoNormal" style="mso-list: l1 level1 lfo1;"&gt;Debunking asset allocation as a method of defense. The old style of asset allocation in no longer effective.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="MsoNormal" style="mso-list: l1 level1 lfo1;"&gt;Absolutely nothing about options, hedging or volatility was discussed at the Morningstar Advisor Event last year.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="MsoNormal" style="mso-list: l1 level1 lfo1;"&gt;You are not fully diversified in this market unless you have something that gives you volatility exposure and negative correlation, i.e. protective puts, collars, volatility instruments, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="MsoNormal" style="mso-list: l1 level1 lfo1;"&gt;"Hedging is too expensive!" The cost of the protection is mitigated, particularly if you manage the positions effectively.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="MsoNormal" style="mso-list: l1 level1 lfo1;"&gt;Outperforming to the downside is still outperforming.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;ul style="margin-top: 0in;" type="disc"&gt;
&lt;li class="MsoNormal" style="mso-list: l1 level1 lfo1;"&gt;Defensive positions can still generate competitive returns.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;em&gt;The purpose of this conversation is not just to promote Swan, but also to show that incorporating options into you asset allocation is part of the fiduciary responsibility of any advisor in this marketplace.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;Listener Mail: Tell us what you want to know:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul style="margin-top: 0in;" type="disc"&gt;
&lt;li class="MsoNormal" style="mso-list: l0 level1 lfo2;"&gt;Question from (Name withheld) - As an active financial manager coming to options for the first time, I'd like to know what the hosts consider to be the most effective options position for busy advisors? If I only have time to learn one, I'd like it to be the best.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="MsoNormal" style="mso-list: l0 level1 lfo2;"&gt;Question from Tom Meadows, Pittsburgh, PA - What percentage of financial advisors and planners do you estimate currently use options?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="MsoNormal" style="mso-list: l0 level1 lfo2;"&gt;Question from Allan Gregory, San Diego, CA - If options education for financial advisors is such a problem, why doesn't OIC or some other entity offer a certification course for planners and advisors?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="50840555" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/advisorsoption/AdvisorOption5.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>52:52</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords>investing,wealth,trading,advisors,asset,assets,options,vix,spreads,swan,futures,allocation,volatility</itunes:keywords>
                    <itunes:subtitle>The Advisors Option 5: Asset Allocation
Tricks of the Trade: The myth/lie of asset allocation.

It used to be 20 different underlyings to be fully diversified. Now with increasing correlation, it is closer to 40.
Debunking asset allocation as a method...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Advisors Option: Tales from the Front</title>
                    <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2013 17:35:34 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">9d022495a4139e4c2fe5a53980a2a039</guid>
                    <link>http://traffic.libsyn.com/advisorsoption/AdvisorsOptionTales.mp3</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/5573358"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;!--[if gte mso 9]&gt;&lt;xml&gt;
 &lt;o:OfficeDocumentSettings&gt;
  &lt;o:AllowPNG/&gt;
 &lt;/o:OfficeDocumentSettings&gt;
&lt;/xml&gt;&lt;![endif]--&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration: underline;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Advisors Option: Tales from the Front&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;Mark, Mike, and Randy are joined by Alan Grigoletto and Eric Cott from the Options Industry Council.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tricks of the Trade:&lt;/strong&gt; OIC has issued a new white paper, &amp;ldquo;Tales from the Front,&amp;rdquo; that looks at the use of options from the advisor point-of-view.&lt;span style="mso-spacerun: yes;"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;Eric and Alan give an overview, the purpose, and some of the findings.&lt;span style="mso-spacerun: yes;"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;Randy and Mike give their perspective as advisors who already use options.&lt;span style="mso-spacerun: yes;"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;Each person gives their key surprising takeaway.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Listener Mail:&lt;/strong&gt; Do you want to know what we&amp;rsquo;re talking about? What are your questions?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;How do I find an advisor who uses options?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;How do I find out which funds use Randy&amp;rsquo;s overlay?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="57677914" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/advisorsoption/AdvisorsOptionTales.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:00:00</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords>trading,advisors,options,derivatives,weath,oic,occ</itunes:keywords>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Advisors Option: Tales from the Front
Mark, Mike, and Randy are joined by Alan Grigoletto and Eric Cott from the Options Industry Council.
Tricks of the Trade: OIC has issued a new white paper, &amp;ldquo;Tales from the Front,&amp;rdquo; that looks at the use...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Advisor Option: Volatility</title>
                    <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2013 18:15:05 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">48a2db8a92c947705c1dff58feef23bb</guid>
                    <link>http://traffic.libsyn.com/advisorsoption/AdvisorsOptionVolatility.mp3</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/5417491"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;!--[if gte mso 9]&gt;&lt;xml&gt;
 &lt;w:WordDocument&gt;
  &lt;w:View&gt;Normal&lt;/w:View&gt;
  &lt;w:Zoom&gt;0&lt;/w:Zoom&gt;
  &lt;w:TrackMoves/&gt;
  &lt;w:TrackFormatting/&gt;
  &lt;w:PunctuationKerning/&gt;
  &lt;w:ValidateAgainstSchemas/&gt;
  &lt;w:SaveIfXMLInvalid&gt;false&lt;/w:SaveIfXMLInvalid&gt;
  &lt;w:IgnoreMixedContent&gt;false&lt;/w:IgnoreMixedContent&gt;
  &lt;w:AlwaysShowPlaceholderText&gt;false&lt;/w:AlwaysShowPlaceholderText&gt;
  &lt;w:DoNotPromoteQF/&gt;
  &lt;w:LidThemeOther&gt;EN-US&lt;/w:LidThemeOther&gt;
  &lt;w:LidThemeAsian&gt;X-NONE&lt;/w:LidThemeAsian&gt;
  &lt;w:LidThemeComplexScript&gt;X-NONE&lt;/w:LidThemeComplexScript&gt;
  &lt;w:Compatibility&gt;
   &lt;w:BreakWrappedTables/&gt;
   &lt;w:SnapToGridInCell/&gt;
   &lt;w:WrapTextWithPunct/&gt;
   &lt;w:UseAsianBreakRules/&gt;
   &lt;w:DontGrowAutofit/&gt;
   &lt;w:SplitPgBreakAndParaMark/&gt;
   &lt;w:DontVertAlignCellWithSp/&gt;
   &lt;w:DontBreakConstrainedForcedTables/&gt;
   &lt;w:DontVertAlignInTxbx/&gt;
   &lt;w:Word11KerningPairs/&gt;
   &lt;w:CachedColBalance/&gt;
  &lt;/w:Compatibility&gt;
  &lt;w:BrowserLevel&gt;MicrosoftInternetExplorer4&lt;/w:BrowserLevel&gt;
  &lt;m:mathPr&gt;
   &lt;m:mathFont m:val="Cambria Math"/&gt;
   &lt;m:brkBin m:val="before"/&gt;
   &lt;m:brkBinSub m:val="&amp;#45;-"/&gt;
   &lt;m:smallFrac m:val="off"/&gt;
   &lt;m:dispDef/&gt;
   &lt;m:lMargin m:val="0"/&gt;
   &lt;m:rMargin m:val="0"/&gt;
   &lt;m:defJc m:val="centerGroup"/&gt;
   &lt;m:wrapIndent m:val="1440"/&gt;
   &lt;m:intLim m:val="subSup"/&gt;
   &lt;m:naryLim m:val="undOvr"/&gt;
  &lt;/m:mathPr&gt;&lt;/w:WordDocument&gt;
&lt;/xml&gt;&lt;![endif]--&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration: underline;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Advisor Option: Volatility &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Options 101: &lt;/strong&gt;Volatility&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;--What is Vega?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;--Implied vs. realized volatility.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;--What is the impact of low vs. high volatility environment on options trading?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;--Correlation and becoming fully diversified by adding a volatility component to your portfolio.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;--How do you get volatility exposure?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;--What is an overlay strategy, and how do you construct one?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;Misconceptions of the VIX:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;--Quoting the VIX cash, which is the same as not VIX futures.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;--The current pervasive attitude that the VIX is low.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;--Believing it is a fantastic inverse correlation portfolio hedging tool, instead of buying a more direct portfolio hedge.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Buzz:&lt;/strong&gt; Potential new taxes that might be on the horizon for traders. Swan Wealth Advisors is in discussions with TD Ameritrade to start monthly options seminars.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="50726285" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/advisorsoption/AdvisorsOptionVolatility.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>52:42</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords>wealth,trading,advisors,options,vix,swan,vega,volatility,oic</itunes:keywords>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Advisor Option: Volatility 
Options 101: Volatility
--What is Vega?
--Implied vs. realized volatility.
--What is the impact of low vs. high volatility environment on options trading?
--Correlation and becoming fully diversified by adding a volatility...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Advisors Option: Spreads</title>
                    <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2013 17:21:56 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">47dab08e9606601191019e7ba5612ea5</guid>
                    <link>http://traffic.libsyn.com/advisorsoption/AdvisorsOptionSpreads.mp3</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/5282694"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;!--[if gte mso 9]&gt;&lt;xml&gt;
 &lt;o:OfficeDocumentSettings&gt;
  &lt;o:AllowPNG/&gt;
 &lt;/o:OfficeDocumentSettings&gt;
&lt;/xml&gt;&lt;![endif]--&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration: underline;"&gt;Advisors Option: Spreads&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Options 101: &lt;/strong&gt;Spreads. What is a spread? Vertical spreads? How do you add spreads to your portfolio? How do spreads affected by the Greeks?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mail Bag: &lt;/strong&gt;Our hosts answer listener questions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;Question from Tony - Glendale, AZ: Thank you for this insightful program! I typed the terms financial planner and options into the iTunes search bar on a whim and was amazed to find the Advisors Option. You have been a godsend for professionals like me who want to learn more about these products for our clients. I feel much better prepared to deal with their questions now thanks to your program. Thanks again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;Question from Spencer - Portland, OR: I mostly deal with retired clients whose assets are tied up in IRAs. I was under the impression that options were prohibited in IRAs. Is that the case? Perhaps you can do a program on options for retirees, or people with assets in retirement accounts. Thanks for your one-of-a-kind program Mark!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;Question from Alexander S - Portland, ME: I've heard the Advisors Option team, in particular Randy Swan, discussing options overlays in the past. Can you explain exactly what you mean by that term? Do you modify the underlying portfolio to conform to the specifications of the options allocation, or are the options a truly separate component? Also, I listened to a recording of a buy-side panel from the OIC/FIA conference in September. One of the fund managers on that panel said he prefers to liquidate his positions, rather than purchase protective puts. Why do you think so many advisors/assets managers are still so ignorant of the benefits options offer a portfolio manager?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;Question from James C: I have a 401K that is invested in the S&amp;amp;P. What's the best way to hedge it outside of the 401K from downside risk? Would beta weighting with SDS be a good hedge or is there a better way? Also, I heard the terms "hitting offers" and "lifting bids," I hope I got that right. What does that mean?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;Question from Orlando T: Mark you're program is uniquely situated to address a serious problem in the advisor community - the lack of any real understanding of hedging and risk management using options. I think everyone on your program will agree options are the best tools for this, yet advisors don't have any substantive training on this subject. Why is that? Why don't the CFA/CFP exams offer more in the way of options instruction? Why doesn't the OIC partner with these organizations, or create their own certification exam? It seems to be the only organization that has a shot at solving this problem, otherwise we're all poised to recreate 2008/2009 the next time the market crashes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="53078298" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/advisorsoption/AdvisorsOptionSpreads.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>55:12</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords>wealth,advisors,options,spreads,swan,oic</itunes:keywords>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Advisors Option: Spreads
Options 101: Spreads. What is a spread? Vertical spreads? How do you add spreads to your portfolio? How do spreads affected by the Greeks?
Mail Bag: Our hosts answer listener questions.
Question from Tony - Glendale, AZ: Thank...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Advisors Option: Collar Strategies</title>
                    <pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2012 17:22:21 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">5030294733487cb884afa4e4cad9946e</guid>
                    <link>http://traffic.libsyn.com/advisorsoption/AdvisorsOption.mp3</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/5231476"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;!--[if gte mso 9]&gt;&lt;xml&gt;
 &lt;o:OfficeDocumentSettings&gt;
  &lt;o:AllowPNG/&gt;
 &lt;/o:OfficeDocumentSettings&gt;
&lt;/xml&gt;&lt;![endif]--&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration: underline;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Advisors Option: Collar Strategies&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;Join your co-hosts Mark Longo, founder of the Options Insider, Randy Swan, co-founder of Swan Wealth Advisors, and Mike Cavanaugh from Know Your Options, Inc., as they help advisors navigate their way through the world of options.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;Options 101: The ultimate advisor&amp;rsquo;s option strategy: the collar.&lt;span style="mso-spacerun: yes;"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;The group is joined by Alan Grigoletto, director of Education at OIC, to discuss the collar.&lt;span style="mso-spacerun: yes;"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;The group discusses the ways in which collars can be useful for wealth advisors in particular, especially in terms of risk management and managing existing equity positions. Taking the collar to the next level: collar-plus.&lt;span style="mso-spacerun: yes;"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;Do collars limit upside gains? Will advisors underperform their peers if using this strategy?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="44120185" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/advisorsoption/AdvisorsOption.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>45:52</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords>wealth,management,strategy,trading,advisors,collar,risk,options</itunes:keywords>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Advisors Option: Collar Strategies
Join your co-hosts Mark Longo, founder of the Options Insider, Randy Swan, co-founder of Swan Wealth Advisors, and Mike Cavanaugh from Know Your Options, Inc., as they help advisors navigate their way through the...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Advisors Option Episode 6: Swan Wealth Advisors</title>
                    <pubDate>Wed, 08 Aug 2012 14:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">41139e8f997f621163daf019024df534</guid>
                    <link>http://traffic.libsyn.com/advisorsoption/A06_SwanWealthAdvisors.mp3</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/2030159"/>
                    <description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;span style="color: #000000;" color="#000000"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration: underline;"&gt;Advisors Option Episode 6: Swan Wealth Advisors&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;span style="color: #000000;" color="#000000"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mark and Mike are joined by Randy Swan, President of Swan Wealth Advisors. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;span style="color: #000000;" color="#000000"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In the &lt;strong&gt;Interview Segment&lt;/strong&gt;, the group discusses:&lt;br /&gt;Two words: Risk Management.&lt;br /&gt;The major stumbling blocks keeping advisors from using options.&lt;br /&gt;How to take the first steps?&lt;br /&gt;Should there be more credentials to help people feel more secure with an advisor trading options with their assets.&lt;br /&gt;The wake-up call for brokerage firms.&lt;br /&gt;Two more words: It's insurance.&lt;br /&gt;You cannot adequately control risk without using derivatives.&lt;br /&gt;The new normal - prepare for it.&lt;br /&gt;The wish for problem-solving tools.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #000000;" color="#000000"&gt;Industry Buzz: The nexus of options and advisors has produced a theme of concern over what to do about risk. Why are volumes going down? Why are options still perceived as risky? Dodd-Frank &amp;amp; other regulation. How the political climate affects the markets.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="40060404" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/advisorsoption/A06_SwanWealthAdvisors.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>41:36</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords>management,financial,insurance,risk,options,advisor,futures,derivatives</itunes:keywords>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Advisors Option Episode 6: Swan Wealth Advisors
Mark and Mike are joined by Randy Swan, President of Swan Wealth Advisors. 
In the Interview Segment, the group discusses:Two words: Risk Management.The major stumbling blocks keeping advisors from using...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>The Advisors Option Episode 5: Selling Puts</title>
                    <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2012 18:04:43 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">e44d764a2f567b0fcee673410d5a338d</guid>
                    <link>http://traffic.libsyn.com/advisorsoption/AO5_SELLING_PUTS.mp3</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/2011273"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration: underline;"&gt;The Advisors Option Episode 5: Selling Puts&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In this episode, Mark is joined by Mike Cavanaugh of Know Your Options Inc., and Option Block Fame.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Options&amp;nbsp; 101: &lt;/strong&gt;Looking at the other end of the spectrum, the Covered Put. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;bull;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Reasons why you, as an advisor, may want to consider selling naked short puts. &lt;br /&gt;&amp;bull;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Less risk than buying a stock outright. &lt;br /&gt;&amp;bull;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Examples with everyone's favorite stock: XYZ. &lt;br /&gt;&amp;bull;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; How does KYO use the naked short put to employ their Triple Income Strategy (aka the Wheel of Fun)?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="24653417" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/advisorsoption/AO5_SELLING_PUTS.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>25:33</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords>calls,investment,stock,trading,advisors,options,puts,derivatives,volatility</itunes:keywords>
                    <itunes:subtitle>The Advisors Option Episode 5: Selling PutsIn this episode, Mark is joined by Mike Cavanaugh of Know Your Options Inc., and Option Block Fame.Options&amp;nbsp; 101: Looking at the other end of the spectrum, the Covered Put. &amp;bull;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>The Holy Grail of the Options Market</title>
                    <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jul 2012 15:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">37450580d5e1afae23383c5c416fbb3e</guid>
                    <link>http://traffic.libsyn.com/advisorsoption/OIC2012HolyGrail.mp3</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/1998043"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration: underline;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Holy Grail of the Options Market&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration: underline;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Our exclusive OIC 2012 audio coverage continues with Options Insider Founder Mark S. Longo's compelling panel The Holy Grail of The Options Market. This session explores the tumultuous relationship between financial advisors, asset managers and the options market. What are the major stumbling blocks keeping advisors from adopting options? Why aren't more asset managers using options to hedge their portfolios or generate income? We explore these topics and many more on The Holy Grail of The Options Market.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Joining Mark on the panel are:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Michael Cavanaugh, Founder, Know Your Options Inc &amp;amp; Co-Host, The Advisor's Option.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Randy Swan, Co-Founder, Swan Wealth Advisors&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Stephen Solaka, Co-Founder, Belmont Capital Group&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="49287338" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/advisorsoption/OIC2012HolyGrail.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>51:18</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords>manager,financial,2012,asset,options,advisor,oic</itunes:keywords>
                    <itunes:subtitle>The Holy Grail of the Options Market
Our exclusive OIC 2012 audio coverage continues with Options Insider Founder Mark S. Longo's compelling panel The Holy Grail of The Options Market. This session explores the tumultuous relationship between...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Advisors Option Episode 3: Mysteries of the Covered Call</title>
                    <pubDate>Mon, 30 Apr 2012 17:54:14 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">4bf4533884b8c8b045435e393fdf19c3</guid>
                    <link>http://traffic.libsyn.com/advisorsoption/AdvisorsOption3.mp3</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/item/1931905"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration: underline;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Advisors Option Episode 3: Mysteries of the Covered Call&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Options 101: Covered Calls&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; What is a covered call?&lt;br /&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; When should you use it?&lt;br /&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Reasons to write covered calls&lt;br /&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Downsides to the covered call&lt;br /&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Covered call vs. Naked short put&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Interview Segment with Sean Heron&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mr. Heron is an Adjunct Finance Professor, CFA, Rutgers University as well as the Senior Investment Manager, Glenmede Trust Company.&amp;nbsp; In this segment, the gang discusses the OIC/Rutgers options program for advisors.&amp;nbsp; They touch on topics including: a lack of options education for advisors; why advisors are hesitant to use options; what can be done to increase the adoption rate of options by advisors.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Industry Buzz Segment&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Overview of the upcoming financial advisor conference in New Orleans.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;For more information on OIC Advisor, please visit: http://advisor.optionseducation.org/&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information on the Rutgers/OIC program, visit: http://options.rutgers.edu/&lt;br /&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;For more information on the Options Industry Conference, please visit: http://www.optionsconference.com/2012/default.jsp&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="45920747" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/advisorsoption/AdvisorsOption3.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:03:35</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords>call,calls,trading,options,covered,puts,derivatives,volatility,oic</itunes:keywords>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Advisors Option Episode 3: Mysteries of the Covered Call&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Options 101: Covered Calls&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; What is a covered call?&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; When should you use it?&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Reasons to write covered calls&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;...</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Episode 2: Playing Defense with Protective Puts</title>
                    <pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2012 23:55:19 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">fa502aa277d92128d70ac718eecb4457</guid>
                    <link>http://traffic.libsyn.com/advisorsoption/AO2_ProtectivePut.mp3</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/4308489"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration: underline;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Advisor&amp;rsquo;s Option Episode Two: Playing Defense with Protective Puts&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Options 101: Continuing Education: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Graduating from the long call to the protective put&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The many uses of protective puts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Speculative - using leverage to place a bearish bet&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Defensive - a &amp;ldquo;married put&amp;rdquo; can limit risk against the downside while maintaining the benefits of a long stock position&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The benefits of protective puts - maintain voting rights, collect dividends, maintain upside potential, limit tax liability&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;No free lunch - puts can be expensive&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Finding the sweet spot between buying too much insurance and paying too much time decay&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Put options vs. stop-loss order - which is preferable?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt; Tricks of the Trade:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;How to introduce the idea of portfolio protection to your clients&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Options are appropriate for every level of risk tolerance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;How to take the emotion out of the advisor/client relationship using options&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Practical tips for implementing puts into your practice&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;div style="overflow: hidden; color: #000000; background-color: #ffffff; text-align: left; text-decoration: none;"&gt;Read more: &lt;a style="color: #003399;" href="http://www.theoptionsinsider.com/radio/?id=330#ixzz1n9oBMUh8"&gt;http://www.theoptionsinsider.com/radio/?id=330#ixzz1n9oBMUh8&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;The Options Insider: Your Inside Source For Options Information &lt;/div&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="39383535" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/advisorsoption/AO2_ProtectivePut.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>54:32</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords>call,manager,financial,protection,asset,portfolio,option,advisor,protective,put</itunes:keywords>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Playing Defense with Protective Puts</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <title>Episode 1: Spreading The Gospel Of Options</title>
                    <pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2012 23:36:16 +0000</pubDate>
                    <guid isPermaLink="false">000aa61badfbe77ad6b83259fa32d517</guid>
                    <link>http://traffic.libsyn.com/advisorsoption/AdvisorsOptionPremiere.mp3</link>
                    <itunes:image href="http://assets.libsyn.com/content/4308451"/>
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to The Advisor's Option - The first radio program designed to help registered investment advisors, asset managers and financial planners properly manage risk using options. Join your hosts Mark Longo, Mike Cavanaugh (Know Your Options, Inc.), and Eric Cott (The Options Industry Council) as they dive into options education, outline tricks of the trade and update advisors with the latest industry buzz. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;span style="color: #000000;" color="#000000"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration: underline;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Options 101-Continuing Education&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &lt;/span&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #000000;" color="#000000"&gt;Who is the OIC?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #000000;" color="#000000"&gt;The results of a recent OIC study of option usage among advisors. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #000000;" color="#000000"&gt;Dealing with the dreaded "D" word. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #000000;" color="#000000"&gt;Options demand is growing and much of it is client-driven. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #000000;" color="#000000"&gt;How to differentiate your practice by using options as risk mitigation tools. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Why should advisors use options?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #000000;" color="#000000"&gt;What are options?&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;We break down all of the terms that may have confused you in the past?&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #000000;" color="#000000"&gt;What is a call?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #000000;" color="#000000"&gt;What is a put?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #000000;" color="#000000"&gt;What is a multiplier?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #000000;" color="#000000"&gt;How can I use options to generate leverage?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #000000;" color="#000000"&gt;What are the Greeks?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #000000;" color="#000000"&gt;What do in-the-money, at-the-money and out-of-the-money mean?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #000000;" data-mce-style="color: #000000;" color="#000000"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration: underline;"&gt;Tricks of the Trade&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Practical tips for adopting options into your practice.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Eric discusses OIC's Seven Simple Steps for incorporating options into an advisory practice.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Finding the hidden derivatives exposure that may already be lurking in your portfolios.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #000000;" color="#000000"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color: #000000;" data-mce-style="color: #000000;" color="#000000"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration: underline;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration: underline;"&gt; Buzz&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #000000;" data-mce-style="color: #000000;" color="#000000"&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Developments from the world of options that will impact advisors.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Large pension funds are beginning to allocate resources toward asset managers with derivatives expertise.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Record options volume coming from retail investors...don't be outpaced by your clients.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #000000;" color="#000000"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color: #000000;" color="#000000"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #000000;" color="#000000"&gt;To read the full study mentioned in Options 101, visit &lt;a style="color: #ff0000;" href="http://www.optionseducation.org/advisor" target="_blank"&gt;www.optionseducation.org/advisor&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div style="overflow: hidden; color: #000000; background-color: #ffffff; text-align: left; text-decoration: none;"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Read more: &lt;a style="color: #003399;" href="http://www.theoptionsinsider.com/radio/?id=319#ixzz1n9j7qsDE"&gt;http://www.theoptionsinsider.com/radio/?id=319#ixzz1n9j7qsDE&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;The Options Insider: Your Inside Source For Options Information &lt;/div&gt;</description>
                    <enclosure length="46218621" type="audio/mpeg" url="http://traffic.libsyn.com/advisorsoption/AdvisorsOptionPremiere.mp3"/>
                    <itunes:duration>01:04:01</itunes:duration>
                    <itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
                    <itunes:keywords>how,to,calls,trade,manager,fund,pension,financial,asset,options,option,puts,hedge,advisor,planner,derivative,protective,put</itunes:keywords>
                    <itunes:subtitle>Spreading The Gospel Of Options</itunes:subtitle>
                </item>
            </channel>
        </rss>
    </httpclient:body>
</httpclient:response>